<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Altcoin Trading</title>
    <description>Altcoin Trading is the forex of cryptocurrencies, with bitcoin as the base currency.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 06:00:54 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 06:00:54 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.4.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ripple vs Stellar</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Bitfinex has added Ripple trading recently (May 19 announcement &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bitfinex.com/posts/204&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;), and according to the crypto trading myths that should mean the rally is over. They say, whenever a mainstream exchange with fiat deposits adds a coin, the smart money leaves it and sells to the laggards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Ripple, a double-top going on is already old news:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/uploads/2017/05/21/hJtMYhLc.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/uploads/2017/05/21/hJtMYhLc.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is what the lovely Ripple chart looks like in 1D version on Bitfinex:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/x/ctF9dUWV&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/x/ctF9dUWV&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;would-you-buy-ripple-now&quot;&gt;Would you buy Ripple now?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buy Ripple only of you trust its fundamentals, as a long term investment - and this is entirely your call. There is no problem storing it - &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ledgerwallet.com/r/e274?path=/products/ledger-nano-s&quot;&gt;Ledger Nano S&lt;/a&gt; has a Ripple wallet now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ripples-fundamentals&quot;&gt;Ripple’s Fundamentals&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To some altcoin traders, Ripple is a &lt;em&gt;centralized bankster scamcoin&lt;/em&gt;, a sort of “step back” in the world of crypto. To others, Ripple being &lt;a href=&quot;https://dealbook.nytimes.com/2013/11/11/the-rush-to-coin-virtual-money-with-real-value/?_php=true&amp;amp;_type=blogs&amp;amp;_r=1&quot;&gt;backed by banks&lt;/a&gt; is actually a good, reassuring sign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some things to keep in mind:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ripple is not a blockchain.&lt;/strong&gt; No blockchain also means there is no scaling problem and so in this way, Ripple as a medium for payments and settlements is better. The Ripple network works in such a way that transactions are forgotten once they are through so the ledger doesn’t grow as fast as blockchains do (all of them, Ethereum too).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Ripple, only address balances are kept - no histories. Meaning, &lt;strong&gt;Ripple is only a payment protocol&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ripple cannot be mined. Transactions get validated via consensus mechanism where participants are responsible to choose a set of validators that will not be fraudulent: &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/technical-faq-ripple-consensus-ledger/&quot;&gt;https://ripple.com/technical-faq-ripple-consensus-ledger/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/i6mhQcpPtyk&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/i6mhQcpPtyk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; custom-element=&quot;amp-youtube&quot; src=&quot;https://cdn.ampproject.org/v0/amp-youtube-0.1.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;amp-youtube data-videoid=&quot;i6mhQcpPtyk&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; height=&quot;360&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-youtube&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ripples-competition-stellar&quot;&gt;Ripple’s Competition: Stellar&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stellar makes it possible to send remittances cheaply across borders via its tokens, lumens. Originally, Stellar was based on the Ripple protocol (and founded by one of the Ripple founders) but after changes in the Ripple codebase Stellar forked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compared to Ripple being picked up mostly by banks, Stellar is a platform that gets used &lt;a href=&quot;http://fortune.com/2016/12/06/fintech-stellar-blockchain-stripe-remittances/&quot;&gt;IRL in non-profits&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;On a call with Fortune, McCaleb, Stellar’s cofounder and chief technology officer, expressed his desire to connect everyone in the world through the Stellar network. “We’re trying to be an Internet-level protocol for payments,” he said, drawing an analogy to SMTP, a standard for email transmission.
He added: “We want everybody to plug into it and for money to float seamlessly.”Other companies are also competing to become the standard for blockchain-based cross-border payments. Among them are McCaleb’s former firm Ripple, and Chain, a fintech startup backed by Visa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no mining in Stellar. Confirmations are done by selected trusted nodes - AKA Stellar Consensus Protocol. To a non-techie it is similar to Ripple: In Bitcoin, any miner is a trusted node by default, in consensus mechanism participants choose a trusted set of validators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reality is more complex:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;At a low level, the consensus mechanism used by Stellar is a decentralized version of PBFT called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stellar.org/papers/stellar-consensus-protocol.pdf&quot;&gt;Stellar Consensus Protocol&lt;/a&gt;, whereas &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/dev-blog/consensus-whitepaper-released/&quot;&gt;Ripple uses probabilistic voting&lt;/a&gt;. Those are fairly different even though they both tackle solving the same problem of reaching consensus between nodes. SCP biases towards correctness at the expense of liveness; Ripple follows a model similar to Bitcoin allowing ledger forks to occur temporarily and relying on majority validation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is not clear from this but the Stellar network &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stellar.org/developers/guides/concepts/ledger.html&quot;&gt;remembers transactional history&lt;/a&gt;. “Transactions are now a series of operations that affect the state of the world. For example, a single transaction can trivially say A sends to B if B sends to C. These abstractions, coupled with the network’s distributed exchange, produce a surprisingly rich vocabulary for contracts. Bonds, escrow, collateralized debt and the Lightning Network are all possible on the network.” - via &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinmagazine.com/articles/stellar-s-jed-mccaleb-what-s-new-on-the-upgraded-stellar-network-1452109082/&quot;&gt;bitcoinmagazine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;At the system level, &lt;strong&gt;Stellar’s native currency is inflationary whereas Ripple’s is not&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More to this below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;At the ledger operation level, Stellar adopted a very &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.faqs.org/rfcs/rfc1832.html&quot;&gt;strict API based off XDR&lt;/a&gt;, Ripple is built on top of &lt;a href=&quot;https://developers.google.com/protocol-buffers/&quot;&gt;Google Protocol Buffers&lt;/a&gt;. XDR can be thought of as “statically typed” vs “dynamically typed” for something like proto buf: the tradeoffs made are speed of development (in Ripple) vs safety and correctness (for Stellar’s approach).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-main-difference-between-Stellar-and-Ripple-protocols&quot;&gt;via Quora&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-inflation&quot;&gt;The Inflation&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stellar has limited supply with built-in inflation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stellar.org/developers/guides/concepts/inflation.html&quot;&gt;via stellar.org:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Stellar distributed network has a built-in, fixed, nominal inflation mechanism. New lumens are added to the network at the rate of 1% each year. Each week, the protocol distributes these lumens to any account that gets over .05% of the “votes” from other accounts in the network.
Using the set options operation, every account selects another account as its inflation destination, or nominee to receive new currency. The inflation destination will persist until changed with another set options operation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ripple has limited supply buy the native currency gets destroyed with successful transactions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.xrpchat.com/topic/2207-xrps-deflationary-nature/&quot;&gt;via xrpchat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q:&lt;/strong&gt; I guess this is a very basic-level question, but I don’t see it usually comes up on this forum whenever people speculate about XRP’s future price:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the deflationary nature of XRP, do you believe this feature might ever be an obstacle for XRP’s success? I mean, people will tend to save their XRP and not to spend them because they will be supposed to get more valuable over time, but at the same time this could also result in a constraint of XRP market and liquidity. By contrast, the Stellar network automatically applies a small inflation rate of 1% to its currency that could help solve this issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is your opinion? Could this be an original design flaw of XRP?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&lt;/strong&gt; Small amount of xrp gets destroyed with each transaction and its expected that as demand and transaction will increase that destruction rate will increase which will cause the same effect as inflation because of slowly decreasing supply but since things are in initial stage its gonna take long time in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-giveaway&quot;&gt;The giveaway&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you hold Bitcoins you can invest in Stellar for free (which is frankly a no-brainer). &lt;strong&gt;There is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stellar.org/blog/bitcoin-claim-lumens/&quot;&gt;second Stellar giveaway for Bitcoin hodlers lined up for the summer 2017&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; The giveaway starts on July the 5th and the only drawback is you will need to have a facebook profile that confirms you reside in an unrestricted state:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Due to regulatory restrictions, this program is closed to residents of the U.S. states of New York, Georgia, New Hampshire, and Connecticut as well as the nations of Iran, Cuba, North Korea, and other countries subject to sanctions by the United States.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s probably still enough time to make one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-ad layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; type=&quot;adsense&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-6979812205705127&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;4445157690&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-ad&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;so-ripple-is-deflationary&quot;&gt;So, Ripple is deflationary.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;There is currently circulating 38,532,538,149 XRP out of 99,994,681,824.21 XRP.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;There is currently circulating 9,624,904,739 XLM out of 102,920,806,155 XLM.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both coins are really only possibly valuable for payment processing – at least as long as Paypal or something like that is not an option. Well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Unlike some other fintechs, Ripple is bank centric. Banks connect to the Ripple network not their customers. This has two big benefits. First, customers are used to trusting banks (which is better than having to get comfortable with entrusting your money to some fintech you never heard of). Second, regulators are comfortable with banks (which means they will not pull the plug on Ripple as they might with non bank fintechs). - via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/ripple-vs-swift-payment-revolution-david-blair&quot;&gt;linkedin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is something to the obsession with bank coins. They say that when the wall street decides to pour all the money into something you would be stupid for not taking the ride with them. It’s just that in the case of Ripple, the banks &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/ripple-vs-swift-payment-revolution-david-blair&quot;&gt;are thrilled to use Ripple as a layer&lt;/a&gt; but that can only increase the value of Ripple by burning the currency as transactions get settled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, given the hype on altcoin forums whenever anything gets official acknowledgement from the shiny official people up there in the institutions, it’s quite likely the “fundamental” price growth is going to be small compared to the &lt;em&gt;buy the rumor&lt;/em&gt; hype. In other words, bubbles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, Stellar looks more compatible with Bitcoin - maybe as an offchain layer, one day?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 02:38:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/ripple-vs-stellar</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/ripple-vs-stellar</guid>
        
        <category>feature</category>
        
        
        <category>altcoins</category>
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How the legacy finance might be feeling about cryptocurrencies</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Most of the people who have invested in cryptocurrencies in the past years were not professional investors. And a big chunk of those who went into altcoin trading might not have been rich before they hodl’d Ethereum since it was $9 – or something like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in the day when Ethereum didn’t exist yet there were running jokes in Bitcoin forums about one day getting as rich as to be able to bribe senators. Well, these days nobody jokes about things like that anymore. By now the people from two three years back are probably just getting closer to where the target audience of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mauldineconomics.com/&quot;&gt;Mauldin Economics&lt;/a&gt; is: people who have earned some, yet aren’t the ones who move the ocean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below are excerpts taken from a today’s newsletter on Mauldin Economics. The letter does not even mention let alone endorse cryptocurrencies (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hrrF6Wz61HE&quot;&gt;although the autors have in the past&lt;/a&gt;), but it is an interesting insight into the minds of a lot people who on Reddit would be called &lt;em&gt;normies&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apparently, no matter how zerohedge “every day is a doomsday” it sounds, these people might be starting to worry about the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.zerohedge.com/news/2016-05-11/what-will-global-economy-look-after-great-reset&quot;&gt;Great Reset&lt;/a&gt;, the re-evaluation of the markets. The &lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.is/djUcU&quot;&gt;newsletter&lt;/a&gt; seems to be targeting people who have good income and reinvest the extra money so that it doesn’t lie around losing value. That means, a lot of people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We need […] to restructure our portfolios to make sure we get as much of our wealth as we possibly can to the “other side” of the coming crisis […] We just have to get there with our assets intact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you read the &lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.is/djUcU&quot;&gt;full thing&lt;/a&gt; you’ll learn why the debt-economy could collapse and all the rest of it in detail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, the newsletter is primarily a pitch and the main point consist mainly of the modern portfolio theory getting beaten. If there is a truly global crisis …&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I believe that diversifying among asset classes will simply diversify your losses during the next global recession.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hence …&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I think the answer lies in diversifying among noncorrelated &lt;em&gt;trading strategies&lt;/em&gt; that can invest in any asset class.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;… And that’s about it, with one little detail - it’s focused on ETFs. Diverse ETF trading strategies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;You know how somebody will talk about getting a time-consuming task done and then the next person says, “There’s an app for that”? No matter what asset you want, there’s now an ETF for that. I am constantly amazed how narrowly focused ETFs can be. There is now an ETF that focuses its investments just on companies in the ETF industry. It’s not all large-cap-index ETFs anymore. &lt;strong&gt;Some really small, niche-market ETFs have attracted significant capital.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I find interesting is how they particularly consider the niche ETFs. It almost sounds like they’d take any ETF, and perhaps the more outlandish the better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seems that in case there were a cryptocurrency ETF, there would be plenty of buyers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 09:11:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/diversification-craze</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/diversification-craze</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
        <category>eth</category>
        
        <category>altcoins</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A &quot;This Is Gentlemen&quot; Moment</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Something sober to thin down the moonjuice before the weekend:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ethereum-past-100&quot;&gt;Ethereum past $100&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;r/ethtrader&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I’m not liking this whole “Bitcoin to the Moon on devasted fundamentals,” thing we got going on right now. Having to resist the fomo.
I certainly hope those off chain scaling fanatics drop the price if BTC forks,I don’t want to be left behind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-uuid=&quot;ba94139b-7ccb-4cc3-93bc-42da8a30efa1&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2017-05-19T12:12:38.822Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/6c0opi/we_hit_100_mirin_my_btc_hodlings/dhrcy8s/&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/6c0opi/we_hit_100_mirin_my_btc_hodlings/&quot;&gt;We hit $100!! &amp;#x27;Mirin my BTC hodlings? 😜&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What caused the jump?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;could be ripple pump earlier this week is selling off into ETH + big announcements coming up next week.
but the real answer is no one really knows except more buyers than sellers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-uuid=&quot;0fbdf20c-6593-469c-a796-129e21884251&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2017-05-19T12:14:01.121Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/6c0opi/we_hit_100_mirin_my_btc_hodlings/dhr5ms4/&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/6c0opi/we_hit_100_mirin_my_btc_hodlings/&quot;&gt;We hit $100!! &amp;#x27;Mirin my BTC hodlings? 😜&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/Ethereum/&quot;&gt;Facebook group&lt;/a&gt; posters remain quite conservative, expecting mostly $200 or $300 ETH by the end of 2017, although $500 can be seen too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;bitcoin-hitting-2000-on-bitfinex&quot;&gt;Bitcoin hitting $2000 on Bitfinex&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;r/bitcoinmarkets&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;u/Merlin560: &lt;strong&gt;Point and Figure Update&lt;/strong&gt;
It did not take long to hit our first price target at $1,940. And now we are at the &lt;strong&gt;Long Pole&lt;/strong&gt;.
The price looks like it just keeps getting stronger. The Alts continue move up as well. Is this because the Japanese are going nuts? Is it because there are bad bongos coming out of China? Or is it just “growth.”
Anyone telling you definitively what is driving this will be lying to you.
For now the pole grows higher. If it turns quickly expect to see lows around $1,800. Obviously, that is not the end of the world.
But, I am going to sit back and enjoy this. It was payday today…and I made more on paper before six AM this morning that I got paid last week. Not a bad place to me.
Enjoy it while its going up.
PS: Happy Birthday to my daughter!
The Daily Chart http://imgur.com/a/MA8UM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-uuid=&quot;c46c276e-da5f-45f8-9339-6fda983100cb&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2017-05-19T12:01:28.838Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/6c1eim/daily_discussion_friday_may_19_2017/dhrh84o/&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/6c1eim/daily_discussion_friday_may_19_2017/&quot;&gt;[Daily Discussion] Friday, May 19, 2017&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who don’t know, a “long pole” warning means a correction is due. However, in bubbles these corrections sometimes don’t come – the worse is then the burst.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 02:19:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/all-green</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/all-green</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Monero mining malware</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Just a few days after the WannaCry mass ransomware a Monero mining malware has been reported.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-ad layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; type=&quot;adsense&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-6979812205705127&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;4445157690&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-ad&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After WannaCry, UIWIX Ransomware and Monero-Mining Malware Follow Suit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WannaCry ransomware’s outbreak during the weekend was mitigated by having its kill switch domain registered. It was only a matter of time, however, for other cybercriminals to follow suit. Case in point: the emergence of UIWIX ransomware (detected by Trend Micro as RANSOM_UIWIX.A) and one notable Trojan our sensors detected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from WannaCry and UIWIX, our sensors also detected a Trojan delivered using EternalBlue—Adylkuzz (TROJ_COINMINER.WN). This malware turns infected systems into zombies and steals its resources in order to mine for the cryptocurrency Monero.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.trendmicro.com/trendlabs-security-intelligence/wannacry-uiwix-ransomware-monero-mining-malware-follow-suit/&quot;&gt;Read the full report.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 03:41:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/monero-mining-malware</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/monero-mining-malware</guid>
        
        
        <category>xmr</category>
        
        <category>altcoins</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Peerplays crowdfund ends in 3 days</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;At the current stage the PPY tokens cost $5.20 each, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.altcointrading.net/ico-regulations&quot;&gt;ICO - sorry, the crowdfund&lt;/a&gt; - ends in three days at 15:00 UTC on 14 May 2017, the PPY tokens will be distributed to participants on 30 May 2017. You can invest BTC, ETH, LTC, DOGE, BitShares and &lt;a href=&quot;http://prntscr.com/f6pdj3&quot;&gt;couple other coins to participate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.peerplays.com/crowdfund/&quot;&gt;https://www.peerplays.com/crowdfund/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;whats-peerplays&quot;&gt;What’s Peerplays&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Peerplays aim to work as a betting platform. Because it’s on the blockchain, it will be available from all countries. Users place a bet, the bet is processed on the blockchain (it’s a dapp), profits are distributed via PPY - the Peerplays profit sharing tokens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is an interesting concept, except the red flag that comes with everything that is &lt;em&gt;the UBER of [industry]&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Peerplays will eliminate the need for traditional bookies in their sports betting.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is this problem with people who keep coming back to estabilished bookies because everyone keeps coming back to estabilished bookies. Peerplays would require people to trust a dapp and it would require them to work with a dapp, that’s two very new things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But who knows. The Bookie app that should enable betting is not going to be out before November 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However unlikely, maybe it will be sports betting made simple, and maybe the network effect will not play out because that’s a more substantial thing with poker rooms and trading platforms - places where you need other people to come by otherwise the experience sucks. Sports betting is something you do on your own, after all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either way, this is what everyone likes to hear preferentially these days: &lt;strong&gt;Peerplays is a divident paying token&lt;/strong&gt;. Yay!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peerplays Makes HODLing Profitable with Automatic Fee-Sharing Distributions: “Peerplays is aiming to be the first truly Decentralized Autonomous Cooperative (DAC) [...] With this new profit sharing module, all the &lt;strong&gt;fees that Peerplays charges&lt;/strong&gt; for smart contract operations and peer-to-peer wagering will be &lt;strong&gt;distributed directly to the holders of the core Peerplays blockchain tokens&lt;/strong&gt;, just like a traditional co-op pays &lt;strong&gt;dividends to its shareholders&lt;/strong&gt;.” &lt;a href=&quot;https://steemit.com/peerplays/@cryptoprometheus/peerplays-makes-hodling-profitable-with-automatic-fee-sharing-distributions&quot;&gt;- via steem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;resources&quot;&gt;Resources&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ICO:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.peerplays.com/news/faq/&quot;&gt;Peerplays FAQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.peerplays.com/news/primary_crowdfund/&quot;&gt;Crowdfund info&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People and networks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/FalloutComplex&quot;&gt;FalloutComplex on Reddit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ca.linkedin.com/in/jonathanbahai&quot;&gt;Johnatan Bahai on LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://nl.linkedin.com/in/dan-maloney&quot;&gt;Daniel Maloney of http://www.pbsa.info/ on LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;. Speaking of PBSA, despite fancy sounding names, their &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pbsa.info/partners/&quot;&gt;partners&lt;/a&gt; are a freelancer on Upwork and a “&lt;a href=&quot;http://prntscr.com/f6pjxo&quot;&gt;master marketer and speaker on Internet marketing, success, happiness and the enlightened workplace&lt;/a&gt;”.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://t.me/PeerplaysBlockchain&quot;&gt;Peerplays Telegram Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://soundcloud.com/beyond-bitcoin-hangouts/e167-beyond-bitcoin-peerplays-update-blockpay-ceo-talks-privacy-faddats-nanochip-implant&quot;&gt;The CEO Michael Maloney in an old interview at Beyond Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 12:49:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/peerplays</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/peerplays</guid>
        
        
        <category>altcoins</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is the end of ICOs approaching?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A lot has changed since &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.altcointrading.net/ico-2016/&quot;&gt;the last post on ICOs&lt;/a&gt; in summer 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;lawmakers-have-noticed&quot;&gt;Lawmakers have noticed&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There has been a post on 2nd May 2017 at law111 and elsewhere that caught the attention of the crypto community. To be honest, it was an interesting thing for some die hard bitcoiners since they started projecting the EndOfEtherium™ - the ICOs will get regulated, there will be no reason to buy ETH anymore, ETH will collapse and BTC will get it’s market cap share back. It is a bit too far out there, nonetheless there seem to be regulations in the making. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.law111.com/11state-lawmakers-increasing-their-focus-on-vc-and-blockchain-technology&quot;&gt;post on law111&lt;/a&gt; says:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In early 2017, multiple state legislatures have taken action reflecting their recognition of the potential impact of virtual currency and blockchain technology. These actions have ranged from requests for further information regarding the technology to an active debate regarding a specific use case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…continuing with a state-by-state US legislations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a more human readable form, this was discussed at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crowdfundinsider.com/2017/03/96598-initial-coin-offering-probably-regulated-securities-law/&quot;&gt;crowdfundinginsider.com&lt;/a&gt; in March already:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;For those of you not familiar with what ICOs are, here’s a quick summary. Lots of folks working in the blockchain world needed money to fund their project or startup. So they decided to invent their own “coin” variant and sold those coins to fund their project/startup, in exchange for some financial upside in the project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Sound familiar? That’s because it is. This is the story of every capital-hungry startup/business/entrepreneur.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I’ve heard ICOs described as a “donation with financial upside” or “crowdsale” (whatever that is), and a number of other things—to try to avoid securities laws. First of all, a donation is a donation— you’re giving away money (or bitcoin), and there is no financial upside to a donation. A “crowdsale” of tokens—to the extent those “tokens” represent securities—is still a security. There are a number of different things that ICOs are doing, so it’s difficult to address the entire industry in one article, but let me impart some guidance to make this easier to understand: If walks like a duck and quacks like a duck, its probably a duck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;eric-voorhees-was-the-first-to-test-the-waters&quot;&gt;Eric Voorhees was the first to test the waters&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The penalty for such offense is a fine and restriction for the person that was the head of the enterprise - typically they cannot serve as a chief executive of any company again, or they cannot raise capital again. This is supposed to mean the end of the person’s career although apparently &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/litigation/admin/2014/33-9592.pdf&quot;&gt;Eric Voorhees is still around and doing well&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;June 3, 2014, via SEC.gov/litigation – Respondent has undertaken to: Forgo directly or indirectly, including, but not limited to, through any entity owned or controlled by Respondent, participating in any issuance of any security in an unregistered
transaction, in exchange for bitcoins or other virtual currency, for a period of five years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His later crypto-focused company that he founded, ShapeShift, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crunchbase.com/organization/shapeshift#/entity&quot;&gt;had normal funding rounds&lt;/a&gt; like your usual startup would have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-is-the-regulation-actually-for&quot;&gt;What is the regulation actually for?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, it is supposed to be a way to check the entrepreneur, in theory it should reduce the amount of scam artists in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First thing, however, it is safe to say it will take the regulators a while to figure out how to deal with the very new thing an ICO is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another thing is, many people who had done ICOs before are certainly safe. There is several hundreds of crypto tokens by now. Some of them were funded by pseudonymous identities. In some cases the project that was backing them doesn’t exist anymore. Nobody will ever know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wait…is there a way this could possibly be done in the future as well? Could this actually mean the scams will not go away, not even with the regulation?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;new-icos-in-2017&quot;&gt;New ICOs in 2017&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tim Draper has been “the person in the news” this week when he announced his participation in Tezos token ICO. Some people even said, &lt;em&gt;this might be the last ICO before regulations so I might just invest&lt;/em&gt;. That’s totally a … reason /s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pehub.com/2017/05/investor-tim-draper-to-participate-in-blockchain-token-sale-for-first-time-reuters/#&quot;&gt;Via Reuters News:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Draper, an early supporter of bitcoin and its underlying blockchain financial ledger technology, told Reuters in an interview he will for the first time participate in a so-called “initial coin offering” (ICO) of Tezos slated later [in May 2017].
“The best thing I can do is lead by example,” said Draper, on his plan to participate in Tezos’ token offering. “Over time, I actually feel that some of these tokens are going to improve the world, and I want to make sure those tokens get promoted as well. I think Tezos is one of those tokens.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With someone so influential backing a token, this could likely be a self fulfulling prophecy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tezos&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tezos is a self-governing technology running with proof of stake. All upgrades and changes can be done automatically, without forking and without political infights. There should also be incentive for making the inovation on the Tezos ledger rather than forking off an appcoin. The Tezor creators argue the appcoins dilute the value of the parent coin rather than contribute to the network effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;button&quot; href=&quot;https://www.tezos.com/&quot;&gt;Tezos Homepage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your usual popular ICO 2017 resources:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/1216757095051232/&quot;&gt;Facebook Group&lt;/a&gt; - closed group, login and ask for membership. The group is not very active, mostly just people posting announcements.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.icocountdown.com/&quot;&gt;ICO Countdown&lt;/a&gt; - the only site that has been featured here in 2016 and stays top.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://icoindex.com/&quot;&gt;Icoindex.com&lt;/a&gt;and their Slack channel - &lt;a href=&quot;https://icoindex-official.herokuapp.com/&quot;&gt;invite&lt;/a&gt; - they are also on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/ICOindex/&quot;&gt;facebook and are not getting very good&lt;/a&gt; reviews.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;you-still-have-to-make-your-own-decision&quot;&gt;You still have to make your own decision&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look at the idea, the team, the marketing, the roadmap and last but not least the token. The price, the allocation (how much will the developers have?) and inflation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The market cap thing is flawed, there is a good in-depth article about that on &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.sia.tech/want-to-deflate-the-token-bubble-fix-the-market-cap-indicator-d50f7f1e1ec4&quot;&gt;blog.sia.tech&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Take Zcash for example. It has a current market cap of $110 million with a total supply of 1.2 million ZEC, but over the next five years 9.8 million ZEC will enter existence. This super-high inflation will drastically increase supply each year, which in turn will affect the market cap. There is no way, however, for the average investor to quickly discover this inflation factor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We recommend adding a new metric called inflation factor that indicates how the market cap could be affected over the next five years by token inflation:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Inflation factor = (new supply over 5 years) / (current total supply) * 100%.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Inflation factors calculated for the top 15 tokens &lt;a href=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1600/1*goypbtaXje1QRL7KGoAK4g.png&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see that only by making economically sound decision rather than spreading your money randomly across all ICOs will shrink the amount of feasible ICOs a lot. But indeed, reason is never enough to stop the bubble.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 14:46:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/ico-regulations</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/ico-regulations</guid>
        
        
        <category>eth</category>
        
        <category>altcoins</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grayscale did it</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en-gb&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;The Ethereum Classic Investment Trust is now live for eligible accredited investors! &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/ViBWrnpmaP&quot;&gt;https://t.co/ViBWrnpmaP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;cc: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/EthereumTrust&quot;&gt;@EthereumTrust&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETC&amp;amp;src=ctag&quot;&gt;$ETC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Grayscale (@GrayscaleInvest) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/GrayscaleInvest/status/857217741161459715&quot;&gt;26 April 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 09:06:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/etc-etf/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/etc-etf/</guid>
        
        
        <category>coins</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Gnosis thing</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/coins/gnosis.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/coins/gnosis.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Wtf is Gnosis?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-ad layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; type=&quot;adsense&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-6979812205705127&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;4445157690&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-ad&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, Poloniex announced on their website they will list Gnosis token one week after the end of the auction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Gnosis GNO tokens will be available
for trading on Poloniex one week
after the close of the auction.

Posted by OldManKidd at 2017-04-24 19:28:26
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en-gb&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Gnosis &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/search?q=%24GNO&amp;amp;src=ctag&quot;&gt;$GNO&lt;/a&gt; tokens will be available for trading on Poloniex one week after the close of the auction. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/GlwkoAO1UE&quot;&gt;https://t.co/GlwkoAO1UE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Poloniex Exchange (@Poloniex) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/856570173112942593&quot;&gt;24 April 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It came shortly after the controversial &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=1876467.0&quot;&gt;delisting of 17 coins&lt;/a&gt;. Some traders were even talking about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoMarkets/comments/668gim/poloniex_delisting_some_apparently_good_coins_on/&quot;&gt;broken trust&lt;/a&gt; and moving &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoMarkets/comments/668gim/poloniex_delisting_some_apparently_good_coins_on/dgglcbv/?utm_content=permalink&amp;amp;utm_medium=front&amp;amp;utm_source=reddit&amp;amp;utm_name=CryptoMarkets&quot;&gt;coins to bittrex&lt;/a&gt;. Anyway. Apparently the time has come to have fun on new and totally different altcoin markets!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-is-gnosis-for&quot;&gt;What is Gnosis for&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a prediction multi-market where you can create your own markets for events if you have WIZ tokens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You get WIZ tokens in exchange for your Gnosis tokens if you decide to lock them in a smart contract for some period of time.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You get Gnosis tokens for ETH, Gnosis runs on Ethereum.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The token model is not implemented yet.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The auction is over by now and people who bought the Gnosis tokens will receive them right before the trading will start at Polo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.gnosis.pm/what-are-gnosis-tokens-the-new-access-based-token-model-e59c5a490af6&quot;&gt;blog.gnosis.pm/what-are-gnosis…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;why-it-would-make-crypto-traders-rage&quot;&gt;Why it would make crypto traders rage&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…if they still had emotions?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) The Gnosis token sale ended at a theoretical 312.5 Million valuation.
2) Only 4.17 % of all tokens have been distributed to you early investors, the other 95.83 % of the tokens is in hands of the Gnosis team.
3) The Gnosis team now owns 299 million USD in artificial token value. They’ve invested 0 USD.
4) In contrast, the investors who paid 100 % of the money, invested and own 13 million USD in tokens.
5) Let me be more clear: You paid 31.25 USD per Gnosis token and as a collective, have only received 4.17 % of all tokens.
6) Now take a seat before you read number 7
7) The actual value of the Gnosis tokens is 13 million USD (this is all of the actual money brought in by the investors) divided by 10 million tokens. That means each individual token now has a factual value of 1.3 USD.
8) As of now, your net result on your investment is -95 %
9) We did warn you: http://i.imgur.com/WAVLXWE.png - You triggered the worst case scenario in this graph
10) And warned by /r/ethtrader
11) But you just didn’t want to listen, did you&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/67ax24/to_all_gnosis_token_holders_take_a_seat_before/&quot;&gt;r/ethtrader/comments/67ax…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-media&quot;&gt;The media&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;obligatory-what-does-forbes-say&quot;&gt;Obligatory, what does Forbes say?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/rogeraitken/2017/04/24/gnosis-prediction-market-scores-12-5m-in-record-breaking-crypto-auction/#1aa4f80ae87d&quot;&gt;forbes.com/sites/rogeraitken/2017/04/24/…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnosis, a decentralized platform for prediction markets that uses “crowdsourced wisdom” sourced globally and built on Ethereum technology, has set a new record by raising $12.5 million (m) in a token offering via a Dutch auction, the first successful one of its kind in crypto, and the fastest crowdsale to date to sell out more than $10m.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;so-what-do-people-say&quot;&gt;So what do people say?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Starting at over $300mill market cap?  Dump city (-90%)  RIP ICO investors.&lt;/em&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/3ideRaven/status/856570546204663809&quot;&gt;twitter, @3ideRaven&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;So you are listing a coin where the devs own 95% of the total supply with more ICOS coming? Just wow…&lt;/em&gt; - &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/GetYourBounty/status/856614171768750082&quot;&gt;twitter, @GetYourBounty&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember though, it’s not an obvious short either - it’s the same as DASH where the empire can move the price as needed because they have their precious instamine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-ad layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; type=&quot;adsense&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-6979812205705127&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;4445157690&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-ad&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 08:06:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/gnosis/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/gnosis/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
        <category>coins</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Opinion: Time in the market vs timing the market</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/editorial/likeaboss.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/editorial/likeaboss.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: In the long run, time in the market beats timing the market.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-ad layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; type=&quot;adsense&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-6979812205705127&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;4445157690&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-ad&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s take a quick look at the difference between trading and investing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When you trade&lt;/strong&gt; you don’t care which way the market goes as long as your position is making you money. All you need is to be right about the direction. For what it’s worth, even if you hold a shitcoin with absolutely no future and it pumps, you are making money - not that it wouldn’t resemble casino though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When you invest&lt;/strong&gt; you are looking for value and you put in money that you realistically won’t need even in a few years time. You go for value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;which-one-is-more-profitable&quot;&gt;Which one is more profitable?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They say that in the long run, time in the market beats timing the market. With the short term direction you cannot know for sure - even technical and fundamental analysis together with Reddit sentiment can only give you what’s likely, not what’s hundred percent sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Realistically you have higher chance to be wrong in timing the market than you have when carefully picking an asset which you think has a long term chance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Time in the market is so much more important for an investor’s long-term returns than timing the market. This is something The Motley Fool takes to heart, because no one can accurately know when to get in and get out.  […] “Generally that tends to be true. But, alas, there are no firm rules here, and context is king in pretty much all of this. For example, there are times where valuations get super lofty.”&lt;/em&gt; - via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fool.com/investing/2016/07/01/time-in-the-market-vs-timing-the-market.aspx&quot;&gt;The Motley Fool&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;hodlers-hate&quot;&gt;Hodlers Hate&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These days everyone hates the hodler cult in both BTC and ETH. The truth is though, as a hodler who is in a position for the long run, your biggest risk really is &lt;em&gt;losing your position&lt;/em&gt;. And the best way to lose it is to try and sell high to rebuy lower. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.altcointrading.net/litecoin-pump/#the-technicals&quot;&gt;In a bull market, the low won’t be so low.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, how should you look at an asset if you want to hold?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investors look at the following characteristics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1/ Real-World Adoption™ - That’s why &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.altcointrading.net/zoe-ethereum-alphabay/&quot;&gt;Ethereum on Alphabay&lt;/a&gt; is bigger a deal than &lt;a href=&quot;http://raiden.network/&quot;&gt;Raiden network&lt;/a&gt; or dapps even though both of the latter features are really cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2/ &lt;a href=&quot;https://etherscan.io/chart/tx/&quot;&gt;Transactions per day&lt;/a&gt; which is related to adoption, and &lt;a href=&quot;/eth-traders-tool/&quot;&gt;other network data&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3/ &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinmarketcap.com/&quot;&gt;Exchange volume per day&lt;/a&gt; and (anti)correlation with bitcoin to see how much of the use is just speculation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course all cryptocurrency is still very young though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-ad layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; type=&quot;adsense&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-6979812205705127&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;4445157690&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-ad&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;an-unlikely-altcoin-fundamental&quot;&gt;An unlikely altcoin fundamental&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/editorial/fuck.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/editorial/fuck.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What would happen if Ethereum lost Vitalik? Something quite explicit for sure, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Go for a business that any idiot can run - because sooner or later, an idiot probably is going to run it.” - Peter Lynch&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe this is a drawback of Ethereum as an investment asset. That &lt;strong&gt;doesn’t mean ETH wasn’t an outstanding trading opportunity&lt;/strong&gt; just recently - but that’s precisely the difference between trading and investment. For the &lt;em&gt;long&lt;/em&gt; long term, it’s a question how sustainable this is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, compare it to other popular altcoins on the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sure there are people who believe &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Monero/comments/61atcg/what_i_believe_is_holding_back_our_adoption_and/&quot;&gt;certain coins&lt;/a&gt; are lead by idiots at present already, while other coins are &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/notgrubles/status/851878073909862400/photo/1&quot;&gt;quickly&lt;/a&gt; getting &lt;a href=&quot;http://cointimes.tech/2017/04/napoleonbitcoin/&quot;&gt;there&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You shouldn’t blame people for holding on to assets with slower development and moronic leads. After all &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lindy_effect&quot;&gt;the longer the assets are surviving this misfortune the more valuable they are for the long run&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-ad layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; type=&quot;adsense&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-6979812205705127&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;4445157690&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-ad&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 12:24:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/time-vs-timing/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/time-vs-timing/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
        <category>coins</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Litecoin: This time it's different?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/emotions/up.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/emotions/up.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Wait is this up or down?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-ad layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; type=&quot;adsense&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-6979812205705127&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;4445157690&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-ad&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-rock&quot;&gt;The Rock&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Arthur Hayes of BitMEX made his prognosis in the last issue of their newsletter - &lt;a href=&quot;http://us3.campaign-archive1.com/?u=db45c09bdf20e1866bb32123f&amp;amp;id=256c134334&quot;&gt;available here&lt;/a&gt;, scroll down to &lt;em&gt;The Rock Is In The Building&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Litecoin has acted like a rock in trader’s bags since it hit its all time high of $40 in 2013. The technical merits of why Litecoin should be worth more than $0 are few and far between. Litecoin exists on life support only because Chinese traders for some reason enjoy trading it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Litecoin is some form of legacy. A BTC spinoff dangerously close to bitcoin only with the advantage of faster transactions, it is easy to implement for an exchange that already does BTC. The reason most people who aren’t bagholders buy and sell litecoin is they are bitcoin traders and &lt;a href=&quot;/altcoin-exchanges/&quot;&gt;want to move USD from one exchange to the other&lt;/a&gt; whenever BTC is too volatile or too FUD-ridden to be safely in. By the way, that’s also what people sometimes use DOGE for but LTC is more widely supported. For one thing, it’s the only non-fiat and non-BTC way to get out of OkCoin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;first-class-and-second-class&quot;&gt;First class and second class&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over time this developed into a popular strategy: Altcoin traders might trade the first class altcoins - think &lt;a href=&quot;/coin/eth/&quot;&gt;Ethereum&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;/coin/xmr/&quot;&gt;Monero&lt;/a&gt;. Once they feel like the bull cycle is soon to be over they park the money in the second grade alts that remain more or less stable. With the money in the second class they wait for another opportunity in the first class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second class coins rarely dump without pumping first so it’s not a totally unreasonable idea, especially if you don’t pick the parking coin completely by random. Sometimes the second grade coins do pump which makes for a nice benefit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-reason&quot;&gt;The Reason™&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless it wouldn’t be a proper pump without people coming up with arbitrary rationalization of the surge. In the case of the Litecoin surge the rationalization says it’s network scaling implementation that is currently still argued about in BTC. This way LTC could be a flagship - if anything the market is letting everybody know that &lt;em&gt;little less conversation little more action please&lt;/em&gt; is what makes the community happy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/chart/LTCBTC/cFRt8jgX-LTC-BTC-this-time-is-different-lol/&quot;&gt;btc_joe’s TradingView idea&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In a world where bitcoin gets bigger and bigger (and thus less and less likely to make any &lt;strong&gt;consensus changes&lt;/strong&gt; whether it be a hard fork or segwit, etc), ask yourself, does litecoin deserve a place in the market? I certainly have my opinion.  Not to mention, if it gets the &lt;strong&gt;lightning network&lt;/strong&gt; before bitcoin…are you excited about this technology? I certainly am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indeed, this news came in a moment where the market was so to say available to be affected by the news.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Litecoin was in a downtrend for all of 2016. Technically the price (relatively to BTC) was closing towards a support back from pre-pump 2013 (see BTC-e Quandl data &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.quandl.com/data/BTCE/BTCLTC&quot;&gt;https://www.quandl.com/data/BTCE/BTCLTC&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/ltcbtc-quandl.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/ltcbtc-quandl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soon after that the BTC ETF and BU FUD took over which helped as well. On the April fool’s day someone started signaling segwit on the LTC network originally as a joke but lo and behold, traders took it quite seriously because the discussion was ongoing since February already, see &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@thecryptoconomy/the-barely-discussed-incredible-benefit-of-the-lightning-network-4ce82c75eb58&quot;&gt;this medium.com post&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;With the adoption of Segregated Witness and the announcements of support progressing quickly within the Litecoin network, we may first get to see the full benefits of this technology on one of the original altcoins. With a smaller market cap and some distance from contentious Bitcoin politics, Litecoin is able to take greater risks. It may get to be the first to see this incredible innovation in action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;laggards-beware&quot;&gt;Laggards beware&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/litecoin-coinbase.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/litecoin-coinbase.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: You see that squishy?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Litecoin &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/GDAX&quot;&gt;@GDAX&lt;/a&gt; vol is over $10M. &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/brian_armstrong&quot;&gt;@brian_armstrong&lt;/a&gt;, I think it&amp;#39;s time we let people easily buy LTC with fiat on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/coinbase&quot;&gt;@coinbase&lt;/a&gt;. What do you say? 😁&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Charlie Lee (@SatoshiLite) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SatoshiLite/status/849792340357029888&quot;&gt;6 April 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The prognosis of Arthur Hayes in his &lt;a href=&quot;http://us3.campaign-archive1.com/?u=db45c09bdf20e1866bb32123f&amp;amp;id=256c134334&quot;&gt;newsletter&lt;/a&gt; is that LTC is bound to go down since GDAX got the USD pair too when it showed such a pretty activity now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is likely that this is what’s going to happen: GDAX is the exchange removed far from the Poloniex altcoin trading epicenter. It’s where a newly listed altcoin might be bought by laggards who don’t really know much about its market but hope to still make a buck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They’ll be buying the coins sold by those who bought at Polo early enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-technicals&quot;&gt;The Technicals&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the cryptowatch snapshot above you’ll probably be able to tell the current action looks like &lt;em&gt;wave 4&lt;/em&gt;. The people who timed it right took their profits but there is still some buying by those who came a bit late. It should still make for one more up before crashing though, and how big the crash will be, nobody knows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/BTC-squishies.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/BTC-squishies.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After all, altcoins in general are in a bull market. As such, the end of the wave cycle shouldn’t be as dreary as it was in 2013. In a bull market, the end of the cycle could be a simple consolidation and after a few weeks there could be more of the movement up north - see the image from the BTCUSD market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this case one should look into fundamentals for clarity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And in the case of litecoin, this doesn’t end up on a positive note: no real adoption, not much innovation. For cryptogeeks it’s a legacy, it’ll stick around for some time no matter what, but in the real world litecoin as a name is nonexistent. That shouldn’t make for an exciting future…Unless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-lightning-network-plans&quot;&gt;The lightning network plans&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…Unless LN. The Lightning Network can bridge channels between different blockchains, possibly allowing users to use their LTC at places that accepts Bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charlie Lee via &lt;a href=&quot;https://litecointalk.io/t/my-vision-for-segwit-and-lightning-networks-on-litecoin-and-bitcoin-by-charlie-lee/600&quot;&gt;litecointalk.io&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;(Y)ou may wonder why I’m pushing for SegWit. Litecoin does not have a block size problem. That’s right, and SegWit is not just a block scaling solution. I would even say block scaling is just a side benefit of SegWit. The main fix is transaction malleability, which would &lt;strong&gt;allow Lightning Networks (LN)&lt;/strong&gt; to be built on top of Litecoin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;(S)ome people say LN on Bitcoin will kill any reason to use Litecoin. If people can do instantaneous transactions on Bitcoin, why would they use Litecoin? My gut feel is that this is not the case. […] LN nodes will charge a fee for LN txns going through them and that fee will be relative to the Bitcoin network fee. So &lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin LN txns will be more expensive than Litecoin LN&lt;/strong&gt; txns. It may make economic sense for a LN txn to go via Litecoin and back to Bitcoin to get the cheapest rate. Lightning makes this possible because it allows the two LN to be &lt;strong&gt;interoperable&lt;/strong&gt;. I don’t know that this use case will be economical or not, but we won’t know until both LNs are built and running.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;segwit-activation-litecoin&quot;&gt;Segwit Activation Litecoin&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://segwit.co/ltc&quot;&gt;Follow segwit.co/ltc to see whether segwit was activated yet&lt;/a&gt;. It should be activated in mid May 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow the LTCBTC pair technicals on &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://tradingview.go2cloud.org/SHW9&quot;&gt;TradingView&lt;/a&gt; via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/chart/LTCBTC/cFRt8jgX-LTC-BTC-this-time-is-different-lol/&quot;&gt;this btc_joe’s idea from 23 February&lt;/a&gt; - it gets updated daily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow Charlie Lee on twitter &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SatoshiLite&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/SatoshiLite&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 11:20:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/litecoin-pump/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/litecoin-pump/</guid>
        
        <category>popular</category>
        
        
        <category>coins</category>
        
        <category>ltc</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
