<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Altcoin Trading</title>
    <description>Altcoin Trading is the forex of cryptocurrencies, with bitcoin as the base currency.</description>
    <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.altcointrading.net/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 17:34:21 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 17:34:21 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Opinion: Time in the market vs timing the market</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/editorial/likeaboss.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/editorial/likeaboss.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: In the long run, time in the market beats timing the market.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s take a quick look at the difference between trading and investing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When you trade&lt;/strong&gt; you don’t care which way the market goes as long as your position is making you money. All you need is to be right about the direction. For what it’s worth, even if you hold a shitcoin with absolutely no future and it pumps, you are making money - not that it wouldn’t resemble casino though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When you invest&lt;/strong&gt; you are looking for value and you put in money that you realistically won’t need even in a few years time. You go for value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;which-one-is-more-profitable&quot;&gt;Which one is more profitable?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They say that in the long run, time in the market beats timing the market. With the short term direction you cannot know for sure - even technical and fundamental analysis together with Reddit sentiment can only give you what’s likely, not what’s hundred percent sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Realistically you have higher chance to be wrong in timing the market than you have when carefully picking an asset which you think has a long term chance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Time in the market is so much more important for an investor’s long-term returns than timing the market. This is something The Motley Fool takes to heart, because no one can accurately know when to get in and get out.  […] “Generally that tends to be true. But, alas, there are no firm rules here, and context is king in pretty much all of this. For example, there are times where valuations get super lofty.”&lt;/em&gt; - via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fool.com/investing/2016/07/01/time-in-the-market-vs-timing-the-market.aspx&quot;&gt;The Motley Fool&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;hodlers-hate&quot;&gt;Hodlers Hate&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These days everyone hates the hodler cult in both BTC and ETH. The truth is though, as a hodler who is in a position for the long run, your biggest risk really is &lt;em&gt;losing your position&lt;/em&gt;. And the best way to lose it is to try and sell high to rebuy lower. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.altcointrading.net/litecoin-pump/#the-technicals&quot;&gt;In a bull market, the low won’t be so low.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, how should you look at an asset if you want to hold?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investors look at the following characteristics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1/ Real-World Adoption™ - That’s why &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.altcointrading.net/zoe-ethereum-alphabay/&quot;&gt;Ethereum on Alphabay&lt;/a&gt; is bigger a deal than &lt;a href=&quot;http://raiden.network/&quot;&gt;Raiden network&lt;/a&gt; or dapps even though both of the latter features are really cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2/ &lt;a href=&quot;https://etherscan.io/chart/tx/&quot;&gt;Transactions per day&lt;/a&gt; which is related to adoption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3/ &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinmarketcap.com/&quot;&gt;Exchange volume per day&lt;/a&gt; and (anti)correlation with bitcoin to see how much of the use is just speculation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course all cryptocurrency is still very young though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;an-unlikely-altcoin-fundamental&quot;&gt;An unlikely altcoin fundamental&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/editorial/fuck.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/editorial/fuck.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What would happen if Ethereum lost Vitalik? Something explicit for sure, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Go for a business that any idiot can run - because sooner or later, an idiot probably is going to run it.” - Peter Lynch&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe this is a drawback of Ethereum as an investment asset. That &lt;strong&gt;doesn’t mean ETH wasn’t an outstanding trading opportunity&lt;/strong&gt; just recently - but that’s precisely the difference between trading and investment. For the &lt;em&gt;long&lt;/em&gt; long term, it’s a question how sustainable this is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, compare it to other popular altcoins on the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sure there are people who believe &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Monero/comments/61atcg/what_i_believe_is_holding_back_our_adoption_and/&quot;&gt;certain coins&lt;/a&gt; are lead by idiots at present already, while other coins are &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/notgrubles/status/851878073909862400/photo/1&quot;&gt;quickly getting there&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You shouldn’t blame people for holding on to assets with slower development and moronic leads. After all &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lindy_effect&quot;&gt;the longer the assets are surviving this misfortune the more valuable they are for the long run&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 12:24:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/time-vs-timing/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/time-vs-timing/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
        <category>coins</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Litecoin: This time it's different?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/emotions/up.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/emotions/up.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Wait is this up or down?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-rock&quot;&gt;The Rock&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Arthur Hayes of BitMEX made his prognosis in the last issue of their newsletter - &lt;a href=&quot;http://us3.campaign-archive1.com/?u=db45c09bdf20e1866bb32123f&amp;amp;id=256c134334&quot;&gt;available here&lt;/a&gt;, scroll down to &lt;em&gt;The Rock Is In The Building&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Litecoin has acted like a rock in trader’s bags since it hit its all time high of $40 in 2013. The technical merits of why Litecoin should be worth more than $0 are few and far between. Litecoin exists on life support only because Chinese traders for some reason enjoy trading it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Litecoin is some form of legacy. A BTC spinoff dangerously close to bitcoin only with the advantage of faster transactions, it is easy to implement for an exchange that already does BTC. The reason most people who aren’t bagholders buy and sell litecoin is they are bitcoin traders and &lt;a href=&quot;/altcoin-exchanges/&quot;&gt;want to move USD from one exchange to the other&lt;/a&gt; whenever BTC is too volatile or too FUD-ridden to be safely in. By the way, that’s also what people sometimes use DOGE for but LTC is more widely supported. For one thing, it’s the only non-fiat and non-BTC way to get out of OkCoin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;first-class-and-second-class&quot;&gt;First class and second class&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over time this developed into a popular strategy: Altcoin traders might trade the first class altcoins - think &lt;a href=&quot;/coin/eth/&quot;&gt;Ethereum&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;/coin/xmr/&quot;&gt;Monero&lt;/a&gt;. Once they feel like the bull cycle is soon to be over they park the money in the second grade alts that remain more or less stable. With the money in the second class they wait for another opportunity in the first class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second class coins rarely dump without pumping first so it’s not a totally unreasonable idea, especially if you don’t pick the parking coin completely by random. Sometimes the second grade coins do pump which makes for a nice benefit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-reason&quot;&gt;The Reason™&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless it wouldn’t be a proper pump without people coming up with arbitrary rationalization of the surge. In the case of the Litecoin surge the rationalization says it’s network scaling implementation that is currently still argued about in BTC. This way LTC could be a flagship - if anything the market is letting everybody know that &lt;em&gt;little less conversation little more action please&lt;/em&gt; is what makes the community happy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/chart/LTCBTC/cFRt8jgX-LTC-BTC-this-time-is-different-lol/&quot;&gt;btc_joe’s TradingView idea&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In a world where bitcoin gets bigger and bigger (and thus less and less likely to make any &lt;strong&gt;consensus changes&lt;/strong&gt; whether it be a hard fork or segwit, etc), ask yourself, does litecoin deserve a place in the market? I certainly have my opinion.  Not to mention, if it gets the &lt;strong&gt;lightning network&lt;/strong&gt; before bitcoin…are you excited about this technology? I certainly am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indeed, this news came in a moment where the market was so to say available to be affected by the news.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Litecoin was in a downtrend for all of 2016. Technically the price (relatively to BTC) was closing towards a support back from pre-pump 2013 (see BTC-e Quandl data &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.quandl.com/data/BTCE/BTCLTC&quot;&gt;https://www.quandl.com/data/BTCE/BTCLTC&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/ltcbtc-quandl.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/ltcbtc-quandl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soon after that the BTC ETF and BU FUD took over which helped as well. On the April fool’s day someone started signaling segwit on the LTC network originally as a joke but lo and behold, traders took it quite seriously because the discussion was ongoing since February already, see &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@thecryptoconomy/the-barely-discussed-incredible-benefit-of-the-lightning-network-4ce82c75eb58&quot;&gt;this medium.com post&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;With the adoption of Segregated Witness and the announcements of support progressing quickly within the Litecoin network, we may first get to see the full benefits of this technology on one of the original altcoins. With a smaller market cap and some distance from contentious Bitcoin politics, Litecoin is able to take greater risks. It may get to be the first to see this incredible innovation in action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;laggards-beware&quot;&gt;Laggards beware&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/litecoin-coinbase.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/litecoin-coinbase.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: You see that squishy?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Litecoin &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/GDAX&quot;&gt;@GDAX&lt;/a&gt; vol is over $10M. &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/brian_armstrong&quot;&gt;@brian_armstrong&lt;/a&gt;, I think it&amp;#39;s time we let people easily buy LTC with fiat on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/coinbase&quot;&gt;@coinbase&lt;/a&gt;. What do you say? 😁&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Charlie Lee (@SatoshiLite) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SatoshiLite/status/849792340357029888&quot;&gt;6 April 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The prognosis of Arthur Hayes in his &lt;a href=&quot;http://us3.campaign-archive1.com/?u=db45c09bdf20e1866bb32123f&amp;amp;id=256c134334&quot;&gt;newsletter&lt;/a&gt; is that LTC is bound to go down since GDAX got the USD pair too when it showed such a pretty activity now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is likely that this is what’s going to happen: GDAX is the exchange removed far from the Poloniex altcoin trading epicenter. It’s where a newly listed altcoin might be bought by laggards who don’t really know much about its market but hope to still make a buck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They’ll be buying the coins sold by those who bought at Polo early enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-technicals&quot;&gt;The Technicals&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the cryptowatch snapshot above you’ll probably be able to tell the current action looks like &lt;em&gt;wave 4&lt;/em&gt;. The people who timed it right took their profits but there is still some buying by those who came a bit late. It should still make for one more up before crashing though, and how big the crash will be, nobody knows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/BTC-squishies.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/BTC-squishies.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After all, altcoins in general are in a bull market. As such, the end of the wave cycle shouldn’t be as dreary as it was in 2013. In a bull market, the end of the cycle could be a simple consolidation and after a few weeks there could be more of the movement up north - see the image from the BTCUSD market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this case one should look into fundamentals for clarity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And in the case of litecoin, this doesn’t end up on a positive note: no real adoption, not much innovation. For cryptogeeks it’s a legacy, it’ll stick around for some time no matter what, but in the real world litecoin as a name is nonexistent. That shouldn’t make for an exciting future…Unless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-lightning-network-plans&quot;&gt;The lightning network plans&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…Unless LN. The Lightning Network can bridge channels between different blockchains, possibly allowing users to use their LTC at places that accepts Bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charlie Lee via &lt;a href=&quot;https://litecointalk.io/t/my-vision-for-segwit-and-lightning-networks-on-litecoin-and-bitcoin-by-charlie-lee/600&quot;&gt;litecointalk.io&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;(Y)ou may wonder why I’m pushing for SegWit. Litecoin does not have a block size problem. That’s right, and SegWit is not just a block scaling solution. I would even say block scaling is just a side benefit of SegWit. The main fix is transaction malleability, which would &lt;strong&gt;allow Lightning Networks (LN)&lt;/strong&gt; to be built on top of Litecoin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;(S)ome people say LN on Bitcoin will kill any reason to use Litecoin. If people can do instantaneous transactions on Bitcoin, why would they use Litecoin? My gut feel is that this is not the case. […] LN nodes will charge a fee for LN txns going through them and that fee will be relative to the Bitcoin network fee. So &lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin LN txns will be more expensive than Litecoin LN&lt;/strong&gt; txns. It may make economic sense for a LN txn to go via Litecoin and back to Bitcoin to get the cheapest rate. Lightning makes this possible because it allows the two LN to be &lt;strong&gt;interoperable&lt;/strong&gt;. I don’t know that this use case will be economical or not, but we won’t know until both LNs are built and running.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow the LTCBTC pair technicals on &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://tradingview.go2cloud.org/SHW9&quot;&gt;TradingView&lt;/a&gt; via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/chart/LTCBTC/cFRt8jgX-LTC-BTC-this-time-is-different-lol/&quot;&gt;this btc_joe’s idea from 23 February&lt;/a&gt; - it gets updated daily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow Charlie Lee on twitter &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SatoshiLite&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/SatoshiLite&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 11:20:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/litecoin-pump/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/litecoin-pump/</guid>
        
        
        <category>coins</category>
        
        <category>ltc</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>About the proposed Ethereum ETF</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/emotions/document.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/emotions/document.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: The surveillance section of the rule change seems to be the key part after the rejection of Winklevoss COIN ETF. EtherIndex’s suggestion seems more plausible.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the SEC disapproved the rule change to allow listing of Bitcoin ETF on the 10th of March 2017 the majority opinion has been along the lines that other cryptocurrency ETFs most likely don’t have a chance because all cryptocurrency markets are unregulated. Nonetheless there is a nice twist in the rule change for ETH ETF - an idea that didn’t appear in the Bitcoin rule change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;etherindex---the-eth-exchange-traded-fund&quot;&gt;EtherIndex - The ETH Exchange Traded Fund&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The initial S-1 filling for the ETH fund appeared in July 2016 after the SEC opening a proposal for the COIN ETF for public comment and also right after a filing by SolidX to launch a Bitcoin ETF. Laura Shin of Forbes commented the “filing appears to be hastily put together”:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;EtherIndex itself was only founded a month ago, and its filing is mostly incomplete, acting more as a shell or placeholder. It does not name an exchange, ticker, trustee or administrator. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/laurashin/2016/07/18/as-race-to-offer-first-bitcoin-etf-heats-up-new-company-files-to-create-an-ether-etf/#2e9e14a47d76&quot;&gt;via forbes.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-s-1-filing&quot;&gt;The S-1 Filing&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a snippet from the filing itself. It introduces Ether by comparison to Bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;As filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission on &lt;strong&gt;July 15, 2016&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Ether is a digital asset (“Digital Asset”) &lt;strong&gt;similar to bitcoin&lt;/strong&gt; that is not issued by any government, bank or central organization. […] The Ethereum Network is a recent technological innovation, and the ether that is created, transferred, used and stored by entities and individuals have certain features associated with several types of assets, most notably commodities and currencies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The Trust’s Sponsor is EtherIndex LLC, a Delaware limited liability company formed on &lt;strong&gt;June 15, 2016&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1679791/000121390016015007/fs12016_etherindexether.htm#a_001&quot;&gt;via sec.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, further down in the text it clears up distinctions between Ether and Bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;While the bitcoin network permits users primarily to execute value transfers, the Ethereum Network allows users to program any arbitrary code and execute it, including value transfers. […] The Ethereum Network may be viewed as a &lt;strong&gt;global, decentralized computer&lt;/strong&gt; in comparison to the bitcoin network, which is more
similar to a global, decentralized &lt;strong&gt;payment network&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1679791/000121390016015007/fs12016_etherindexether.htm#a_001&quot;&gt;via sec.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The filing also explains that as Bitcoin is meant more like a store of value it has a cap on the amount of BTC that will be ever mined. It goes on to say that ETH has no such cap and more Ether will be created as needed, but the utility of Ether is primarily not a store of value or a payment system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The nonexistent cap has been controversial ans is also the reason why this &lt;a href=&quot;https://moneymorning.com/2016/07/20/bitcoin-etfs-can-work-but-this-ethereum-etf-wont/&quot;&gt;moneymorning.com&lt;/a&gt; article claims that an ETH ETF can never work - it is supposed to be a bad idea since ETH has no cap on the amount of Ether that will be created.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-rule-change&quot;&gt;The Rule Change&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rule change to allow listing of an ETF trading Ether shares was published in January 2017. The ETH ETF should be listed under NYSE Arca Equities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Release No. 34-79792; File No. SR-NYSEARCA-2016-176, January 13, 2017&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Pursuant to Section 19(b)(1)1 of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934 (the “Act”)2 and
Rule 19b-4 thereunder,3 notice is hereby given that, on December 30, 2016, NYSE Arca, Inc.
(the “Exchange” or “NYSE Arca”) filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission (the
“Commission”) the proposed rule change […] The Commission is publishing this notice to solicit comments
on the proposed rule change from interested persons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The Exchange proposes to list and trade shares of the following under &lt;strong&gt;NYSE Arca
Equities&lt;/strong&gt; Rule 8.201: EtherIndex Ether Trust (“Trust”).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the EtherIndex ETF, Coinbase is supposed to be the custodian and the pricing should be based on GDAX dollar price of ETH.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The
Exchange proposes to list and trade shares (“Shares”) of the Trust pursuant to NYSE Arca
Equities […] The sponsor of the Trust is EtherIndex LLC (“Sponsor”), a Delaware limited liability
company. Delaware Trust Company is the trustee of the Trust (“Trustee”). The Bank of New
York Mellon will be the administrator (“Administrator”) and custodian of cash of the Trust
(“Cash Custodian”). &lt;strong&gt;Coinbase will be the custodian of the ether of the Trust (“Ether
Custodian”)&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/rules/sro/nysearca/2017/34-79792.pdf&quot;&gt;via sec.gov (Release No. 34-79792; File No. SR-NYSEARCA-2016-176)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For one thing, the participation of Coinbase/GDAX itself seems to be a better idea compared to the Winklevoss Gemini - an exchange that doesn’t have much volume and was probably created only with the ETF in mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The interesting part comes with the Surveillance section of the ETH ETF rule change though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you didn’t care about the Bitcoin ETF much you might not know it but insufficient control over BTC markets (both spot and derivatives) was the most prominent critic the SEC mentioned in their order disapproving the COIN ETF.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Order disapproving rule change for COIN ETF&lt;/em&gt;: […] the Commission is disapproving this proposed rule change because it does not find the proposal to be consistent with Section 6(b)(5) of the Exchange Act,
which requires […] to prevent fraudulent and manipulative acts and practices […]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;[…] First, the
exchange must have &lt;strong&gt;surveillance-sharing agreements&lt;/strong&gt; with significant markets for trading the
underlying commodity or derivatives on that commodity. And second, those &lt;strong&gt;markets must be
regulated&lt;/strong&gt;. Based on the record before it, the Commission believes that the &lt;strong&gt;significant&lt;/strong&gt; markets for
&lt;strong&gt;bitcoin&lt;/strong&gt; are &lt;strong&gt;unregulated&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/rules/sro/batsbzx/2017/34-80206.pdf&quot;&gt;via sec.gov (Release No. 34-80206; File No. SR-BatsBZX-2016-30)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The SEC didn’t like the fact that majority of BTC trading occurs on exchanges out of their reach. Should a manipulation occur the SEC also wouldn’t be able to find out who’s causing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The surveillance-sharing agreement was a term that caught on quickly at Bitcoin trading forums. It quickly solidified into “the SEC wanted access to data about customers, exchanges didn’t want to provide it”. How did this surveillance-sharing agreement come about? It was the central point of the Bats rule change for COIN ETF:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bats rule change / Surveillance&lt;/em&gt;: The Exchange believes that its surveillance procedures are adequate to properly monitor
the trading of the Shares on the Exchange during all trading sessions and to deter and detect
violations of Exchange rules and the applicable federal securities laws. […] The Exchange may obtain information regarding trading in the Shares via the Intermarket Surveillance Group
(“ISG”), from other exchanges who are members or affiliates of the ISG, or with which the
Exchange has entered into a comprehensive surveillance sharing agreement. In addition, &lt;strong&gt;the
Exchange may obtain information&lt;/strong&gt; about bitcoin transactions, trades and market data &lt;strong&gt;from
Bitcoin Exchanges&lt;/strong&gt; with which the Exchange has entered into a &lt;strong&gt;comprehensive surveillance
sharing agreement&lt;/strong&gt; as well as certain additional information that is publicly available through the
Blockchain. The Exchange notes that &lt;strong&gt;it has entered&lt;/strong&gt; into a comprehensive surveillance sharing
agreement &lt;strong&gt;with Gemini Exchange&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/rules/sro/batsbzx/2016/34-78262.pdf&quot;&gt;via sec.gov (Release No. 34-78262; File No. SR-BatsBZX-2016-30)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Was it the Winkletwins’ idea that exchanges should agree to provide data so that there can be an ETF listed? There is no mention about surveillance-sharing agreement in the EtherIndex rule change. Instead, the exchange pleads to monitor the market and intervene in case there is an anomaly in the trading activity which could potentially be a manipulation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given enough data this sounds like a plausible way to detect manipulation while at the same time there is no agreement needed whatsoever: the market data are freely accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;NYSE rule change / Surveillance&lt;/em&gt;: The Exchange represents that trading in the Shares will be subject to the existing trading
surveillances administered by the Exchange, as well as cross-market surveillances administered
by the Financial Industry Regulatory Authority (“FINRA”) on behalf of the Exchange&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The surveillances referred to above generally focus on &lt;strong&gt;detecting securities trading outside
their normal patterns&lt;/strong&gt;, which could be indicative of &lt;strong&gt;manipulative&lt;/strong&gt; or other violative &lt;strong&gt;activity&lt;/strong&gt;.
When such situations are detected, surveillance analysis follows and investigations are opened,
where appropriate, to review the behavior of all relevant parties for all relevant trading
violations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/rules/sro/nysearca/2017/34-79792.pdf&quot;&gt;via sec.gov (Release No. 34-79792; File No. SR-NYSEARCA-2016-176)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rule change also states that price of Ether shares should be determined based on GDAX ETHUSD market but if the market will seem unhealthy, a Kraken pricing might be used. If Kraken is not available, it would be Gemini. If no big American exchange provides reasonable data, &lt;em&gt;the pricing of Ether shares can be set manually&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;[…] if the Sponsor determines that the Kraken Bitcoin Exchange and the Gemini
Exchange prices are not appropriate bases for evaluation of the Trust’s ether, &lt;strong&gt;the Sponsor’s&lt;/strong&gt; [EtherIndex LLC] &lt;strong&gt;good
faith estimate&lt;/strong&gt; of the market price of ether.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/rules/sro/nysearca/2017/34-79792.pdf&quot;&gt;via sec.gov (Release No. 34-79792; File No. SR-NYSEARCA-2016-176)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course one question is whether there was a reason the Winklevoss brothers opted for the tedious and probably next to impossible route of surveillance agreements - or whether simply nobody considered this way. In the recent days &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coindesk.com/winklevoss-bitcoin-etf-relaunch-analysts-chance/&quot;&gt;Bats filed a petition for the SEC to change their decision and list the COIN ETF after all&lt;/a&gt; but even now there has been no change made to the proposal. And another question is indeed what will the SEC actually say to the EtherIndex suggested solution for the surveillance and control problem. We’ll have to wait for that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last but not least, one thing that could surely help the ETH ETF is the majority of ETH/fiat trading occurs in the US. Only very small amount of ETH/fiat trading happens in China and Russia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; alt=&quot;Ethereum ETF&quot; src=&quot;/img/eth/eth-vol-by-country.png&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; data-original-width=&quot;578px&quot; data-original-height=&quot;638px&quot; width=&quot;578px&quot; height=&quot;638px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: An illustration, not a statistics! Volume distribution across countries for ETH/fiat pairs in the top 20 ETH markets. Single day data only, via coinmarketcap.com. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.altcointrading.net/img/eth/ETH-GEO.pdf&quot;&gt;View as PDF&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After all, from a legacy investor point of view it does not make such a fundamental difference whether to invest in Bitcoin or in Ether. The two currencies trade like competitors, very often they are inversely correlated, while both of them are equally uncorrelated with all of the legacy markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://www.slideshare.net/slideshow/embed_code/key/lTYUhBkIAJ5Q0Y&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 15:20:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/ethereum-etf/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/ethereum-etf/</guid>
        
        
        <category>coins</category>
        
        <category>eth</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to setup Monero core wallet (for dummies)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-cli-1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-cli-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Monero CLI wallet is the only reasonable and well tested option to store larger amount of XMR. A graphical wallet (GUI) is out too and working though. It’s probably safe but it is beta and it’s always safer to wait some time with new releases to get them tested.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you hold a sizable amount of Monero and &lt;a href=&quot;https://mymonero.com&quot;&gt;mymonero.com&lt;/a&gt; is not an option for security reasons (which it shouldn’t if you have a large stash) you’ll have to get the Monero’s core client.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That means downloading the full blockchain and creating a seed for your XMR wallet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The setup is not difficult, especially now that there is a GUI option for those who are not comfortable with command line clients. However, you should consider the size of the Monero blockchain: it is around 10 GB now so you’ll use a lot of data. And even though it’s not really a big issue for most people these days, the blockchain also grows so make sure you have enough space on your hard drive. &lt;a href=&quot;https://forum.getmonero.org/20/general-discussion/315/blockchain-size-forecast&quot;&gt;This thread&lt;/a&gt; on Monero forums says 57 GB blockchain by 2020 is a reasonable estimate so with some commonly retailed 1 TB external HDD you should be well beyond OK even for a very long term storage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to store a lot of XMR you should go for the CLI wallet. A &lt;a href=&quot;http://monero.stackexchange.com/questions/3237/is-the-gui-safe-for-storing-thousands-of-monero&quot;&gt;Stack Overflow thread here&lt;/a&gt; explains this code of good practice: The GUI wallet works with the same deamon as the CLI wallet, it is just a wrapper. The GUI shouldn’t be less secure than the CLI - but you just don’t know. The CLI client has been used since Monero’s inception, it is thoroughly tested by real users. The GUI wallet is new. Leave it some time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;monero-cli-wallet&quot;&gt;Monero CLI Wallet&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can download Monero Core for your OS &lt;a href=&quot;https://getmonero.org/downloads/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-cli-1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-cli-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a real human the only two scripts you’ll use are &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;monerod&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;monero-wallet-cli&lt;/code&gt;. In a console app (like iTerm on Mac) simply navigate into the extracted file you downloaded from the link above and run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;./monerod&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MoneroD means Monero deamon, it will start downloading the blockchain. This will take a few hours. You should see random gibberish of this kind until the blockchain is fully synced:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-cli-2.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-cli-2.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it’s done it’ll tell you SYNCHRONIZED OK. At this point you can generate the monero CLI wallet, run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;./monero-wallet-cli&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-cli-3.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-cli-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The client will ask for a name of the wallet and a password. It will generate your address and seed for you so copy the address and write the seed on paper. You should have the monero deamon running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, right now and until you &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;exit&lt;/code&gt; this process you are in the CLI wallet interface. You only need to know the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To check your balance, type &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;refresh&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To send Monero, type &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;transfer [address] [amount]&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To leave the CLI wallet, type &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;save&lt;/code&gt;, wait for response and then type &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;exit&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;monero-gui-wallet&quot;&gt;Monero GUI Wallet&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can download the beta release of Monero GUI wallet &lt;a href=&quot;https://getmonero.org/2016/12/22/monero-core-gui-beta-released.html&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-gui-1.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-gui-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-gui-2.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-gui-2.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Allowing an app from outside of the App Store in system preferences is as much challenge as you’ll be facing with the XMR GUI wallet&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The GUI is much easier to work with, especially if you have worked with BTC wallets like Electrum before. You simply download your distribution from the link above, extract the file and if you’re on Mac, move the app into Applications. Once you launch the GUI it guides you through the wallet creation and starts synchronizing the blockchain automatically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-gui-3.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-gui-3.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re just creating a new wallet go with the default localhost:18081 and write down your seed and password on paper. Your wallet files will be in home/Monero/wallets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-gui-4.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-gui-4.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a wallet at the ready you get into this view which is the actual GUI client. The wallet will start downloading the blockchain by itself. All you do from here is wait, and wait, and wait.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;further-reading&quot;&gt;Further reading&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://weuse.cash/monero/&quot;&gt;Learn more about Monero cryptocurrency&lt;/a&gt; - how it works&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.monero.how/&quot;&gt;Monero tutorials&lt;/a&gt; - how to create paper wallet for Monero cold storage and other useful things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 03:20:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/monero-wallet-dummies/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/monero-wallet-dummies/</guid>
        
        
        <category>wallets</category>
        
        <category>xmr</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cryptosignal - New tool for Ethereum traders</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/emotions/u-wot2.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/emotions/u-wot2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Yeah it’s a wonder&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;cryptosignal&quot;&gt;Cryptosign.al&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptosign.al&quot;&gt;https://cryptosign.al&lt;/a&gt; is a free tool that lets you correlate the dollar price of ETH with hash rate, difficulty or daily number of transactions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tool was published via r/bitcoinmarkets only a few hours ago. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/60php5/introducing_cryptosignal_directly_analyze_bitcoin/&quot;&gt;Here’s what&lt;/a&gt; the author himself has to say:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Hey BitcoinMarkets,
Cryptosign.al is a tool for finding patterns in the prices / data of the top cryptocurrencies (right now just BTC and ETH). It gives you the ability to directly overlay charts, use common technical indicators, and visualize statistics including linear and polynomial regression, and correlation. Right now, the data is updated daily but I’m looking to make the periods smaller in the near future.
I’m a data scientist by trade and have been working on this site casually for the last 6 months, it’s been a ton of fun and I hope you guys find it useful. Some upcoming features I was thinking of: hourly (or finer) periods and live updates, more data sources (signals) to analyze, more advanced modeling features.
I would really enjoy hearing some feedback and any ideas you guys have (e.g., the next feature you want to see the most).
Also worth mentioning that I’ve been a long time member on these and other crypto subreddits but I’m separating my work/play accounts. Thanks for all your contributions and I hope this website reciprocates that at least a little bit.
Edit: Some people may be receiving a startup page for Nginx. I’ll look into it, but PM if it’s still an issue in a day or two, thanks :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;is-eth-overpriced-now-at-40-usd&quot;&gt;Is ETH overpriced now at 40 USD?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far Cryptosignal is only available for BTCUSD and ETHUSD but if it gets popular it might change in the future. Specifically, people already suggested to add Google Trends volume (to track adoption and general interest) and of course more altcoins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is amazing to see it clearly how considering the hashrate ETH was undervalued for some time. The price matched the hashrate in the recent ETH surge:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/eth/cryptosignal.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/eth/cryptosignal.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the contrary, BTC looks undervalued at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nonetheless, the correlation between hash rate and price has been a controversial topic. The majority opinion seems to be that hash rate follows price, not the other way round.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consider &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/577awf/hashrate_vs_price/&quot;&gt;this thread from October 2016&lt;/a&gt;. OP suggests that (on the bitcoin market) the hash rate could act as a ceiling for potential price growth:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;BTC supply can be divided between existing bitcoins [where the supply (just for simplification) is very unelastic, because of hodling etc.] and freshly minted bitcoins [where the supply is very elastic, because miners are selling everything they mine for current price (again for simplification)].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;So with those assumptions, where the price is defined by near zero profit of miners, the price should be rising max at the pace of hashrate surge. But the trick is the max. It would happen only in a world without technological innovation. If miners get more effective tools, then the price will surge less than hashrate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;So if those thoughts are correct, I think much more hashrate has to be added to allow btc price to grow. For example from halving we see only 25% rise of hashrate, but much of it if not all is swallowed by the technological advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;So does bitcoin need surge in demand that will cause temporary high price that will be very attractive for miners and that will then cause the high hashrate and new equilibrium will come?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In short: should the hashrate follow the price or vice versa? Maybe there was some article about that, I would be happy to read it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To a comment that says hash rate and price are not correlated like this, OP responds with an explanation that the correlation for BTCUSD was bad when BTC was in it’s infancy but as the market matures the correlation improves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;They were not related in the past, because it was a wild west. The approx 2 years 1/2013-1/2015 were anomal in many ways (price overshooted). But during the last year the correlation is near perfect for example. Now the situation must consolidate for next few halvings. After them, who knows how the price will be determined. Maybe another factor steps in by then - the fees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://bitcoin.stackexchange.com/questions/3171/relation-between-network-hash-rate-bitcoin-value&quot;&gt;This Stack Overflow thread&lt;/a&gt; back from 2012 claims the hash rate to be rather a lagging indicator but on the individual level, if hash rate grows it means that more people decided to mine the coin. If they decided so for profit it indicates they expect the coin they mine will increase in value over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That would go well together with the idea that in some cases if price lags behind growing hash rate it could mean bullish sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptosign.al&quot;&gt;Go to Cryptosignal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 04:20:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-traders-tool/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-traders-tool/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
        <category>eth</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alphabay to adopt ETH for payments ahead of new privacy features</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/emotions/bridge.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/emotions/bridge.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: In the months to come ETH should get payments privacy enhancements which could mean a big change in fundamentals.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today Alphabay posted an announcement on their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/AlphaBayMarket/comments/60355i/alphabay_will_add_etherum_to_its_payment_options/&quot;&gt;subreddit&lt;/a&gt; stating that they are implementing ETH for payments. The implementation should be operational by May 1st 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Following the popularity of the new altcoin Ethereum and the recent price
hike showing a growing interest, Alphabay has made the decision to start
accepting Ethereum for marketplace listing purchases.

We are currently laying out the framework to make ETH acceptance possible,
and we will enable Ethereum deposits and withdrawals starting May 1st, 2017.
Vendors wishing to accept Ethereum can edit their listings and set the &quot;Accept
ETH&quot; to &quot;On&quot; in order to be able to be paid in Ethereum.

We have plenty of new stuff in the works, so expect more updates in the near
future.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was some &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/603xpa/alphabay_market_adding_ethereum_for_payments/df39uks/&quot;&gt;backlash against this news&lt;/a&gt; since ETH is not currently meant as a cash-like payment system and transactions are easily traceable, as opposed to Monero transactions. However, in the months to come ETH should start support zkSNARKs which would put the transaction privacy on the level with ZCASH.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The abbreviation zk-SNARK means “zero knowledge succinct argument of knowledge”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://www.slideshare.net/slideshow/embed_code/key/ZPGDobtOhYwC2&quot;&gt;
  &lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;//www.slideshare.net/FengRenTsai1/zksnarks-in-ethereum-and-baby-zoe&quot; title=&quot;zkSNARKs in Ethereum, and Baby ZoE&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;zkSNARKs in Ethereum, and Baby ZoE&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; von &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;//www.slideshare.net/FengRenTsai1&quot;&gt;Feng-Ren Tsai&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These days an ETH transaction gets confirmed within seconds which is a relief for everyone coming in from the BTC blockchain. However, ETH doesn’t have any magical scaling solution - under Bitcoin’s occasional network load the Ethereum blockchain wouldn’t perform much better. Nevertheless this is not an issue ETH should be facing in the months to come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/wallets/jaxx.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/wallets/jaxx.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding the privacy enhancements to ETH would give it a significant advantage: ETH would become a private coin that is being actively developed, is easily available on most exchanges and can be stored comfortably in both light clients (&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://jaxx.io/&quot;&gt;Jaxx&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.exodus.io/&quot;&gt;Exodus&lt;/a&gt;) and cold storage (&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://shop.trezor.io/?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;Trezor&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ledgerwallet.com/r/e274&quot;&gt;Ledger&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile Monero holders still need to resort to downloading the full blockchain if they want to store the altcoin on their computer and DASH seems to be rebranding and refocusing away from “the private coin” image to “the easy payment system” image in spite of its lack of merchant adoption. Not to mention Bitcoin - the oldest cryptocurrency is currently amidst the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/view/articles/2017-03-16/someone-wants-to-stick-a-fork-in-bitcoin&quot;&gt;FUD over potential network split&lt;/a&gt;. The market is taking a dive even though the news is probably exaggerated since it is not clear whether the fork will indeed happen at all in the first place, let alone any time soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nonetheless ETH could potentialy profit greatly from this situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.ethereum.org/2017/01/19/update-integrating-zcash-ethereum/&quot;&gt;Read the update on ZCASH integration on the Ethereum blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 17:20:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/zoe-ethereum-alphabay/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/zoe-ethereum-alphabay/</guid>
        
        <category>popular</category>
        
        
        <category>coins</category>
        
        <category>eth</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Monero Cold Storage: Current Situation</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/emotions/crowd.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/emotions/crowd.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: The crowd wants it but there won’t be an easy-to-use Monero cold storage any time soon even though this single product could make a new leader in the field of hardware wallets.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not so long ago there were rumors about various wallet providers finally integrating Monero - desktop wallets, light clients, hardware wallets. Turns out we got all of this for DASH, also for ETH, in some cases for ZEC, DAO, REP…Not for XMR though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Monero’s long-term holder base increased, price has been consolidating at a nice level after the surge by the end of summer 2016 and everyone who ever heard of altcoin trading is eager to jump after the first viable product that will provide a safe storage for Monero.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It got to the point that such a feature would shake up the market of hardware wallet providers - even if it were a standalone Monero-only wallet, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Monero/comments/5lf9ns/is_there_any_update_on_monero_support_for_the/&quot;&gt;people would buy it&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s an obvious opportunity, so what is the problem?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;mailchimpfix&quot;&gt; &lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;400px&quot; height=&quot;300px&quot; layout=&quot;fixed&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://amp2disqus.netlify.com/altcointrading/signup.html&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is a technical one. There is a lot of open sourced code to handle Bitcoin and today’s most popular altcoins all use some of Bitcoin’s basics. DASH is the obvious example but even ETH was in fact built up on a Bitcoin fork. That means, for most altcoins you could pick, you would always just tweak a BTC block explorer and use it, or you would fork a BTC light wallet and so on - it makes the process a whole lot easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is, you can do this with most altcoins other than Monero. Monero was built from scratch and none of the BTC codebase can be reused. The whole system has to be developed again, specifically for Monero.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apparently this will be a chance for someone new to enter the market because the winners of today don’t have enough people (nor pressing need for the profit and glory) to be bothered with Monero.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;ledger-nano---no-eta&quot;&gt;Ledger Nano - ,,No ETA”&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-ledger.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/xmr/monero-ledger.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://trello.com/c/wsK0myEm/52-monero-support&quot;&gt;public Trello board&lt;/a&gt; regarding the Monero support and for a time it looked quite promising. However, u/btchip from Ledger cleared it up:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It’s not yet started - a few other things to work on first. We have no ETA but have the right communication channels open to move quickly once we go. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Monero/comments/5lf9ns/is_there_any_update_on_monero_support_for_the/dbvmfo0/&quot;&gt;via r/ledgerwallet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;trezor---project-stalled&quot;&gt;Trezor - Project Stalled&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://shop.trezor.io?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt; &lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/wallets/trezor-altcoins-long.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; data-original-width=&quot;728px&quot; data-original-height=&quot;90px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot;&gt; &lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trezor by SatoshiLabs was supposed to get Monero supported by their hardware wallet, &lt;a href=&quot;https://altcointrading.net/monero-wallet/&quot;&gt;someone worked on the project before&lt;/a&gt; and there are a few brave ones who hacked up their Trezors to get a working hardware wallet for Monero punk-style. Working for now, that is. The code written for Trezor will be incompatible soon as Monero upgraded since that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;keepkey---erm-not-really&quot;&gt;Keepkey - ,,Erm, not really.”&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Trezor spin-off is not planning to implement Monero either:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We are considering it, but it is not on the roadmap at the moment. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/keepkey/comments/5m58vv/monero_support/dc1fkzx/&quot;&gt; via r/keepkey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;jaxx---near-term-plans-halted&quot;&gt;Jaxx - ,,Near term plans halted”&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/wallets/jaxx.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/wallets/jaxx.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en-gb&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Saddens me to announce we&amp;#39;ve halted &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/jaxx_io&quot;&gt;@jaxx_io&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/monerocurrency&quot;&gt;@monerocurrency&lt;/a&gt; near term integration plans. Too many difficulties. Need to refocus resources.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Anthony Di Iorio (@diiorioanthony) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/diiorioanthony/status/826953622088982528&quot;&gt;2 February 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jaxx was the most promising Monero integration, hands down. In &lt;a href=&quot;http://decentral.ca/jaxx-monero-integration-update/&quot;&gt;November 2016&lt;/a&gt; Jaxx people asked the Monero team for help - fluffypony &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Monero/comments/5dsqrf/jaxx_monero_integration_update_3/da73yrj&quot;&gt;provided source code for both backend and frontend&lt;/a&gt; and whenever Jaxx developers were clueless with something they could ask. The discussion was even public on Reddit at first, before trolls chased the devs away to private channels. Since then amount of news diminished.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fast-forward to February 2017, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&quot;something something no Monero for Jaxx&quot;&lt;/code&gt;. It seems like there was some tension between the Jaxx team and fluffypony - apparently fluffy’s changes in XMR codebase rendered some of the Jaxx’s new code useless again so the management decided to ditch it for now and focus on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/diiorioanthony/status/842000749106237441&quot;&gt;currently ongoing major Jaxx upgrade&lt;/a&gt;, although &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Monero/comments/5rjll8/looks_like_monero_wont_be_in_jaxx_for_a_while/dd7yfo6/&quot;&gt;fluffypony was more sarcastic than that&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;whos-still-working-on-that&quot;&gt;Who’s still working on that?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chances are it’s going to be fashionable to start claiming work on XMR support to get people buy your product in expectations of future joy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nonetheless, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.exodus.io/&quot;&gt;Exodus, the desktop multicoin wallet with Shapeshift integration&lt;/a&gt; seems to have Monero support as top priority for new features.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Likewise the official web client mymonero.com should get a mobile interface later this year. Mymonero.com is a fully functional thing by now, the obvious idea would be to use what is there now as a webview to create the most basic online-only app. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Monero/comments/5tfz27/why_not_use_opensourced_mymonero_fronend_as_quick/&quot;&gt;And some have indeed succeeded with that&lt;/a&gt;, so hopefully this is expectation is a realistic one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 class=&quot;post comment&quot; id=&quot;disqus_embed&quot;&gt;Comment on &quot;Monero Cold Storage: Current Situation&quot;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;600px&quot; height=&quot;400px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://amp2disqus.netlify.com/altcointrading/#monero&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 01:20:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/monero-cold-storage-2017/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/monero-cold-storage-2017/</guid>
        
        
        <category>wallets</category>
        
        <category>xmr</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bitcoin ETF rejected, Ethereum ETF is probably off the table too</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/emotions/sadness.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/emotions/sadness.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Cryptocurrencies are not going to be part of the mainstream finance for now.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today just after 4PM Eastern time the SEC finally dropped the long postponed decision regarding the proposed COIN ETF, the first Bitcoin exchange traded fund.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The SEC cites lack of regulations and the fact that BTC markets can be manipulated as the main reasons for rejection of the rule change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;[…] the Commission is disapproving this proposed rule change because it does not find the proposal to be consistent with Section 6(b)(5) of the Exchange Act, which requires, among other things, that the rules of a national securities exchange be &lt;strong&gt;designed to prevent fraudulent and manipulative acts&lt;/strong&gt; and practices and to protect investors and the public interest. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/rules/sro/batsbzx/2017/34-80206.pdf&quot;&gt;Full SEC announcement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though there is another BTC ETF proposal lined up for the 30th of March and Ethereum has a proposal for listing, it seems that any cryptocurrency exchange traded fund is off the table for now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/etherindex-registers-sec-issue-ether-shares/&quot;&gt;EtherIndex, the ETH ETF proposal - 19/07/2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ETC product (created by Barry Silbert’s Grayscale) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2017-03-09/bitcoin-trust-s-silbert-to-launch-classic-ether-fund-this-month&quot;&gt;is supposed to launch this month though&lt;/a&gt;, even though it will probably start trading over-the-counter first. It is modeled after the Bitcoin Investment Trust (GBTC) which is also a &lt;a href=&quot;https://grayscale.co/bitcoin-investment-trust/&quot;&gt;Grayscale product&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Eventually, just like Bitcoin Investment Trust, it may start trading over the counter, Silbert said in an interview. The bitcoin trust, started in 2013, is currently waiting for approval to list on the NYSE Arca market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Classic ether’s development and rules governing the nets; recently, developers announced there will be no more than 230 million classic ether tokens issued – a decision that makes the digital currency a scarce resource, just like bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short, it is not going to get any easier for legacy investors to trade cryptocurrency in the months to come, but that’s about it. Cryptocurrencies are for now just cryptocurrencies, the niche speculative bet on the future. That’s not quite a reason to panic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;They have two mutually exclusive, and self destructive ideals.
Pursue valuation from regulated sources.
Or undermine those sources they pursue.
These Ideas can’t exist on the same chain, there isn’t some quantum solution. They need to fork to meet both, or continue in purgatory. meanwhile, Ethereum will just find implementation and application as a tool. It really is oil vs gold. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/5yoqdr/denied/&quot;&gt;via /r/ethtrader&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/ethereum-etf-unlikely/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/ethereum-etf-unlikely/</guid>
        
        
        <category>coins</category>
        
        <category>eth</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Avoidance Strategy in Altcoin Trading</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/emotions/standby.JPG&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/emotions/standby.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Altcoin trading strategy: Wyckoffian avoidance?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wyckoff method is getting popular in the cryptocurrency space mainly because John Bollinger the author of bbands keeps recommending it on twitter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While it can be called a “legacy” thing no doubt it is useful for crypto as well:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en-gb&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/kenzboard&quot;&gt;@kenzboard&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MrJozza&quot;&gt;@MrJozza&lt;/a&gt; Yeah, Wyckoff is as near to a universal key to understanding trading as we have.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; John Bollinger (@bbands) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/bbands/status/835170564431962112&quot;&gt;24 February 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-value-trading&quot;&gt;The value trading&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Wyckoff style is to trade only the best stocks in the leading sectors. Can you use this motto when trading cryptocurrencies? It is an emerging asset class but figuring out which cryptocurrency has actual &lt;strong&gt;value&lt;/strong&gt; will make your decisions a lot clearer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You want to buy/hold a &lt;em&gt;valuable&lt;/em&gt; asset through shorter timespans when the &lt;em&gt;price&lt;/em&gt; is not reflecting the value (yet).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You want to take profits and abandon an asset that is appreciating in the short term because of things like tiny market hence manipulation, or media hype.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;altcoin-trading-strategy-how-strong-a-coin-is&quot;&gt;Altcoin Trading Strategy: How strong a coin is&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The Wyckoffian mission is to trade and invest in the best stocks in the leading Industry Groups. We have been studying examples of leadership characteristics using &lt;strong&gt;Wyckoff Analysis&lt;/strong&gt; in combination with &lt;strong&gt;Relative Strength&lt;/strong&gt;. […] Always seeking the strongest stocks in the strongest groups. It is also a worthwhile exercise to study groups that are stalling and falling from favor. &lt;a href=&quot;http://stockcharts.com/articles/wyckoff/2017/02/avoidance-strategy.html&quot;&gt;StockCharts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key point is that a leader of a group dies not remain a leader indefinitely. At some point the leader leaves the limelight, becomes a laggard and may stay a laggard for some time. That’s what the Wyckoff avoidance strategy is about - spotting the transition from leader to laggard and avoiding longing that market rather than getting to think in forever terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This transition is a substantial change, technically you should be looking for it on longer timeframes (daily, 3D or weekly charts).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;select-assets-that-are-in-harmony-with-the-market&quot;&gt;Select assets that are in harmony with the market&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In a &lt;strong&gt;bull (uptrend) market&lt;/strong&gt;, select [assets] that are &lt;strong&gt;stronger than the market itself&lt;/strong&gt;. In a bear market choose those that are weaker than the market itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you figure out consistently strong cryptocurrencies and their counterparts you have your best candidates for mid-term longs and shorts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Strong altcoins rally quite easily but after the rally retraces some of the gains remain.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Weak altcoins are traded but don’t rally consistently. If they do, the retrace kills all the gains.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;mailchimpfix&quot;&gt; &lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;400px&quot; height=&quot;300px&quot; layout=&quot;fixed&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://amp2disqus.netlify.com/altcointrading/signup.html&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In legacy markets one can compare stocks against a composite index. In a bull market well below a known resistance line, if a stock gains more than the index, it’s typically a good bet to open a long, avoding all the rest of the assets in the group. If the resistance approaches it’s time to close that long and find which stock was performing poorly in the rally. That is going to be to one most likely to drop significantly, you can short it and avoid trading the strong performers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In cryptocurrencies we don’t have an index that would track the performance of top 100 or 500 altcoins. You will have to put in a little bit more work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A handy tool that will help you do that is &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinmarketcap.com/&quot;&gt;coinmarketcap.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can track the historical weekly performance of cryptocurrencies at &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinmarketcap.com/historical/&quot;&gt;http://coinmarketcap.com/historical/&lt;/a&gt; - this page has snapshots dating back to 2013.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daily data is available at &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinmarketcap.com/#BTC&quot;&gt;the homepage&lt;/a&gt; or from their API. If you are trading altcoins against BTC, that is pairs like ETHBTC, you should switch to BTC pricing. This way you’ll see which altcoins perform the best and the worst against bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/cmc-snapshot.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/cmc-snapshot.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Going through the weekly data from 2016 you can filter each table by traded volume.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You’ll see that small altcoins show up every week with immense gains but after some weeks you don’t hear about them again.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;On the other hand, for instance litecoin is consistently being traded but the price doesn’t change much - perhaps people use it to move funds across exchanges instead of using fiat but next to no people believe it is worth to hold LTC.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ethereum and Dash have volumes in the upper part of the spectrum but they actually see a rally or two once in a while with gains that don’t completely disappear after the retrace.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;going-back-to-individual-coins&quot;&gt;Going back to individual coins&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To spot the beginning of short term changes in the market, topping patterns and reversals you will have to go back to individual cryptocurrencies. The chart below is a bitcoin chart but the same TA is valid with all commonly traded coins with good holder base these days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What people use the most to spot these changes is Parabolic SAR, RSI and MACD. You can use &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://cryptowat.ch&quot;&gt;Cryptowatch&lt;/a&gt; for the basics or &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://tradingview.go2cloud.org/SHW9&quot;&gt;TradingView&lt;/a&gt; which provides interface where you can tune the indicator parameters and do some very basic backtesting. To name one, the default Parabolic SAR will be too sensitive, giving you flips that will be a false positive so you should pick your timeframe and tune the PSAR settings so that it flips really mostly only before a reversal historically happened on that timeframe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hourly bitcoin chart below shows a SAR set to &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;0.025, 0.02, 0.03&lt;/code&gt; on &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://tradingview.go2cloud.org/SHW9&quot;&gt;TradingView&lt;/a&gt;. If you click on the picture to zoom it you’ll see it flipping, and if you look at the RSI at the bottom you’ll see a divergence between the RSI lows and the price lows, which is bullish as it shows the lows are too low for the strength of the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/btc-rsidiv.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/btc-rsidiv.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course in both bitcoin and altcoins you cannot discount “conspiracy theories” about whales manipulating the markets - given the (little) money one needs to do that it’s entirely possible. Even the legacy guys found it out themselves, I encourage you to read the following excerpt from FT where an investor whines about getting rekt on OkCoin because of a bearwhale, it’s hilarious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;this is from ft, somehow archive.is works around their log in wall: http://archive.is/aQ7Om&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Daniel Masters, the founder of one of the world’s first bitcoin funds – Jersey-based Global Advisors Bitcoin Investment Program (GABI) – is calling for position limits on bitcoin exchanges, after falling prey to a heinous case of cash-to-futures basis manipulation in February, when bitcoin soared to new record high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Our position was liquidated at $767 and, needless to say, by the time we were back in the market the price was shooting back above $900. This was of course an extremely unfortunate state of affairs in which to find ourselves and a hard lesson learned. Accordingly, we lost around 10% of performance against our benchmark, the USD price of bitcoin. The matters set out above highlighted another issue with bitcoin trading, which up until this point we had not considered. After the price drop, one player emerged as totally dominant in the open interest of the futures contract. It seemed pretty clear to us as a result that this event was not just a normal version of a large liquidation, with which we are familiar, but was a premeditated attack. When the dust settled, one unidentified player was short well over half the open interest. We would therefore class this episode as clear market manipulation, and in fact it was not just momentary: for many days thereafter the basis was so weak that it seemed that the one attack was being followed up by periodic smaller attacks. As such we approached the exchange. They confirmed to us that there were no position limits whatsoever and that people were free to do whatever they wanted in their “happy trading environment” (yes, they used those actual words). We made it very clear that such activity, whether in a regulated environment or not, might amount to criminality in Hong Kong and would certainly do so in many other jurisdictions. Following a number of discussions, the exchange encouraged the ‘rogue’ player to withdraw and things have now normalized.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“happy trading environment” from hong kong…that’s okcasino amirite &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/5y5qzz/daily_discussion_wednesday_march_08_2017/deo070z/&quot;&gt;via r/bitcoinmarkets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the next days I’ll be looking over altcoins historical performance so stay tuned for next posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reading&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://technical.traders.com/tradersonline/display.asp?art=167&quot;&gt;http://technical.traders.com/tradersonline/display.asp?art=167&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://stockcharts.com/articles/wyckoff/&quot;&gt;https://stockcharts.com/articles/wyckoff/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/wyckoff-avoidance/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/wyckoff-avoidance/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>TradingView users on DASH: March 7th 2017</title>
        <description>&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot; src=&quot;https://s3.amazonaws.com/tradingview/tv.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/coins/dash.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/coins/dash.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: What do traders think of the recent DASH price action?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the time of writing the DASHBTC trades at about 0.038 while about a week ago it topped close below 0.05 on Poloniex. What do traders think the outlooks are?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;long-term-optimism-for-all-of-2017-by-lowstrife&quot;&gt;Long term optimism for all of 2017 by lowstrife&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;!-- TradingView Chart BEGIN --&gt;
&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;
var tradingview_embed_options = {};
tradingview_embed_options.width = '750';
tradingview_embed_options.height = '385';
tradingview_embed_options.chart = 'B0AH2eWl';
new TradingView.chart(tradingview_embed_options);
&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/chart/DASHBTC/B0AH2eWl-DASH-still-has-promising-outlook-coming-in-2017/&quot;&gt;DASH still has promising outlook coming in 2017&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/u/lowstrife/&quot;&gt;lowstrife&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;http://tradingview.go2cloud.org/SHW9&quot;&gt;TradingView.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- TradingView Chart END --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tradingview cryptocurrency chat mod lowstrife posted his chart in January 2017 when DASH was showing something that looked like long term accumilation before a jump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is extremely promising market structure for DASH, very well defined highs that have been hit multiple times. I could see a serious run attempt at 0.1 in the coming months if it continues to provide. I’m a bit late on my timing, I would have liked to publish this chart around 0.0012, but as long as it continues to make higher lows on the high timeframes it should be setup for a very nice run. 3 years of consolidation bewteen 0.005 and 0.03, the trend is sideways but with an upward bias.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the beginning of March DASH peaked around 0.048 BTC and started wicking hard which was pronounced the end of the bull run:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/x/Hc2N2FE0/&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/x/Hc2N2FE0/&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wow, gigantic wicks and margin calls. Close everything, this is the top.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are now ripe for another consolidation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;dash-will-come-back-to-reality-by-bagofxmr&quot;&gt;DASH will come back to reality by bagofXMR&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;!-- TradingView Chart BEGIN --&gt;
&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;
var tradingview_embed_options = {};
tradingview_embed_options.width = '750';
tradingview_embed_options.height = '385';
tradingview_embed_options.chart = 'ijMvaxAY';
new TradingView.chart(tradingview_embed_options);
&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/chart/DASHBTC/ijMvaxAY-DASH-WILL-COME-BACK-TO-REALITY/&quot;&gt;DASH WILL COME BACK TO REALITY&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/u/bagofXMR/&quot;&gt;bagofXMR&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;http://tradingview.go2cloud.org/SHW9&quot;&gt;TradingView.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- TradingView Chart END --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a short position from the top based on RSI (overbought and declining) and MACD “bad squishy”. However, the prediction was more bearish than the reality, DASH seems to be consolidating sideways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;short-term-bearish-rising-wedge-by-mateuszgrzelak&quot;&gt;Short term bearish rising wedge by MateuszGrzelak&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;!-- TradingView Chart BEGIN --&gt;
&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;
var tradingview_embed_options = {};
tradingview_embed_options.width = '750';
tradingview_embed_options.height = '380';
tradingview_embed_options.chart = 'YPhmb4oO';
new TradingView.chart(tradingview_embed_options);
&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/chart/DASHBTC/YPhmb4oO-DASH-BTC-on-POLONIEX/&quot;&gt;DASH BTC on POLONIEX&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/u/MateuszGrzelak/&quot;&gt;MateuszGrzelak&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;http://tradingview.go2cloud.org/SHW9&quot;&gt;TradingView.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- TradingView Chart END --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this is an hourly chart showing the current sideways action where you might be scalping it quite easily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can trade DASH on &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://poloniex.com&quot;&gt;Poloniex&lt;/a&gt; with fees of .15%/.25% and newly also on &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.bitfinex.com/?refcode=5egV78YtlC&quot;&gt;Bitfinex - sign up with this link to get the generous fees of .09%/.18%&lt;/a&gt;. All altcoin charts and indicators are &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://tradingview.go2cloud.org/SHW9&quot;&gt;available on TradingView&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt; &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://shop.trezor.io?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt; &lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/wallets/trezor-altcoins-long.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; data-original-width=&quot;728px&quot; data-original-height=&quot;90px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot;&gt; &lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/dash-03-2017/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/dash-03-2017/</guid>
        
        
        <category>dash</category>
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
