<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Altcoin Trading</title>
    <description>Altcoin Trading is the forex of cryptocurrencies, with bitcoin as the base currency.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 12:55:11 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 12:55:11 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.4.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tezos fundraiser scheduled 1 July</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Tezos Foundation just sent out an email detailing the eagerly awaited ICO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://image.prntscr.com/image/XujkhUErQmCyI-hpq7qM2A.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;text-of-the-email&quot;&gt;Text of the email:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tezos Fundraiser scheduled for July 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is a message from the Tezos foundation.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Tezos Foundation is pleased to announce that the legal structure of the Tezos Foundation, its fundraiser, and related contracts have been approved by the Swiss Foundation Supervisory Authority.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this regulatory stamp of approval, we are now excited to announce the official start of the &lt;strong&gt;Tezos fundraiser on Saturday, July 1, 2017 at 6 am UTC&lt;/strong&gt;. We chose this date to give everyone enough time to complete their funding arrangements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe it’s important to do things right and protect our contributors and users from risk, which is why we went beyond current industry practice and waited to receive official approval before accepting contributions. We expect this high level of care to serve our technology, our community, and the world as we continue to build and grow this essential infrastructure for a free and prosperous society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For technical information on how to participate in the Tezos fundraiser, please always refer exclusively to the Tezos website at https://tezos.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contributions will open at https://tezos.com on July 1 at 6 am UTC&lt;/strong&gt;. In addition, we have approved our broker, &lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin Suisse&lt;/strong&gt;, to offer its customers participation in the Tezos fundraiser for a fee. Note that only Bitcoin Suisse and no other service has been approved to do so, and that using such a service requires you to trust the service provider with your private keys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to contribute, only do so through our own website https://tezos.com once the fundraiser opens, or through &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bitcoinsuisse.ch/tezos&quot;&gt;https://www.bitcoinsuisse.ch/tezos&lt;/a&gt; starting today&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No other websites are authorized to provide information on Tezos or accept contributions to the Tezos fundraiser.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To stay updated with developments, sign up for the mailing list at https://tezos.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Tezos Foundation is extremely pleased with the fantastic community that is starting to sprout around the Tezos project. The interest in the Tezos fundraiser has been electrifying. It is an amazing vote of confidence in decentralized governance and in the world class team developing the project. That interest has been matched by engineering development resulting in a testnet that has been operating for several months already and a production version that is expected to ship later this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Many thanks&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Johann, Guido, Diego, and the Tezos Foundation team&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: If you intend to participate through Bitcoin Suisse rather than directly through https://tezos.com, bear in mind that funding arrangements can take longer than expected - in some cases, two weeks or longer. So if you want to ensure your participation, you should start the process immediately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-fees-and-all&quot;&gt;The fees and all&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some information about the Bitcoin Suisse way: There is a fee of 100 CHF (cca 100USD) and 1.25% fee on the money you want to contribute. You have to AML/KYC with your ID, selfie with ID and proof of address. They say they are getting a lot of requests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To look at the numbers, if you want to send them 10K in bitcoins, your fee will be about 225 USD. You can also send them Ether or several kinds of fiat but in that case expect more haircut as the ICO is on BTC blockchain and all contributions will be changed into bitcoins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you get for this fee in pre-sale is that you are guaranteed to be put in the blocks that get a bonus:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Tezos ICO is capped by transactions that will make it in between the first 2000 blocks after opening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;BTC Block # Bonus   XTZ/BTC
0-399       20%     6’000
400-799     15%     5’750
800-1’199   10%     5’500
1’200-1’599 5%      5’250
1’600-1’999 0%      5’000
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So for one bitcoin invested you are kind-of guaranteed to receive at least 5250 tezzies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is not clear how they are planning to do it, overpaying the fees on bundled transactions or what, to get the transactions confirmed, but that is the phrasing of it in the agreement:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Contributors who have signed up with and participate through Bitcoin Suisse AG, and who have completed their onboarding and funding at least 4 hours prior to the applicable rounds, is guaranteed participation in the “bonus” phase of the respective rounds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;N.B: In case of force majeure, no guarantees regarding allocation or pricing of tokens are applicable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;N.B: Exact conditions regarding the crowd sale may be subject to change from the side of TZ and founders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Force majeure means ‘unforeseeable circumstances that prevent someone from fulfilling a contract’. That’s a normal condition to have in a contract but at the same time there is always a lot of unforeseeable circumstances in crypto.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 10:12:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/tezos</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/tezos</guid>
        
        <category>popular</category>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ledger CTO says Monero viable</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Everyone who managed to buy the blip to $16 on Bitfinex XMRUSD the other day, good on you! It’s time for Monero to rise from the ashes and lure back in all the butthurt ex-holders who got fluffyponied.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://reddit.com/u/btchip&quot;&gt;CTO of Ledger&lt;/a&gt; says the team determined Monero integration is viable after all. Next step is providing the estimated time to delivery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ledgerwallet/comments/6hdo1r/does_ledger_nano_s_support_monero_xmr_yet/&quot;&gt;Thread on reddit&lt;/a&gt; from just two hours ago&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;u/btchip: &lt;em&gt;From our current evaluation we’re convinced it’s doable. Next step will be to provide an ETA.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 06:36:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/ledger-monero</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/ledger-monero</guid>
        
        
        <category>xmr</category>
        
        <category>wallets</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Important - Jaxx Vulnerability</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vxlabs.com/2017/06/10/extracting-the-jaxx-12-word-wallet-backup-phrase/&quot;&gt;vxlabs.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even when your Jaxx has a security PIN configured, anyone with 20 seconds of (network) access to your PC can extract your 12 word backup phrase and copy it down. Jaxx does not have to be running for this to happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the 12 word backup phrase, they can later restore your wallet, including all of your private keys, on their own computers, and then proceed to transfer away all of your cryptocurrency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main problem is that the Jaxx software encrypts the mnemonic using a hard-coded encryption key, instead of making use of a strong user-supplied password. (As Daira Hopwood points out in the comments, using the PIN would not be sufficient.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This means we can easily read and decrypt the full recovery phrase from local storage using sqlite3 and some straight-forward code.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I successfully tested this vulnerability on the Jaxx Chrome extension v1.2.17 and the Jaxx Linux desktop app 1.2.13.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have BTC, ETH, ETC or other coins in Jaxx &lt;a href=&quot;https://image.prntscr.com/image/H0bBXL7eQvmoiHnzyhF5nQ.png&quot;&gt;get them out now&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you only ever used the Jaxx mobile apps your coins are apparently safe (not if you use both desktop and and mobile though).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&quot;https://image.prntscr.com/image/jfXeeLw_Ri2VJjd-sz60fg.png&quot;&gt;People report stolen ETH, ETC and ZEC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you lost coins report it &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.me/whalepoolbtc&quot;&gt;on whalepool telegram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 21:39:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jaxx-vulnerability</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jaxx-vulnerability</guid>
        
        
        <category>wallets</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bitfinex is adding IOTA trading</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;mailchimpfix&quot;&gt; &lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;400px&quot; height=&quot;300px&quot; layout=&quot;fixed&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://amp2disqus.netlify.com/altcointrading/signup.html&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt; &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So whats today’s hype about?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IOTA is a token that is meant to work with the IoT. It promises zero-fee transactions and infinite scalability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far IOTA hasn’t been traded on any exchange. There was p2p trading with escrow going on on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://slack.iota.org&quot;&gt;IOTA Slack chanel&lt;/a&gt;, the channel is now closed to new subscribers though and IOTA will be listed on Bitfinex in a few days. Unless you already are in that channel you won’t be able to buy IOTA until it launches on Finex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, June 13, we will be adding support for IOTA (IOT) exchange trading through IOT/USD and IOT/BTC pairs. Margin trading for IOT pairs will be enabled in the coming days as the order book develops suitable liquidity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Bitfinex has followed IOTA since its earliest stages of development and supports the project’s innovative approach toward a blockless distributed ledger. We believe the underlying technology can lead to a new ecosystem of applications built upon this decentralized and self-regulating peer-to-peer network.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;from https://www.bitfinex.com/posts/206&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/uploads/2017/06/04/iota.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/uploads/2017/06/04/iota.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The technicalities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, IOTA is not on a blockchain, similarly as Ripple although the technology underneath is different. That’s how it can scale and all the rest of it - it is not a blockchain. IOTA uses what they call Tangle:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In the Tangle, every single transaction forms a new block and is essentially verified by itself: In order to successfully conduct a transaction, you first have to verify two randomly chosen transactions is the network. This is done with help of a very simple version of proof-of-work, therefore one could argue that transactions aren’t zero-cost. Yet, the transaction costs are essentially not existent, as the needed PoW is so low that every single device is able to independently carry it out. &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@cryptojudgement/iota-promise-of-a-bright-crypto-future-6b7517349e32&quot;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this kind of decentralized PoW the scalability is also naturally growing as the network gets used more. This is good for the network effect of money that is needed for micropayments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IOTA is premined. There is no mining at all. 2779530283277761 IOTA were created, that is more than 2 · 10^15. Hint: It’s a lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The team behind IOTA has formed a foundation in Berlin. Names: Dominik Schiener, David Sønstebø, Sergey Ivancheglo and Sergei Popov. The development of IOTA was funded via ICO from back in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expectations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this type of coin that had a big ICO and OTC market and is premined it is expected that early adopters will cash out at the exchange listing launch, so don’t rush with your purchase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that, a reasonable amount of hype and “potential”-buying is probably going to happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Charts and info&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;http://iotaprice.com/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;https://www.iotatoken.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;some-in-depth-reading&quot;&gt;Some in-depth reading&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@cryptojudgement/iota-promise-of-a-bright-crypto-future-6b7517349e32&quot;&gt;@cryptojudgement: ,,Promise of a bright crypto future”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://altcoinspekulant.wordpress.com/category/iota/&quot;&gt;altcoinspekulant, for the German in you&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 17:07:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/iota</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/iota</guid>
        
        
        <category>altcoins</category>
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What you need to know about QTUM</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The coin in the news this week is Quantum - newly traded altcoin that &lt;a href=&quot;https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/qtum/#charts&quot;&gt;doubled in dollar value between June 1st ‘17 and June 2nd ‘17&lt;/a&gt;. (But this is not a bubble though, is it? Certainly doesn’t look like it. Corrections are a myth, as said someone in Facebook’s Ethereum group.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;qtum---fundamentals&quot;&gt;QTUM - Fundamentals&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quantum is a Bitcoin/Ethereum hybrid branded as the “business-friendly blockchain”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;By implementing the Bitcoin Improvement Protocols (BIPs), and making use of the Ethereum Virtual Machine, digital currency enthusiasts can finally agree on one platform that will offer stability and direction. – via https://qtum.org/en/general-faq&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main fundamental advantage of the QTUM blockchain is supposed to be the UTXO model. Each token can only be either “spent” or “unspent”, there is no doublespend issue, in this way the blockchain is more secure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s what the QTUM people say about their project, anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ICO Countdown published a full due dilligence post &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@icocountdown/due-diligence-pack-for-qtum-7369ef48917b&quot;&gt;here on medium.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;ico-countdowns-due-dilligence-tldr&quot;&gt;ICO Countdown’s Due Dilligence TLDR&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One worrying thing is that there was apparently something unclear about the QTUM’s lead identity, and there were news about collaborations altered and deleted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turns out the founder, Patric Dai, has been acting in cryptocurrency space &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=1720632.msg17970584#msg17970584&quot;&gt;using various western names as he says himself&lt;/a&gt; after he was &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=1720632.msg17970464#msg17970464&quot;&gt;called out on bitcointalk&lt;/a&gt;. He was involved in the BitBay exchange and co-founded Tilepay. From comments on bitcointalk:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Yes, Shuai Early is Patrick Dai, Steven Dai. And Tilepay’s co-founder, people said he made fake promises at tilepay project, therefor he had several projects before. THB, he should be no face to create more projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The article by &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@icocountdown/due-diligence-pack-for-qtum-7369ef48917b&quot;&gt;@icocountdown says&lt;/a&gt; that Dai should have stolen some money from developer funds he had access to. He then should have used the money to manipulate prices and profit from the pump and dump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*E_d_jyZ0T_JaODIjRuLQhg.png&quot;&gt;See the screenshot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Forbes have been much friendlier towards this project - read here https://www.forbes.com/sites/rogeraitken/2017/03/17/qtums-blockchain-crowdfund-scores-over-12m-from-bitcoin-ethereum-investors/#5ee97ed434ef&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;qtum---technicals&quot;&gt;QTUM - Technicals&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The safest place to bet on this project is &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.bitmex.com/register/iYQB44&quot;&gt;BitMEX&lt;/a&gt; where they opened QTUM contract trading on June 1st with 2x leverage and 25% cap on changes to fight the manipulation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with any ICO these days, traders have gone apathic towards the fundamentals and are ready to buy cheap anything to dump it on the greater fool two hours later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the QTUM BitMEX trading was only announced today in their &lt;a href=&quot;http://mailchi.mp/bitmex/crypto-trader-digest-1307645?e=e9cf3ee662&quot;&gt;latest digest&lt;/a&gt; while people have been trading since yesterday already.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be more specific: people doubled their money on the QTUM contract yesterday already.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technically though, what we see today looks like a bull flag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/uploads/2017/06/02/qtum-bitmex1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/uploads/2017/06/02/qtum-bitmex1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Full specification from BitMEX:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BitMEX is proud to announce the launch of QTUM Futures contracts, expiry 29 September 12:00 UTC with symbol QTUMU17. Each contract is worth 1 QTUM and the contract offers 2x leverage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the QTUM platform is still under development, the following rules will apply:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;QTUMU17 will have a 25% Up and Down Limit against the previous session close price to prevent price manipulation. Each session is 2 hours long, and session closes occur every even numbered hour.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Settlement will occur either at the ICO price (if QTUM/XBT trading has not begun) or at the .QTUMXBT30M Index Price if QTUM/XBT has begun trading prior to 28 September 12:00 UTC.
Further details about this contract can be read in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bitmex.com/app/seriesGuide/QTUM&quot;&gt;QTUM Series Guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.bitmex.com/register/iYQB44&quot;&gt;Signup at BitMEX&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 07:27:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/quantum</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/quantum</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BAT/ETH trading is live</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;mailchimpfix&quot;&gt; &lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;400px&quot; height=&quot;300px&quot; layout=&quot;fixed&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://amp2disqus.netlify.com/altcointrading/signup.html&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt; &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulations to everyone who was faster than a regular American’s spermatozoon and got into the BAT presale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For everyone else, here’s where you can lose some lunch money over it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;https://liqui.io/#/exchange/BAT_ETH&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The BAT ICO was so hyped that the Ethereum network got congested and the sale was finished right in its first block. Some people got in by sending the transaction couple of blocks beforehand, counting on the congestion - but not all of them. It was a hit or miss. The miners gave preference to the chunky transactions, that means, the whales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s how the distribution of the token became so much “the rich are getting richer”. Plebs who just wanted in with 1 ETH didn’t stand a chance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/media/DBKavddU0AA4T3r.jpg&quot; style=&quot;max-width:100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Hilarious &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BAT&amp;amp;src=ctag&quot;&gt;$BAT&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/qMp5Y9JqjI&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/qMp5Y9JqjI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Angelo฿TC (@AngeloBTC) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/AngeloBTC/status/869927821463797760&quot;&gt;May 31, 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 11:53:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/bat-eth</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/bat-eth</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>OkCoin resumed BTC withdrawals</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;mailchimpfix&quot;&gt; &lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;400px&quot; height=&quot;300px&quot; layout=&quot;fixed&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://amp2disqus.netlify.com/altcointrading/signup.html&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt; &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today’s is the day. OkCoin.cn apparently resuming withdrawals - at least this is what the rumor says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;https://twitter.com/cnLedger/status/869934911179735040&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en-gb&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;BREAKING: We received report that OKCoin (CN site) resumed withdraws!&lt;br /&gt;W/d limit based on vip level, starting from 10BTC/200LTC/1000ETH daily&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; cnLedger (@cnLedger) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/cnLedger/status/869934911179735040&quot;&gt;31 May 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ETH on the other hand is experiencing a selloff, perhaps all the people who didn’t get in BAT.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 11:23:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/okcoin-withdrawals</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/okcoin-withdrawals</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>OkCoin Intl is adding ETH on June 1st 2017</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Only a few hours before the BAT ICO opening, today’s news is already more exciting than a double espresso after a night on BitMEX: OKCoin, everyone’s favorite bitcoin casino, is adding ETH trading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full announcement: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.okcoin.com/t-387.html&quot;&gt;https://www.okcoin.com/t-387.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[…] Recently, OKCoin users have taken interest in the development of Ethereum (ETH) and Ethereum Classic (ETC), and there is an increasing demand for OKCoin to enable ETH and ETC trading. For the past two years, we have been constantly reviewing the viability of listing ETH and ETC based on factors including technical maturity, innovation, market liquidity, and compliance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Today, we are formally launching ETH on the OKCoin exchange. Ethereum has a current circulation of 90 million, with ETH reaching a market cap in excess of USD 10 billion, and a total hashrate of more than 25K GB. Hundreds of applications are now built on Ethereum and a growing number of applications are using smart contracts run on the Ethereum blockchain.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;OKCoin will officially enable Ethereum (ETH) deposit and withdrawal services on 22:00, May 31. ETH trading services will be officially available on 12:00, June 1.[…]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t forget that OkCoin.com is a spot exchange only.&lt;/strong&gt; The derivative trading (futures) has been moved to OKEx.com. Hence sadly, there are no ETH futures at the moment. OKEx trades BTC and LTC futures, OkCoin.com trades BTC, LTC and ETH spot.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/okcoin-eth</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/okcoin-eth</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Huobi is adding ETH on May 31st</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Huobi announced an announcement this morning (fluffypony style!), the actual news came soon after from @cnLedger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many had high hopes for the withdrawal situation update – but it’s “just” ETH trading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Huobi has millions of users in China. Up to now none of the &amp;quot;big 3&amp;quot; listed any coins except BTC &amp;amp; LTC. Many CN traders are unaware of ETH &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/Wdd8sE8WuG&quot;&gt;https://t.co/Wdd8sE8WuG&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; cnLedger (@cnLedger) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/cnLedger/status/868457182429233155&quot;&gt;May 27, 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People &lt;a href=&quot;https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-withdrawals-expected-to-resume-as-chinese-exchanges-ask-users-for-funds-info&quot;&gt;still cannot withdraw coins from major Chinese exchanges&lt;/a&gt; but the BTC and LTC premium started diminishing on rumors the withdrawals might be resumed in June.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a letter shared via @cnLedger saying the exchanges were not asked to suspend withdrawals, that they did that on their own accord:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;PBoC reply to BTC user: we did not ask trading platforms to suspend w/d. It was a decision made by themselves. The inspection has not ended. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/mi3IxXR93g&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/mi3IxXR93g&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; cnLedger (@cnLedger) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/cnLedger/status/867651423038603264&quot;&gt;May 25, 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…Surely they were asked nicely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either way, Huobi is the first major exchange to list ETH. That could mean a boost for the coin as new wave of speculators (and bots) chimes in. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/6deopl/daily_discussion_friday_may_26_2017/di3fto6/&quot;&gt;Don’t forget more than 50% of the volume on the now-zero-fee Japanese exchange Bitflyer is done by three monster-bots only&lt;/a&gt; - the volatility there was insane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.okcoin.com/post/161088088064/okcoin-to-migrate-futures-activity-to-okexcom&quot;&gt;OkCoin had a big announcement too this week&lt;/a&gt; as they announced the migration to a new platform OKEx (coins-only, no fiat hence possibly less intervention) but no word about new altcoin implementations.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2017 09:29:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/huobi-eth</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/huobi-eth</guid>
        
        
        <category>eth</category>
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ripple vs Stellar</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;mailchimpfix&quot;&gt; &lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;400px&quot; height=&quot;300px&quot; layout=&quot;fixed&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://amp2disqus.netlify.com/altcointrading/signup.html&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfinex has added Ripple trading recently (May 19 announcement &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bitfinex.com/posts/204&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;), and according to the crypto trading myths that should mean the rally is over. They say, whenever a mainstream exchange with fiat deposits adds a coin, the smart money leaves it and sells to the laggards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Ripple, a double-top going on is already old news:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/uploads/2017/05/21/hJtMYhLc.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/uploads/2017/05/21/hJtMYhLc.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is what the lovely Ripple chart looks like in 1D version on Bitfinex:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/x/ctF9dUWV&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/x/ctF9dUWV&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;would-you-buy-ripple-now&quot;&gt;Would you buy Ripple now?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buy Ripple only of you trust its fundamentals, as a long term investment - and this is entirely your call. There is no problem storing it - &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ledgerwallet.com/r/e274?path=/products/ledger-nano-s&quot;&gt;Ledger Nano S&lt;/a&gt; has a Ripple wallet now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ripples-fundamentals&quot;&gt;Ripple’s Fundamentals&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To some altcoin traders, Ripple is a &lt;em&gt;centralized bankster scamcoin&lt;/em&gt;, a sort of “step back” in the world of crypto. To others, Ripple being &lt;a href=&quot;https://dealbook.nytimes.com/2013/11/11/the-rush-to-coin-virtual-money-with-real-value/?_php=true&amp;amp;_type=blogs&amp;amp;_r=1&quot;&gt;backed by banks&lt;/a&gt; is actually a good, reassuring sign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some things to keep in mind:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ripple is not a blockchain.&lt;/strong&gt; No blockchain also means there is no scaling problem and so in this way, Ripple as a medium for payments and settlements is better. The Ripple network works in such a way that transactions are forgotten once they are through so the ledger doesn’t grow as fast as blockchains do (all of them, Ethereum too).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Ripple, only address balances are kept - no histories. Meaning, &lt;strong&gt;Ripple is only a payment protocol&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ripple cannot be mined. Transactions get validated via consensus mechanism where participants are responsible to choose a set of validators that will not be fraudulent: &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/technical-faq-ripple-consensus-ledger/&quot;&gt;https://ripple.com/technical-faq-ripple-consensus-ledger/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/i6mhQcpPtyk&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/i6mhQcpPtyk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; custom-element=&quot;amp-youtube&quot; src=&quot;https://cdn.ampproject.org/v0/amp-youtube-0.1.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;amp-youtube data-videoid=&quot;i6mhQcpPtyk&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; height=&quot;360&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-youtube&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ripples-competition-stellar&quot;&gt;Ripple’s Competition: Stellar&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stellar makes it possible to send remittances cheaply across borders via its tokens, lumens. Originally, Stellar was based on the Ripple protocol (and founded by one of the Ripple founders) but after changes in the Ripple codebase Stellar forked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compared to Ripple being picked up mostly by banks, Stellar is a platform that gets used &lt;a href=&quot;http://fortune.com/2016/12/06/fintech-stellar-blockchain-stripe-remittances/&quot;&gt;IRL in non-profits&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;On a call with Fortune, McCaleb, Stellar’s cofounder and chief technology officer, expressed his desire to connect everyone in the world through the Stellar network. “We’re trying to be an Internet-level protocol for payments,” he said, drawing an analogy to SMTP, a standard for email transmission.
He added: “We want everybody to plug into it and for money to float seamlessly.”Other companies are also competing to become the standard for blockchain-based cross-border payments. Among them are McCaleb’s former firm Ripple, and Chain, a fintech startup backed by Visa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no mining in Stellar. Confirmations are done by selected trusted nodes - AKA Stellar Consensus Protocol. To a non-techie it is similar to Ripple: In Bitcoin, any miner is a trusted node by default, in consensus mechanism participants choose a trusted set of validators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reality is more complex:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;At a low level, the consensus mechanism used by Stellar is a decentralized version of PBFT called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stellar.org/papers/stellar-consensus-protocol.pdf&quot;&gt;Stellar Consensus Protocol&lt;/a&gt;, whereas &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/dev-blog/consensus-whitepaper-released/&quot;&gt;Ripple uses probabilistic voting&lt;/a&gt;. Those are fairly different even though they both tackle solving the same problem of reaching consensus between nodes. SCP biases towards correctness at the expense of liveness; Ripple follows a model similar to Bitcoin allowing ledger forks to occur temporarily and relying on majority validation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is not clear from this but the Stellar network &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stellar.org/developers/guides/concepts/ledger.html&quot;&gt;remembers transactional history&lt;/a&gt;. “Transactions are now a series of operations that affect the state of the world. For example, a single transaction can trivially say A sends to B if B sends to C. These abstractions, coupled with the network’s distributed exchange, produce a surprisingly rich vocabulary for contracts. Bonds, escrow, collateralized debt and the Lightning Network are all possible on the network.” - via &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinmagazine.com/articles/stellar-s-jed-mccaleb-what-s-new-on-the-upgraded-stellar-network-1452109082/&quot;&gt;bitcoinmagazine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;At the system level, &lt;strong&gt;Stellar’s native currency is inflationary whereas Ripple’s is not&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More to this below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;At the ledger operation level, Stellar adopted a very &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.faqs.org/rfcs/rfc1832.html&quot;&gt;strict API based off XDR&lt;/a&gt;, Ripple is built on top of &lt;a href=&quot;https://developers.google.com/protocol-buffers/&quot;&gt;Google Protocol Buffers&lt;/a&gt;. XDR can be thought of as “statically typed” vs “dynamically typed” for something like proto buf: the tradeoffs made are speed of development (in Ripple) vs safety and correctness (for Stellar’s approach).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-main-difference-between-Stellar-and-Ripple-protocols&quot;&gt;via Quora&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-inflation&quot;&gt;The Inflation&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stellar has limited supply with built-in inflation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stellar.org/developers/guides/concepts/inflation.html&quot;&gt;via stellar.org:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Stellar distributed network has a built-in, fixed, nominal inflation mechanism. New lumens are added to the network at the rate of 1% each year. Each week, the protocol distributes these lumens to any account that gets over .05% of the “votes” from other accounts in the network.
Using the set options operation, every account selects another account as its inflation destination, or nominee to receive new currency. The inflation destination will persist until changed with another set options operation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ripple has limited supply buy the native currency gets destroyed with successful transactions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.xrpchat.com/topic/2207-xrps-deflationary-nature/&quot;&gt;via xrpchat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q:&lt;/strong&gt; I guess this is a very basic-level question, but I don’t see it usually comes up on this forum whenever people speculate about XRP’s future price:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the deflationary nature of XRP, do you believe this feature might ever be an obstacle for XRP’s success? I mean, people will tend to save their XRP and not to spend them because they will be supposed to get more valuable over time, but at the same time this could also result in a constraint of XRP market and liquidity. By contrast, the Stellar network automatically applies a small inflation rate of 1% to its currency that could help solve this issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is your opinion? Could this be an original design flaw of XRP?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&lt;/strong&gt; Small amount of xrp gets destroyed with each transaction and its expected that as demand and transaction will increase that destruction rate will increase which will cause the same effect as inflation because of slowly decreasing supply but since things are in initial stage its gonna take long time in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-giveaway&quot;&gt;The giveaway&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you hold &lt;strong&gt;Bitcoins or Ripple&lt;/strong&gt; you can invest in Stellar/Lumens for free (which is frankly a no-brainer). &lt;strong&gt;There is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stellar.org/blog/bitcoin-claim-lumens-2/&quot;&gt;second Stellar giveaway for Bitcoin hodlers lined up for the summer 2017&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; The giveaway starts on June the 27th and the only drawback is you will need to have a facebook profile that confirms you reside in an unrestricted state:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Due to regulatory restrictions, this program is closed to residents of the U.S. states of New York, Georgia, New Hampshire, and Connecticut as well as the nations of Iran, Cuba, North Korea, and other countries subject to sanctions by the United States.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s probably still enough time to make one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will get Lumens automatically if you have BTC or XRP on Kraken, Poloniex, Deribit or BTC38.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix clearfix adfix&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-iframe width=&quot;728px&quot; height=&quot;90px&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; sandbox=&quot;allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-modals allow-popups allow-forms&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img layout=&quot;fill&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/ad-placeholder.jpg&quot; placeholder=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/amp-iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;so-ripple-is-deflationary&quot;&gt;So, Ripple is deflationary.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;There is currently circulating 38,532,538,149 XRP out of 99,994,681,824.21 XRP.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;There is currently circulating 9,624,904,739 XLM out of 102,920,806,155 XLM.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both coins are really only possibly valuable for payment processing – at least as long as Paypal or something like that is not an option. Well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Unlike some other fintechs, Ripple is bank centric. Banks connect to the Ripple network not their customers. This has two big benefits. First, customers are used to trusting banks (which is better than having to get comfortable with entrusting your money to some fintech you never heard of). Second, regulators are comfortable with banks (which means they will not pull the plug on Ripple as they might with non bank fintechs). - via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/ripple-vs-swift-payment-revolution-david-blair&quot;&gt;linkedin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is something to the obsession with bank coins. They say that when the wall street decides to pour all the money into something you would be stupid for not taking the ride with them. It’s just that in the case of Ripple, the banks &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/ripple-vs-swift-payment-revolution-david-blair&quot;&gt;are thrilled to use Ripple as a layer&lt;/a&gt; but that can only increase the value of Ripple by burning the currency as transactions get settled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, given the hype on altcoin forums whenever anything gets official acknowledgement from the shiny official people up there in the institutions, it’s quite likely the “fundamental” price growth is going to be small compared to the &lt;em&gt;buy the rumor&lt;/em&gt; hype. In other words, bubbles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, Stellar looks more compatible with Bitcoin - maybe as an offchain layer, one day?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 02:38:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/ripple-vs-stellar</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/ripple-vs-stellar</guid>
        
        <category>feature</category>
        
        
        <category>altcoins</category>
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
