<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Altcoin Trading</title>
    <description>Altcoin Trading is the forex of cryptocurrencies, with bitcoin as the base currency.</description>
    <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.altcointrading.net/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 20:03:55 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 20:03:55 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ethereum Classic on Poloniex today, on Bitfinex soon</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-4.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Small part of Ethereum community formed Ethereum Classic.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;/eth-hard-fork/&quot;&gt;Ethereum hard fork&lt;/a&gt; on 20th of July went smoothly without any issues. All was received well by the community, both ETHBTC and ETHUSD price kept rising, DAO funds were recovered, attacker was left with nothing. So what happened?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/ethbtc-postfork.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/ethbtc-postfork.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://themerkle.com/the-ethereum-hard-fork-ethereum-classic/&quot;&gt;The Merkle&lt;/a&gt; puts it in a brief enough way:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;A small group within the Ethereum community has stayed on the old side of the fork with their own duplicate blockchain. This project is called Ethereum Classic and it promises to keep the ecosystem decentralized and free from censorship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This is a contradictory view to some, in the sense that Ethereum Classic has kept their own set of rules despite the consensus of the community, which is the exact opposite of what decentralized and censorship-free means. The project gained traction, none the less, with two mining pools dedicated to classic miners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, only four days after the hard fork, the first exchange is adding ETH Classic:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://themerkle.com/ethereum-classic-is-now-trading-on-poloniex/&quot;&gt;Ethereum Classic is now trading on Poloniex&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ETH Classic is the old blockchain, to be continued by people who don’t agree with recovering of the DAO stolen funds&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Trading of the Classic coin started on Poloniex on 24 July under the symbol ETC.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ETCBTC keeps low price after some wild initial pumping but volume is picking up (see below). At the time of writing ETCBTC costs 0.0014 while ETHBTC keeps at 0.0195 but sinking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/etcbtc.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/etcbtc.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zane Tackett, Bitfinex product manager, confirmed on /r/ethereum that ETHC will indeed be added soon:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-uuid=&quot;08749486-76d2-462e-aced-88ca08bdea5e&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-07-24T16:41:31.232Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethereum/comments/4uczsp/bitfinex_to_list_ethc_soon/d5opzjn&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethereum/comments/4uczsp/bitfinex_to_list_ethc_soon/&quot;&gt;Bitfinex to list $ETHC soon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-is-expected-from-a-traders-point-of-view&quot;&gt;What is expected from a trader’s point of view&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In spite of ETC being “the original” Ethereum it is not expected ETC will moon to the ETH levels any time soon.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Volume is great though, people might be buying in case it sticks.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;51% attack against ETC has been outed &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethereum/comments/4ucgia/i_am_chandler_guo_a_51_attack_on_ethereum_classic/?st=ir0ugc2w&amp;amp;sh=d12a2146&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ETC might be underpriced because traders are finding “free ETC” on their Poloniex accounts and selling them en masse. &lt;strong&gt;That’s the most important thing:&lt;/strong&gt; If you were holding ETH before the hard fork, you should be sitting on some ETC on Poloniex today. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/4ud74f/free_money_on_polo/?ref=share&amp;amp;ref_source=link&quot;&gt;Read here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;On the other hand, the ETC blockchain is not fit to be used for dApps anymore which makes it’s value only speculative at the moment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-classic/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-classic/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Value of Altcoins: Money and Tokens Reloaded</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/charts/ethdash.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/charts/ethdash.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: ETH-Dash chart (data from ShapeShift instant exchange, chart altcoinwisdom.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is it all about altcoins in 2016? It looks like a big thing starting out. Sure, markets are volatile and risky but in spite of that interesting things are on the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, to the altcoin value, apart from the fact that every altcoin is &lt;em&gt;new paradigm, totally&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;absolutely something new&lt;/em&gt;, there are two, well - actually three categories of altcoins out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;types-of-altcoins&quot;&gt;Types of altcoins&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;altcoins-as-means-of-payment&quot;&gt;Altcoins as means of payment&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some altcoins were developed as means of payment. You can usually tell from the coin’s name - like &lt;em&gt;Monero&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Digital Cash (DASH)&lt;/em&gt;. Litecoin was also developed primarily for payments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These altcoins usually solve one of the drawbacks of Bitcoin: the fact that Bitcoin is not anonymous, that scalability is not built in by default (see the current block size debate) or that there is still some sort of centralized governance needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trading money-altcoins is much like trading forex. It’s money, it’s a storage of value, a hedge - it is (if all is right) held and used by some people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interesting altcoins:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Monero&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scalable and mined in a decentralized fashion Monero also takes privacy into account: Payments are unlinkable, untraceable and anonymous. At the moment there is a Monero-based market on Poloniex along with the BTC-based one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;DASH&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dash is short for digital cash. The pivotal property of DASH is anonymous blockchain. No more block explorers. Another advantage is no governance and no way to link transactions together. DASH is currently traded heavily on Poloniex and Bittrex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Litecoin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Up until recently LTC was the second most popular altcoin. It was created to handle massive transaction volumes but, uh, whatever happened to it, nobody seems interested anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similar properties regarding volumes also has Nextcoin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;altcoins-as-tokens&quot;&gt;Altcoins as tokens&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some altcoins were developed with blockchain technology in mind. Anyone who wants to participate in whatever lives on whichever blockchain needs to have the appropriate token. That can be &lt;em&gt;Ether&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;MaidSafeCoin&lt;/em&gt;, for instance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is why Vitalik Buterin doesn’t endorse Ether as a value storage. It is not supposed to be money, it is supposed to be used to fuel certain type of apps. That is supposed to be it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why are these tokens speculated so much then? The answer is &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blue_Ocean_Strategy#Concept&quot;&gt;Blue ocean Strategy&lt;/a&gt;. Traders argue that Ether and other tokens are downplaying the monetary value of the coin on purpose: To show that it is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; just another “better money”. Tokens are a new category - something for which the demand is yet to be created. The value is expected to surge with the new demand. The demand will be by nature of the process focused on the token with no competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interesting altcoins:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MaidSafeCoin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MaidSafeCoin is a token for SAFE network. SAFE means Secure access for everyone, it is a distributed data management. All data is encrypted and cryptosigned by client. Computers storing data of SAFE network are mining credits ( ~ safecoins ) which are exchanged for goods and services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn more about the SAFE network &lt;a href=&quot;http://maidsafe.net/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ether &amp;amp; Co&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ether was heavily pumped, before which fanboys kept spamming bitcoin traders on Reddit claiming ETH is the new bitcoin. Now the interest is cooling down, there are no real massively popular Ethereum apps (Đapps) that would make the interest in Ether more than a pump/dump scheme for now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There in infinite amount of Ether to be mined but the inflation is only 1% a year. If the value of the coin gets stable it makes ETH a better value storage than traditional money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ethereum is the platform on which Ether is the token. It is a platform on which Đapps (decentralized apps) are supposed to live. These can be used to store data or smart contracts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other important tokens related to ETH:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/eth-vs-lisk/&quot;&gt;The DAO&lt;/a&gt; - Decentralized Autonomous Organization - and slock.it&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://dgx.io/#/&quot;&gt;Digix&lt;/a&gt; - Gold certificates&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ripple&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ripple is focused on smart contracts too. As a currency, its value is that of a bridge currency: All transaction across currencies can be instantaneous if every currency is liquid to Ripple and if exchange transactions are done through Ripple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;BitShares&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BitShares are one of the most interesting ideas in the altcoin space (click &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php?topic=7628.0&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for ELI5). The concept of BTS are shares in Decentralized Autonomous Companies (DACs). Anyone can become a “shareholder” of the first DAC by buying BitShares. The company’s work is then focused on revenue generation in form of bitUSD or whatever the company decides to call their profit unit. That is: the profit is generated in form of a “currency” pegged to USD. BTS (BitShares) can be thought of as a regular stock on a stock market&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;List of “Smart Contract” Coins&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ETH&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;DAO&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;LISK&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MAID&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;del&gt;XRP / Codius&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;BURST&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;XCH&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;STEEM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some reading:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://changelly.com/blog/how-smart-contracts-work/&quot;&gt;How smart contracts work @changelly.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://steemit.com/lisk/@dan/why-lisk-is-inferior-to-ethereum&quot;&gt;Steem as a Smart Contract Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;shitcoins&quot;&gt;Shitcoins&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last category are shitcoins. Coins that were created as an ego-blast of someone who could afford to pay the programmer and have no value proposition. If you check their websites you will see generic terms and buzzwords regarding issues that were already solved by many altcoins before, like&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Vcash was engineered to be innovative and forward-thinking. It prevents eavesdropping and censorship, promotes decentralized, energy efficient and instant network transactions.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.vanillacoin.net/&quot;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their value is purely speculative. They might pump and you might be coming early enough to cash in but that’s it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/value/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/value/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Technical Analysis: Divergences</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/ta/bitfinex-divergences.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/ta/bitfinex-divergences.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Divergeces between lows or highs on the price action and the MACD can provide valuable signals.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;so-technical-analysis&quot;&gt;So, technical analysis?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technical analysis is something that newbie crypto-traders search for a lot while the sheer amount of resources is astounding. Often, the little Youtube channels are the best since they are managed by people who make living of trading and don’t have as much time to promote the Youtube channel - which is why most often you will not hear about them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TA Indicator: Divergences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is one channel maintained (occasionally) by a redditor /u/drwd. He does a series called “Better know an indicator” which already provided a very fine intro to the Ichimoku cloud for many traders. He made a good video on divergences (“divs”) that is worth looking at unless you are a seasoned trader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;700&quot; height=&quot;365&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/nGbqFV0koaQ&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Divergences in short&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Divergence happens when market price disagrees with indicators action. Divergence can be regular, hidden and exaggerated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Regular Div&lt;/em&gt; is a sign of trend reversal. Price keeps the trend but indicator already shows the reversal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Signal to short = the price makes higher high but MACD makes lower high. Underlying weakness, possible exhaustion of a bull trend.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Signal to long = the price makes lower low but MACD makes higher low. Underlying strength, possible exhaustion of bears.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hidden Div&lt;/em&gt; is a divergence that follows the trend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Signal to short = price makes lower highs but MACD makes higher highs. Tends to be found during a retracement up during a downtrend.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Signal to long = price makes higher low but MACD makes lower low. Tends to be found during a retracement in an uptrend.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Exaggerated Div&lt;/em&gt; is similar to regular div but price action makes double tops and double bottoms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/ta/divergences1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/ta/divergences1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The logic behind divergences is that sometimes the indicators shows hidden tendencies of the market (strength or weakness) that might not be visible from the price action yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not 100%, as always with technical analysis - the divergence can only inform you about a bias.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve read the list above it should be clear to you that you should first look at the bigger picture - are we in an uptrend or a downtrend? - and then start looking for divergences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you master them you can use them as a signal to enter or exit the market - they mark good spots for dip-buying and rally-selling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;good-to-read&quot;&gt;Good to read:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;”dukascopy.com / Do you know everything about divergences?” - The image above is taken from dukascopy.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dukascopy.com/fxcomm/fx-article-contest/?Do-You-Know-Everything-About=&amp;amp;action=read&amp;amp;id=890&quot; class=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Divs on dukascopy.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;”babypips.com / Divergence cheat sheet” - As images below. PRINT THEM!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.babypips.com/school/high-school/trading-divergences/divergence-cheat-sheet.html&quot; class=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Cheatsheet on babypips.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/ta/bp-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/ta/bp-2.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/ta-divergences/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/ta-divergences/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ethereum hard fork and your positions on exchanges</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-5.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: ETH, the centralized mutable digital token.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The event that is by some pegged as the end of mETH as cryptocurrency is actually hapenning. The response to the DAO hack will, after all, be the hard fork. This is a solution that some say could have happened after the MtGox collaps during the first years of bitcoin, it didn’t happen though since it effectively undermines the most valuable asset of a blockchain based token - it’s immutability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-immutability-of-blockchain---its-not-a-dogma-folks&quot;&gt;The immutability of blockchain - It’s not a dogma, folks&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a misconception that blockchain is immutable by some kind of magic that has no way around it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The very simplistic explanation of blockchain immutability is the hash that is generated for each blockchain block mined. The hash contains among other data also a reference to the previous block’s hash - which contains a reference to the previous block’s hash, and so on. Because of this the blockchain is &lt;em&gt;internally consistent&lt;/em&gt;, there can be some checks run on this. If a block shows up that contains the wrong reference it will be disregarded as invalid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To create a tampered blockchain therefore needs to effectively rebuild the blockchain from the modified block on. This is something that is difficult and won’t occur with no one noticing it, nevertheless &lt;strong&gt;it is possible&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is presumably more difficult with bitcoin since the governance is (in spite of all tryings) still more decentralized. There was a hardfork on bitcoin blockchain once, during the very early stages of it when Satoshi Nakamoto was still the lead and also one of the very few people who actually knew bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ETH is far more widespread than BTC during the time it was forked, but it still revolves all about Vitalik Buterin and Ethereum Foundation. There are many other people on /r/ethereum or /r/ethtrader but if you’ve read them for a while you see they look up to their leaders a lot. It is even now relatively easy for them to just “give a green light” to a decision like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be fair, it should also be mentioned the ETH hard fork will not have the effect of erasing all transaction history to the point of the fork. (More on this in next paragraph.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitsonblocks.net/2016/02/29/a-gentle-introduction-to-immutability-of-blockchains/&quot;&gt;Read more - Immutability of blockchain on bitsonblocks.net.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-it-means-for-an-altcoin-trader&quot;&gt;What it means for an altcoin trader?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many speculations as to the USD and BTC value of Ether and TheDAO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.colony.io/why-a-post-hard-fork-ethereum-will-be-more-valuable-abc35bbf6e98#.2q2vd0xwo&quot;&gt;Here a TheDAO token holder argues post-hard fork ETH will be more valuable.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Unlike Bitcoin, an Ethereum hard fork will not involve a wholesale rollback of the blockchain state. It will involve only a surgical strike to convert theDAO to a withdrawal only contract, allowing theDAO tokens to be redeemed for Ether. That’s it. It will not effect any other transaction history or balances.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;~ This is a very good news since &lt;strong&gt;your positions on exchanges will not be affected&lt;/strong&gt;. There will be a brief period of instability during the actual fork. Because of this, exchanges will freeze withdrawals and deposits for a few hours but trading will carry on as usual. The hard fork will occur and a winnign blockchain will be chosen but all past transactions wil be transferred onto it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It is recommended to record your ETH positions - profits, losses, funding costs and maintenance margin - in case of a glitch on behalf of the exchange.&lt;/em&gt; Make a screenshot or write them on paper and check after the fork if all is OK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another smart argument that speculators will like to see is that ETH hard fork might be very well received by the general public. Forking a coin to mitigate a downside, a bailout effectively, is something most people like to see since it gives them a sense of security. Much like insurance and pension funds. It’s a fact that there are very few people who prefer to really take care of themselves, think through possible risks and manage them - while all this doesn’t make for a good reputation because it is something not quite common among people, making one unpredictable and un-see-through-able for others, which is frowned upon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the hard fork, it’s quite likely ETH will be seen as the legit digital token used for benevolent app development while bitcoin will be seen as the drug money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is quite ironic that a token that has security holes and nothing new about its governance (which is centralized) will come better off out of this but as for trading, there is no truth - the price action depends on if most traders share the same opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://buytrezor.com?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wallets/trezor.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; title=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;official-statements-of-exchanges&quot;&gt;Official statements of exchanges&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.ethereum.org/2016/07/15/to-fork-or-not-to-fork/&quot;&gt;Here is the official blog of Ethereum foundation.&lt;/a&gt; It’s more about the technical details if that’s what you are interested in.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://poloniex.com/press-releases/2016.07.15-Ethereum-Hard-Fork/&quot;&gt;Poloniex press release assures customers they don’t need to do anything.&lt;/a&gt; Deposits and withdrawals will be paused around the hard fork but all ETH balances will be automatically transferred to the winning blockchain.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bitfinex.com/posts/118&quot;&gt;Bitfinex also released an announcement, similar to Poloniex.&lt;/a&gt; If you have more questions you can try support or Reddit, where Bitfinex’s product manager resides at /u/zanetackett. He has already been talking about this - browse through his posts before asking. There will be status updates on &lt;a href=&quot;http://bitfinex.statuspage.io/&quot;&gt;http://bitfinex.statuspage.io/&lt;/a&gt; which you can subscribe via email.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-uuid=&quot;4122a9e5-b2f3-4e80-a502-cb17d6d176a6&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-07-17T08:19:29.133Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/4sxxjf/daily_discussion_15jul2016/d5dp8nj&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/4sxxjf/daily_discussion_15jul2016/&quot;&gt;[Daily Discussion] - 15/Jul/2016&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-hard-fork/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-hard-fork/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bitcoin and Altcoin Trading with the Ichimoku Cloud</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/bitfinex_ichimoku.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/bitfinex_ichimoku.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Ethereum has enough volume, technical analysis is justified.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ichimoku cloud is the mysterious indicator available on &lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptowat.ch/&quot;&gt;cryptowat.ch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://stockcharts.com/school/doku.php?id=chart_school:technical_indicators:ichimoku_cloud&quot;&gt;Stockcharts on Ichimoku cloud&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Ichimoku Kinko Hyo translates into “one look equilibrium chart”. With one look, chartists can identify the trend and look for potential signals within that trend. The indicator was developed by Goichi Hosoda, a journalist, and published in his 1969 book. Even though the Ichimoku Cloud may seem complicated when viewed on the price chart, it is really a straight forward indicator that is very usable. It was, after all, created by a journalist, not a rocket scientist!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;lines-on-ichimoku-cloud-explained-like-youre-five&quot;&gt;Lines on Ichimoku cloud explained like you’re five&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/bitfinex_ichimoku_leg.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/bitfinex_ichimoku_leg.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ichimoku cloud uses past action of the market to predict future most likely direction along with support and resistance lines.
It is calculated from past EMAs and highs vs lows, among other things, &lt;a href=&quot;http://stockcharts.com/school/doku.php?id=chart_school:technical_indicators:ichimoku_cloud&quot;&gt;here’s more if you need to know&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The number of lines is confusing but here’s the basic info you need to know:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Senkou span are the borders of the (here) green cloud. It is green in this case as the market is bullish. It will be red in bearish markets. The space between the lines is called kumo. Senkou spans are major support/resistance lines - people set their stop orders on them because once the trend breaks through both of them, a reversal should come.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kinjun and Tenken lines are “balance” lines - &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.babypips.com/school/elementary/moving-averages/moving-average-crossover-trading.html&quot;&gt;fast and slow EMAs&lt;/a&gt;. If the price keeps around them, it is not overhyped nor underpriced. If it gets distant it is changing direction way faster than it “should” and a pullback is likely. In such a case, people set stop-loss orders around the lines if they are in a position and don’t want to take profits until necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Chinkou line is a lagging indicator. You can use it to confirm a trend.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video Intro into Ichimoku Cloud from Youtube by @CarpeNoctom&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;700&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/J3t2Tsn_Imk&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BASICS: Ichimoku cloud Bullish signals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a strong bullish signal, everything must occur above the Kumo cloud: The price action must remain &lt;strong&gt;above&lt;/strong&gt; the Kumo cloud. The Chinkou line must stay &lt;strong&gt;above&lt;/strong&gt; the kumo and Tenken should be crossing Kinjun also &lt;strong&gt;above&lt;/strong&gt; the Kumo. Tenken should be crossing upside - if this cross occurs inside of the Kumo that’s still bullish but not so strongly bullish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BASICS: Ichimoku cloud Bearish signals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for strong bearish signal, with Ichimoku cloud you can pretty much reverse all that has been said to bullish signals - price action occurs &lt;strong&gt;below&lt;/strong&gt; Kumo, as well as Tenken and Kinjun crossing and the lagging line Chinkou. Basically the more happens below the stronger the bears are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BASICS: None of this?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If none of this is happening then it most likely means that at your timeframe the market is &lt;em&gt;undecided, sideways, waiting for direction&lt;/em&gt;. Don’t worry, if a breakout happens the traders of twitter and reddit will call it - keep reading to learn whom to follow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-to-read-and-whom-to-follow&quot;&gt;What to read and whom to follow&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[TOOL]&lt;/strong&gt; Ichimoku Trading signals&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A whole website about it. None of anything is investment advice though - trade your thoughts. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ichimokutrader.com/signals.html&quot;&gt;See the signal page.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traders who tweet about Ichimoku cloud&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CarpeNoctom&lt;/strong&gt; (Josh Olszewicz)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/CarpeNoctom&quot;&gt;#BubbleMoku&lt;/a&gt; is the author of the above mentioned Youtube channel, and also DrWD on Reddit, as mentioned below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en-gb&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Busy chart that says we&amp;#39;re going up, so long as we don&amp;#39;t break 600. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;trgt = 840-940 BFX &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/j5pzJjXORI&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/j5pzJjXORI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; #BubbleMoku (@CarpeNoctom) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/CarpeNoctom/status/748010819775041542&quot;&gt;29 June 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Triforcetrader&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/triforcetrader&quot;&gt;Triforcetrader&lt;/a&gt; tweets general trading stuff since he is a full-time trader. Sometimes he’ll feaure some TA but there is plenty of it on his website - &lt;a href=&quot;http://triforcetrader.com/trading/ichimoku/&quot;&gt;Here is his post on Ichimoku cloud.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He made a video on how he trades Ichimoku cloud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;700&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/p_Z6ogQIE6E&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Redditors who post about Ichimoku cloud&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DrWD&lt;/strong&gt; (Josh Olszewicz) is probably the only consistent Ichimoku advocate in the cryptocurrency space on Reddit these days. He posts in the stickied threads on /r/BitcoinMarkets. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/drwd&quot;&gt;Bookmark his profile page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SFFWMorin&lt;/strong&gt; posted an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/StockMarket/comments/434jrn/ichimoku_cloud_how_to_trade_guide/&quot;&gt;Ichimoku cloud tutorial on the subreddit /r/StockMarkets&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/ichimoku-cloud/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/ichimoku-cloud/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All about the DAO hack</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-3.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: DAOs have a critical vulnerability that can probably be removed only by a hard fork.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-dao-hack-simplified&quot;&gt;The DAO hack simplified&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great summary can be found on &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.erratasec.com/2016/06/etheriumdao-hack-similfied.html&quot;&gt;erratasec blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It starts with an explanation of what are smart contracts (the main purpose of the Ethereum platform) actually good for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Let’s say that we want to organize a small conference. We need 100 people to sign up and pay/deposit money, so we can rent a hotel and such. But if not enough people sign up by a certain date, then the deposits need to be refunded. With Ethereum, we can write in a JavaScript-like language to code up this contract. It’ll guarantee that everyone will get a ticket to the conference, or everyone will get their money refunded, depending on how many sign up.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main point is, this whole redistribution of payments that, depending on a condition, might or might not be returned to the people who paid them, is supposed to be made automatic. There is supposed to be no human overseeing it or interpreting the circumstances to help &lt;em&gt;someone in power&lt;/em&gt; decide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then the DAOs are explained, specifically how you &lt;em&gt;leave&lt;/em&gt; a DAO (not just TheDAO but any DAO). The issue here is to leave you need to create your own DAO if you have invested in a project that is still ongoing. Your &lt;em&gt;child DAO&lt;/em&gt; will receive the payout of your investment once the project is over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;When you want to leave the fund, you split from it. This includes your share of unspent Ethereum coins, but also tokens representing returns on investments you were part of, but which haven’t yet paid out. That’s why you “split” rather than “cash out”, you need your own DAO shard to track those investments until they pay out.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This DAO splitting is exactly where the hack occured&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;When a member exits the investment scheme, they call the function name splitDAO(). (…) The member will supply some of their own code with the transaction. Among the things that code will do is tell the DAO code how to transfer Ethereum coin. (…) [Another] issue is that Ethereum code is recursive. That means when a function is running, it may call itself a second time. The bug is that when splitDAO() is called, it will then call the recipients code to transfer Ethereum coin, after which the recipients code will call splitDAO() again before finishing. This causes the process to repeat itself, transferring more Ethereum coin, then calling splitDAO() again, which calls the hacker’s code, which calls splitDAO(), which calls the hacker’s code, and so on. The process will continue endlessly, until it drains all of TheDAO’s coin.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.erratasec.com/2016/06/etheriumdao-hack-similfied.html&quot;&gt;Ethereum/TheDAO hack simplified, erratasec.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see that the bug is inherent to DAO codebase and closely related to how Ethereum platform works. If this very basic code is not altered, all future DAOs are subject to this bug.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;stolen-money-recovery&quot;&gt;Stolen money recovery&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only way to &lt;em&gt;undo&lt;/em&gt; this is to rewind the blockchain to the state before the attack occured which has been seriously considered and which spooked all the non-ETH fanbois. It would undo not only the hack but also all the other transactions that occured in the meantime which means screwing over the few for the sake of an organization that is too big to fail, as the ErrataSec article points out. We know that from centralized banking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coindesk.com/ethereum-response-dao-kill/&quot;&gt;Why the Wrong Response to The DAO Attack Could Kill Ethereum, coindesk.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently the ongoing solution to this issue implemented by the developers was one that avoids the rewind: New child &lt;em&gt;whitehat&lt;/em&gt; DAO attacks were created with the purpose to attack the malicious DAO. The whitehad DAOs rolled out on the 21st of June while developers kept reassuring everybody the attacker cannot access the stolen funds for 27 days which is enough time to come up with a solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coindesk.com/ethereum-developers-draining-dao/&quot;&gt;Ethereum Developers Launch White Hat Counter-Attack on The DAO, coindesk.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This attempt to shake off the hacker failed. Since the whitehat DAOs needed capital to run, they started accepting donations. The person behind the initial hack also donated some ETH to the whitehat DAOs and is hence a shareholder, possibly planning to drain the whitehat DAOs as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-06-22T19:18:28.549Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethereum/comments/4p9z93/it_seems_attacker_just_targeted_the_whitehatdaos/d4j7ldn&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethereum/comments/4p9z93/it_seems_attacker_just_targeted_the_whitehatdaos/&quot;&gt;It seems attacker just targeted the WhiteHatDAOs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, a Cornell professor found 10 other vulnerabilities in DAO and calls for a DAO 2.0 movement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coindesk.com/cornell-prof-discovered-dao-vulnerability-reveals-10-exploits/&quot;&gt;Cornell Professor Calls for ‘DAO 2.0’ Movement, coindesk.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;current-ethereum-sentiment&quot;&gt;Current Ethereum Sentiment&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/screenshots/dao2.PNG&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/screenshots/dao2.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People on ETH trading subreddits feel that the dev team looks after them and have more confidence in ETH now than in BTC (with notoriously indecisive governance) - in spite of the fact ETH is fundamentally flawed and DAOs are subject to future fund drainings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/4p9ivx/im_dumping_all_my_btc_for_eth/&quot;&gt;I’m dumping all my BTC for ETH, /r/ethtrader&lt;/a&gt; with a screenshot full of unconfirmed bitcoin transactions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This goes hand in hand with the sentiment that is being created by the community voices, and that is that the DAO hack is good for Ethereum since it is only &lt;em&gt;pruning&lt;/em&gt;, similar to the shaking out of the weak hands during a run-up, where only the most faithful will prevail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-06-22T18:56:51.453Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/4p9ba2/important_announcement_recession_is_cancelled/d4j3dot&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/4p9ba2/important_announcement_recession_is_cancelled/&quot;&gt;Important announcement: Recession is cancelled, effective immediately&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For clarification, traders say that the weak hands are being shaken off when there is a bullish market that retraces significantly after a profit taking on a local top, forcing highly leveraged longs to market sell at a loss. That results in some more price drop where winners take it all, i.e. people with enough capital will take the advantage of - pardon my French - cheap coins and drive the price up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has nothing to do with pseudo-Christian faith in a leader/savior and putting money into a platform where they might be irreversibly lost while there are plenty of alternatives without this downside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consequently careful speculations occurred on /r/bitcoinmarkets considering manipulations from the side of wealthy ETH holders that need the ETH price to hike up to $30 once again before they cash out for good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-06-22T19:14:01.813Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4p8s1p/daily_discussion_wednesday_june_22_2016/d4ja4bb&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4p8s1p/daily_discussion_wednesday_june_22_2016/&quot;&gt;[Daily Discussion] Wednesday, June 22, 2016&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is probably worth mentioning that some people are just in for the penny stock chance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/screenshots/dao3.PNG&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/screenshots/dao3.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, officials are concerned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/screenshots/dao-reg.PNG&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/screenshots/dao-reg.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;####Some more reading&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coindesk.com/the-dao-an-analysis-of-the-fallout/&quot;&gt;Coindesk DAO fail analysis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coindesk.com/the-dao-bitcoin-development/&quot;&gt;What Ethereum’s DAO Disaster Means for Bitcoin Development&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/dao-hack/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/dao-hack/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ETH is selling off...</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-6.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: The DAO funds stolen and panic kicks in.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this place will not be the first website you will open up today, bloodbath on many cryptomarkets today deserves some clarification.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en-gb&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;The DAO is being attacked, massive selloff &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/av0Wk1QuSN&quot;&gt;https://t.co/av0Wk1QuSN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; BitcoinTrading Tools (@TradingFanbois) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/TradingFanbois/status/743735739574214659&quot;&gt;17 June 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier on the 17 of June the &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=11921216&quot;&gt;news started spreading&lt;/a&gt; that someone is leeching on The DAO funds and shouldn’t be. While the real DAO holders were most likely still asleep, a massive ETH sell off started. Lisk, DAO and surprisingly BTC dropped too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;true&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-06-17T10:32:40.829Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4ohgj1/daily_discussion_friday_june_17_2016/d4ctgbt&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4ohgj1/daily_discussion_friday_june_17_2016/&quot;&gt;[Daily Discussion] Friday, June 17, 2016&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indeed everyone who was awake at the moment went to cash in on the ETHUSD and ETHBTC chop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/ethdown.jpeg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/ethdown.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That caused the Bitfinex ETH margin funding rates soar. People went off to Poloniex but their servers are not quite ready for this drama, good luck withdrawing your funds. Not even talking about Kraken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-06-17T10:46:28.399Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4ohgj1/daily_discussion_friday_june_17_2016/d4cspky&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4ohgj1/daily_discussion_friday_june_17_2016/&quot;&gt;[Daily Discussion] Friday, June 17, 2016&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More than usual, be careful about highly leveraged position - it’s mental round here, volatility is high and &lt;strong&gt;you might not make it to add margin in time&lt;/strong&gt; if the market moves against you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Someone rather naive in Poloniex trollbox said “The website is lagging as fuck, is this professional?”.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The charting services most of us tend to use are lagging too when the load is too much (cryptowat.ch particlarly). &lt;strong&gt;Most altcoin pairs are on tradingview.com these days&lt;/strong&gt;, go for charts over there.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bitfinex has a scheduled outage today. &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitfinex.statuspage.io/&quot;&gt;Subscribe to their Statuspage updates&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-17-06-2016/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-17-06-2016/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some more ICOs in 2016?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/icowatch.jpeg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/icowatch.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: In case you missed DAO, Lisk and Waves you might be firing up the search engines in the mighty state of FOMO. Well, there is not much to miss this year.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;ico-watching-services&quot;&gt;ICO Watching Services&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right first off: There are a few websites that gather information about ICOs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all you can go directlt to &lt;a href=&quot;http://icostart.com&quot;&gt;icostart.com&lt;/a&gt; and place random bets. But if you are not a gambler, sign up for newsletter at icocountdown and also watch their blog where they do some good investigative journalism, pretty much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.icocountdown.com/&quot; class=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Homepage IcoCountdown.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@icocountdown/&quot; class=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Blog IcoCountdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;you-think-you-know-whats-ico&quot;&gt;You think you know what’s ICO&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You think you know what’s ICO, right? Initial coin offering, a way to crowdfund development of a new blockchain-based platform. Funds or social media support are provided in return for tokens that are sold out cheap in the presale so &lt;em&gt;speculators&lt;/em&gt; buy in hoping the token will eventually get dearer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well that is quite wrong my friend! Initial coin offering is actually more realistically an easy way for the project leaders to get rich and then let the project stall for whatever reason (governance issues, technical issues, political issues, personal issues) which can in turn serve as a good reason to open a new ICO for a fork of the stalled project (with better governance etc).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is easy to get the money off of people since tokens on ICOs are always speculative in value so anyone setting up an ICO for a vaporware token will get away with that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;so-is-it-a-good-idea-to-invest-in-an-ico&quot;&gt;So is it a good idea to invest in an ICO?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It might be a good idea in some cases - and that’s how many investors think about that: If the project turns out to be vapor and you didn’t go all in, it’s easy to write off a bunch of tokens that were actually very cheap and also a &lt;em&gt;small investment as a whole&lt;/em&gt;. If on the other hand the rare event should occur that the coin will get relatively expensive (like ETH) you might get a very &lt;em&gt;outsized profit&lt;/em&gt; which will also cover the losses - if you let the winner ride, which can be nerve wrecking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;some-research-is-needed-though&quot;&gt;Some research is needed though&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The way I described the ICO investment, it’s very similar to betting. That’s something to keep in mind - because in gamble it might be a good idea to bet on the jockey, not the horse: &lt;strong&gt;Google some information about the project leaders.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is usually fairly easy to find out if the leaders were previously related to a failed shitcoin in which case it might be a good idea to stay the fuck away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s see what’s still out there for the rest of 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;pending-icos-in-june-2016&quot;&gt;Pending ICOs in June 2016&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And let’s pick those kind of interesting. There are plenty more, you can invest directly at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.icostart.com/&quot;&gt;icostart.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;plutusin--get-plutons&quot;&gt;Plutus.in / Get Plutons&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;To Be Announced - June 2016&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plutus was on the radar since deep into last year already as a platform claiming to &lt;em&gt;not trying to change the paradigm&lt;/em&gt;, but rather &lt;em&gt;working with what’s out there&lt;/em&gt;. Next to all the shitcoins that are definitely the next big thing this sound incredibly sane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The use case, to keep it simple, is something like a proxy: You want to shop in a store that only accepts USD, you send a cryptocurrency equivalent to plutus and they will pay the goods for you via a virtual debit card.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The exchange/contract logic runs on Ethereum blockchain with plutons as tokens that can be used to get a rebate for using the platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question is if you are not better off simply with a virtual credit card of Advcash or Neteller - and you know many merchants don’t want to accept these anyway. But you see that it is not a complete bullshit. The crowdsale is yet to be announced, you can sign up for news on the homepage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://getplutons.plutus.it/&quot;&gt;Plutus ICO homepage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;icoo--initial-coin-offering-open-ledger&quot;&gt;ICOO / Initial Coin Offering Open Ledger&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Crowdsale On in June 2016&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Danish cryptocurrency platform, CCEDK, and OpenLedger have announced the crowdsale of its Initial Coin Offering OpenLedger (ICOO) crowdsale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ICOO crowdsale allows people to buy ICOO tokens with Bitcoin or any other currency supported on the CCEDK or OpenLedger platform. However, all the payments towards ICOO tokens, irrespective of the currency will be converted to Bitcoin to prevent loss of value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.icoo.io/&quot;&gt;ICOO has quite a lot of info about the project&lt;/a&gt;. If you want it more PR-style, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.newsbtc.com/2016/05/25/initial-coin-offering-openledger-icoo/&quot;&gt;try newsbtc.com&lt;/a&gt;. To see the Danish trading platform CCEDK &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ccedk.com/&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.openledger.info/&quot;&gt;Open Ledger is a transparent decentralized crypto exchange&lt;/a&gt; using OBITS as means of investing in digital assets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The ICOO’s tokens crowdsale details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Start Date: May 20th at 18:00 UTC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Duration: 42 days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conversion Schedule:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For the first 12 days: 1000 ICOO tokens for 1 bitcoin (BTC)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For the 15 subsequent days: 925 ICOO tokens for 1 bitcoin (BTC)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For the 10 successive days: 850 ICOO tokens for 1 bitcoin (BTC)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For the last 5 days: constant 775 ICOO tokens for 1 bitcoin (BTC)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;rise&quot;&gt;Rise&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Crowdsale On in June 2016 (close 24 June)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CAREFUL!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rise.vision/ico&quot;&gt;Rise ICO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rise looks like an ambitions project. However, Alex of &lt;a href=&quot;http://icocountdown.com&quot;&gt;icocountdown.com&lt;/a&gt; did the legwork of googling and &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@icocountdown/why-has-rise-been-delisted-from-icocountdown-com-2907e956d5a4#.g81o85j0g&quot;&gt;delisted Rise from his ICO-watching website&lt;/a&gt;. The founders already have a history of &lt;a href=&quot;http://cointelegraph.com/news/cloakcoin-we-had-to-do-everything-from-scratch-only-the-name-has-stuck&quot;&gt;CloakCoin&lt;/a&gt; and the testnet seems cranky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are still interested &lt;a href=&quot;https://rise.vision/blog/post/ico-terms&quot;&gt;here are the full ICO terms&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;elastic-project&quot;&gt;Elastic Project&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Crowdsale On in Summer 2016 (close 12 August)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elastic project is listed as an ICO, which it basically is, but not a speculative one. The project needs to be funded which is supposed to be done by means of donations. Donors however shouldn’t expect any profit: The tokens have no value other than accessing the software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;That is, do not expect any future rewards for your donation. Elastic Coins (XEL) have no value and should neither be considered as a storage of value nor as any kind of investment. Instead, the Elastic Coins (XEL) you receive are just an early access to the open source software that is created in the context of Elastic. That is, Elastic Coins (XEL) can be seen as the “cryptographic fuel” that is needed to submit work to the Elastic Network and/or perform transactions on the Elastic blockchain and so Elastic Coins (XEL) are a software product under Swiss law. Donating, to emphasize once again, just means supporting the development of an open source project and nothing else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.elastic.pro/donations&quot;&gt;Elastic.pro Donations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;cometcoin&quot;&gt;CometCoin&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Crowdsale On in June 2nd to 12th 2016&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A small coin that opens ICO to fund a small dev team. The only place it is ever mentioned is &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=1501173.0&quot;&gt;bitcointalk, very briefly&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cometcoin.com/cometcoin-ico&quot;&gt;CometCoin Home&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/ico-2016/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/ico-2016/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s Waves Platform</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/waves.jpeg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/waves.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Waves will be integrated in the new updated version of Mycelium wallet.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New altcoin will be added to Poloniex next week. Initial coin offering (ICO) ended on the first of June but if you want to ride some waves as trading of new coin opens, do follow this one - Waves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;####Waves - Quick Info&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is Waves: &lt;em&gt;Waves is a blockchain-based colored coins platform, which will allow for future decentralized value transfers all over the world. It connects the fiat world and cryptocurrencies.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ICO price per coin: &lt;em&gt;0.2 USD&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Total token supply: &lt;em&gt;100 Million&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Codebase: &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/wavesplatform&quot;&gt;https://github.com/wavesplatform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://wavesplatform.com/whitepaper_v0.pdf&quot;&gt;Whitepaper (link to PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TRADING STARTS: 14 JUNE 2016&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The whitepaper says that WAVES is a decentralized blockchain platform focusing on custom blockchain tokens operations. National currencies transfer is maintained on the WAVES blockchain through compliant gateway operators. Decentralized token exchange facilitates fundraising, crowdfunding, and trading of
financial instruments on the blockchain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In plain English, Waves is meant literally as p2p cash, taking into account different nations have different currencies and putting these on blockchain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is interesting idea but it should be noted that it is unclear how and if it will actually work in real world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;####Getting Waves as a Supporter Bounty&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Early supporters receive bounties for the following activities:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;200000 tokens reserved for following official WAVES account on Twitter.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;200000 tokens reserved for joining official WAVES Facebook group.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;100000 tokens reserved for translations and maintaining national WAVES threads.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;200000 tokens  reserved for subscribing to WAVES newsletter at wavesplatform.com website.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;300000 tokens reserved for signature campaign participants at Bitcointalk.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;####More info:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://slack.wavesplatform.com/&quot;&gt;Free to join Slack channel&lt;/a&gt; - wavesplatform.slack.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=1387944.0&quot;&gt;BitcoinTalk Thread&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.wavesplatform.com/&quot;&gt;Wavesplatform Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;####Press:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://bravenewcoin.com/news/the-new-mycelium-wallet-is-integrating-fiat-currencies-debit-cards-personal-finance-and-more/&quot;&gt;BraveNewCoin: The new Mycelium wallet is integrating fiat currencies, debit cards, personal finance, and more.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://themerkle.com/mycelium-wallet-will-support-fiat-tokens-through-waves/&quot;&gt;The Merkle: Mycelium Wallet Will Support Fiat Tokens Through Waves.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/waves/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/waves/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Technical Analysis in Altcoin Trading</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/ethereum.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/ethereum.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Ethereum has enough volume, technical analysis is justified.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s the &lt;strong&gt;best technical indicator&lt;/strong&gt; for an altcoin?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who knows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should be asking if &lt;strong&gt;technical analysis&lt;/strong&gt; will apply for your altcoin at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;In any case, markets are small and available leverage easy to get. In some cases, like with LTC or ETH, the leverage available is 20x or more. LTC is traded on Okcoin, ETH has futures on BitMEX. It’s easy to be a whale and manipulate the markets.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Usually, if a trend is good, some changes in volume should occure before a spike or chop. But volume indicators should only be applied above certain daily volume. Otherwise the market is too susceptible to manipulation.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;daily-volume&quot;&gt;Daily volume&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see volume for last 24 hours on &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinmarketcap.com/&quot;&gt;coinmarketcap.com&lt;/a&gt;. You should be looking at 100k USD and up if you want to use TA meaningfully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s not to say you shouldn’t trade anything else. It’s just that your everyday usual normal technical analysis won’t work there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take for instance Lisk and The DAO. Both these things were launching on Poloniex (and elsewhere) at close dates. In both cases there was ICO (initial coin offering) where people could buy the token with a discount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very similar situation but different sentiment. There was a lot of talking about DAOs in general (that they are pretty much nonsense). There was no such talk about LISK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though the long term value is questionable in both cases, people launched the trading with the sentiment “new playground for traders, upupupupup free money” in the case of Lisk and with the sentiment “where can I short it?” in the case of The DAO tokens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-to-look-for&quot;&gt;What to look for?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1/ News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read forums, slack chats, gitter chats, idiotic click baits in well-respected printed media etc. Forget about truth or justice. Buy the rumor, sell the news.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2/ Price&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set up price alarm. For altcoins it’s easy to do on mobile with app called TabTrader. It’s free. On desktop you can try cryptowat.ch and bitcoinwisdom.com. During rally though cryptowat.ch tends to lag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once there is a spike or chop in price, it’s generally good idea to trade it as it usually doesn’t end after the first leg. Unless it is a &lt;em&gt;head fake&lt;/em&gt;, a fake movement that will turn into big trend in the other direction. Look for price patterns, more on that in the resources section further down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indicators that will tell you if the altcoin has enough juice to carry on the movement it started are momentum indicators. They are all lagging though - based on past price only. Look for patterns and use indicators only for confirmations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3/ Volume&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, when the volume of the altcoin is good enough, you will see increase in buying volume before the price moves up or increased selling volume before the price drops. There are volume based indicators that follow just that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Bitcoinwisdom has &lt;a href=&quot;http://stockcharts.com/school/doku.php?id=chart_school:technical_indicators:chaikin_money_flow_cmf&quot;&gt;CMF - Chaikin money flow&lt;/a&gt; which is probably your best option.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Cryptowatch has &lt;a href=&quot;http://stockcharts.com/school/doku.php?id=chart_school:technical_indicators:on_balance_volume_obv&quot;&gt;OBV - on balance volume&lt;/a&gt;. To spot emerging trend on Cryptowatch you can also use &lt;a href=&quot;http://stockcharts.com/school/doku.php?id=chart_school:technical_indicators:aroon&quot;&gt;Aroon&lt;/a&gt; even though it’s a momentum indicator.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;resources-to-learn-technical-analysis&quot;&gt;Resources to learn technical analysis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…the good way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You won’t find here any resources that give explicit trading or investment advice. That’s not meant to be (just) the standard no investment advice disclaimer but for real - you should try and see what fits you and what’s the best way you can form decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;John Bollinger&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The creator of Bollinger bands is on twitter and sometimes posting crypto-related ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;de&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Thanks to all the Bitcoin folk who acknowledged my work! BTCUSD is a great vehicle for Bollinger Band analysis. Look at other pairs too.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; John Bollinger (@bbands) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/bbands/status/736226984322203648&quot;&gt;27. Mai 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is also a website called &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bollingeronbollingerbands.com/methods/?m=3&quot;&gt;Bollinger on Bollinger bands&lt;/a&gt; that is full of methods for signal recognition, typical patterns etc. But as the author says himself - try it out yourself and see what fits you. It’s a long read and a 90’s style website but it’s worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bollingeronbollingerbands.com/methods/?m=0&quot; class=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Bollinger on BBANDS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chart Patterns&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simple website not loaded with tons of graphics and ad trash. Just text and a couple of images showcasing chart patterns. Take a look at triangles and pennants if you want to look smart in crypto-trading chats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chartpatterns.com/&quot; class=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Chart Patterns&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Swing Trading Stocks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here it’s not so much about the nitty gritty of technical analysis and more about strategies and methods how to day trade. If you are looking to swing trading altcoins, or even any altcoin trading in shorter timespans, not holding long term - this one will be good for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.swing-trade-stocks.com/&quot; class=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Swing Trading Stocks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/technical-analysis/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/technical-analysis/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
