<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Altcoin Trading</title>
    <description>Altcoin Trading is the forex of cryptocurrencies, with bitcoin as the base currency.</description>
    <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.altcointrading.net/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 21:41:59 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 21:41:59 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>All about the DAO hack</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-3.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: DAOs have a critical vulnerability that can probably be removed only by a hard fork.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-dao-hack-simplified&quot;&gt;The DAO hack simplified&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great summary can be found on &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.erratasec.com/2016/06/etheriumdao-hack-similfied.html&quot;&gt;erratasec blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It starts with an explanation of what are smart contracts (the main purpose of the Ethereum platform) actually good for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Let’s say that we want to organize a small conference. We need 100 people to sign up and pay/deposit money, so we can rent a hotel and such. But if not enough people sign up by a certain date, then the deposits need to be refunded. With Ethereum, we can write in a JavaScript-like language to code up this contract. It’ll guarantee that everyone will get a ticket to the conference, or everyone will get their money refunded, depending on how many sign up.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main point is, this whole redistribution of payments that, depending on a condition, might or might not be returned to the people who paid them, is supposed to be made automatic. There is supposed to be no human overseeing it or interpreting the circumstances to help &lt;em&gt;someone in power&lt;/em&gt; decide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then the DAOs are explained, specifically how you &lt;em&gt;leave&lt;/em&gt; a DAO (not just TheDAO but any DAO). The issue here is to leave you need to create your own DAO if you have invested in a project that is still ongoing. Your &lt;em&gt;child DAO&lt;/em&gt; will receive the payout of your investment once the project is over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;When you want to leave the fund, you split from it. This includes your share of unspent Ethereum coins, but also tokens representing returns on investments you were part of, but which haven’t yet paid out. That’s why you “split” rather than “cash out”, you need your own DAO shard to track those investments until they pay out.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This DAO splitting is exactly where the hack occured&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;When a member exits the investment scheme, they call the function name splitDAO(). (…) The member will supply some of their own code with the transaction. Among the things that code will do is tell the DAO code how to transfer Ethereum coin. (…) [Another] issue is that Ethereum code is recursive. That means when a function is running, it may call itself a second time. The bug is that when splitDAO() is called, it will then call the recipients code to transfer Ethereum coin, after which the recipients code will call splitDAO() again before finishing. This causes the process to repeat itself, transferring more Ethereum coin, then calling splitDAO() again, which calls the hacker’s code, which calls splitDAO(), which calls the hacker’s code, and so on. The process will continue endlessly, until it drains all of TheDAO’s coin.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.erratasec.com/2016/06/etheriumdao-hack-similfied.html&quot;&gt;Ethereum/TheDAO hack simplified, erratasec.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see that the bug is inherent to DAO codebase and closely related to how Ethereum platform works. If this very basic code is not altered, all future DAOs are subject to this bug.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;stolen-money-recovery&quot;&gt;Stolen money recovery&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only way to &lt;em&gt;undo&lt;/em&gt; this is to rewind the blockchain to the state before the attack occured which has been seriously considered and which spooked all the non-ETH fanbois. It would undo not only the hack but also all the other transactions that occured in the meantime which means screwing over the few for the sake of an organization that is too big to fail, as the ErrataSec article points out. We know that from centralized banking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coindesk.com/ethereum-response-dao-kill/&quot;&gt;Why the Wrong Response to The DAO Attack Could Kill Ethereum, coindesk.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently the ongoing solution to this issue implemented by the developers was one that avoids the rewind: New child &lt;em&gt;whitehat&lt;/em&gt; DAO attacks were created with the purpose to attack the malicious DAO. The whitehad DAOs rolled out on the 21st of June while developers kept reassuring everybody the attacker cannot access the stolen funds for 27 days which is enough time to come up with a solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coindesk.com/ethereum-developers-draining-dao/&quot;&gt;Ethereum Developers Launch White Hat Counter-Attack on The DAO, coindesk.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This attempt to shake off the hacker failed. Since the whitehat DAOs needed capital to run, they started accepting donations. The person behind the initial hack also donated some ETH to the whitehat DAOs and is hence a shareholder, possibly planning to drain the whitehat DAOs as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-06-22T19:18:28.549Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethereum/comments/4p9z93/it_seems_attacker_just_targeted_the_whitehatdaos/d4j7ldn&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethereum/comments/4p9z93/it_seems_attacker_just_targeted_the_whitehatdaos/&quot;&gt;It seems attacker just targeted the WhiteHatDAOs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;current-ethereum-sentiment&quot;&gt;Current Ethereum Sentiment&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/screenshots/dao2.PNG&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/screenshots/dao2.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People on ETH trading subreddits feel that the dev team looks after them and have more confidence in ETH now than in BTC (with notoriously indecisive governance) - in spite of the fact ETH is fundamentally flawed and DAOs are subject to future fund drainings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/4p9ivx/im_dumping_all_my_btc_for_eth/&quot;&gt;I’m dumping all my BTC for ETH, /r/ethtrader&lt;/a&gt; with a screenshot full of unconfirmed bitcoin transactions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This goes hand in hand with the sentiment that is being created by the community voices, and that is that the DAO hack is good for Ethereum since it is only &lt;em&gt;pruning&lt;/em&gt;, similar to the shaking out of the weak hands during a run-up, where only the most faithful will prevail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-06-22T18:56:51.453Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/4p9ba2/important_announcement_recession_is_cancelled/d4j3dot&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/4p9ba2/important_announcement_recession_is_cancelled/&quot;&gt;Important announcement: Recession is cancelled, effective immediately&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For clarification, traders say that the weak hands are being shaken off when there is a bullish market that retraces significantly after a profit taking on a local top, forcing highly leveraged longs to market sell at a loss. That results in some more price drop where winners take it all, i.e. people with enough capital will take the advantage of - pardon my French - cheap coins and drive the price up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has nothing to do with pseudo-Christian faith in a leader/savior and putting money into a platform where they might be irreversibly lost while there are plenty of alternatives without this downside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consequently careful speculations occurred on /r/bitcoinmarkets considering manipulations from the side of wealthy ETH holders that need the ETH price to hike up to $30 once again before they cash out for good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-06-22T19:14:01.813Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4p8s1p/daily_discussion_wednesday_june_22_2016/d4ja4bb&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4p8s1p/daily_discussion_wednesday_june_22_2016/&quot;&gt;[Daily Discussion] Wednesday, June 22, 2016&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is probably worth mentioning that some people are just in for the penny stock chance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/screenshots/dao3.PNG&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/screenshots/dao3.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, officials are concerned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/screenshots/dao-reg.PNG&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/screenshots/dao-reg.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;some-more-reading&quot;&gt;Some more reading&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coindesk.com/the-dao-an-analysis-of-the-fallout/&quot;&gt;Coindesk DAO fail analysis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coindesk.com/the-dao-bitcoin-development/&quot;&gt;What Ethereum’s DAO Disaster Means for Bitcoin Development&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/dao-hack/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/dao-hack/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ETH is selling off...</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-6.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: The DAO funds stolen and panic kicks in.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this place will not be the first website you will open up today, bloodbath on many cryptomarkets today deserves some clarification.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en-gb&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;The DAO is being attacked, massive selloff &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/av0Wk1QuSN&quot;&gt;https://t.co/av0Wk1QuSN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; BitcoinTrading Tools (@TradingFanbois) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/TradingFanbois/status/743735739574214659&quot;&gt;17 June 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier on the 17 of June the &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=11921216&quot;&gt;news started spreading&lt;/a&gt; that someone is leeching on The DAO funds and shouldn’t be. While the real DAO holders were most likely still asleep, a massive ETH sell off started. Lisk, DAO and surprisingly BTC dropped too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;true&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-06-17T10:32:40.829Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4ohgj1/daily_discussion_friday_june_17_2016/d4ctgbt&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4ohgj1/daily_discussion_friday_june_17_2016/&quot;&gt;[Daily Discussion] Friday, June 17, 2016&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indeed everyone who was awake at the moment went to cash in on the ETHUSD and ETHBTC chop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/ethdown.jpeg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/ethdown.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That caused the Bitfinex ETH margin funding rates soar. People went off to Poloniex but their servers are not quite ready for this drama, good luck withdrawing your funds. Not even talking about Kraken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-06-17T10:46:28.399Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4ohgj1/daily_discussion_friday_june_17_2016/d4cspky&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4ohgj1/daily_discussion_friday_june_17_2016/&quot;&gt;[Daily Discussion] Friday, June 17, 2016&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More than usual, be careful about highly leveraged position - it’s mental round here, volatility is high and &lt;strong&gt;you might not make it to add margin in time&lt;/strong&gt; if the market moves against you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Someone rather naive in Poloniex trollbox said “The website is lagging as fuck, is this professional?”.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The charting services most of us tend to use are lagging too when the load is too much (cryptowat.ch particlarly). &lt;strong&gt;Most altcoin pairs are on tradingview.com these days&lt;/strong&gt;, go for charts over there.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bitfinex has a scheduled outage today. &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitfinex.statuspage.io/&quot;&gt;Subscribe to their Statuspage updates&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-17-06-2016/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-17-06-2016/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some more ICOs in 2016?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/icowatch.jpeg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/icowatch.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: In case you missed DAO, Lisk and Waves you might be firing up the search engines in the mighty state of FOMO. Well, there is not much to miss this year.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;ico-watching-services&quot;&gt;ICO Watching Services&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right first off: There are a few websites that gather information about ICOs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all you can go directlt to &lt;a href=&quot;http://icostart.com&quot;&gt;icostart.com&lt;/a&gt; and place random bets. But if you are not a gambler, sign up for newsletter at icocountdown and also watch their blog where they do some good investigative journalism, pretty much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.icocountdown.com/&quot; class=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Homepage IcoCountdown.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@icocountdown/&quot; class=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Blog IcoCountdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;you-think-you-know-whats-ico&quot;&gt;You think you know what’s ICO&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You think you know what’s ICO, right? Initial coin offering, a way to crowdfund development of a new blockchain-based platform. Funds or social media support are provided in return for tokens that are sold out cheap in the presale so &lt;em&gt;speculators&lt;/em&gt; buy in hoping the token will eventually get dearer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well that is quite wrong my friend! Initial coin offering is actually more realistically an easy way for the project leaders to get rich and then let the project stall for whatever reason (governance issues, technical issues, political issues, personal issues) which can in turn serve as a good reason to open a new ICO for a fork of the stalled project (with better governance etc).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is easy to get the money off of people since tokens on ICOs are always speculative in value so anyone setting up an ICO for a vaporware token will get away with that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;so-is-it-a-good-idea-to-invest-in-an-ico&quot;&gt;So is it a good idea to invest in an ICO?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It might be a good idea in some cases - and that’s how many investors think about that: If the project turns out to be vapor and you didn’t go all in, it’s easy to write off a bunch of tokens that were actually very cheap and also a &lt;em&gt;small investment as a whole&lt;/em&gt;. If on the other hand the rare event should occur that the coin will get relatively expensive (like ETH) you might get a very &lt;em&gt;outsized profit&lt;/em&gt; which will also cover the losses - if you let the winner ride, which can be nerve wrecking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;some-research-is-needed-though&quot;&gt;Some research is needed though&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The way I described the ICO investment, it’s very similar to betting. That’s something to keep in mind - because in gamble it might be a good idea to bet on the jockey, not the horse: &lt;strong&gt;Google some information about the project leaders.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is usually fairly easy to find out if the leaders were previously related to a failed shitcoin in which case it might be a good idea to stay the fuck away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s see what’s still out there for the rest of 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;pending-icos-in-june-2016&quot;&gt;Pending ICOs in June 2016&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And let’s pick those kind of interesting. There are plenty more, you can invest directly at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.icostart.com/&quot;&gt;icostart.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;plutusin--get-plutons&quot;&gt;Plutus.in / Get Plutons&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;To Be Announced - June 2016&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plutus was on the radar since deep into last year already as a platform claiming to &lt;em&gt;not trying to change the paradigm&lt;/em&gt;, but rather &lt;em&gt;working with what’s out there&lt;/em&gt;. Next to all the shitcoins that are definitely the next big thing this sound incredibly sane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The use case, to keep it simple, is something like a proxy: You want to shop in a store that only accepts USD, you send a cryptocurrency equivalent to plutus and they will pay the goods for you via a virtual debit card.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The exchange/contract logic runs on Ethereum blockchain with plutons as tokens that can be used to get a rebate for using the platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question is if you are not better off simply with a virtual credit card of Advcash or Neteller - and you know many merchants don’t want to accept these anyway. But you see that it is not a complete bullshit. The crowdsale is yet to be announced, you can sign up for news on the homepage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://getplutons.plutus.it/&quot;&gt;Plutus ICO homepage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;icoo--initial-coin-offering-open-ledger&quot;&gt;ICOO / Initial Coin Offering Open Ledger&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Crowdsale On in June 2016&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Danish cryptocurrency platform, CCEDK, and OpenLedger have announced the crowdsale of its Initial Coin Offering OpenLedger (ICOO) crowdsale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ICOO crowdsale allows people to buy ICOO tokens with Bitcoin or any other currency supported on the CCEDK or OpenLedger platform. However, all the payments towards ICOO tokens, irrespective of the currency will be converted to Bitcoin to prevent loss of value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.icoo.io/&quot;&gt;ICOO has quite a lot of info about the project&lt;/a&gt;. If you want it more PR-style, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.newsbtc.com/2016/05/25/initial-coin-offering-openledger-icoo/&quot;&gt;try newsbtc.com&lt;/a&gt;. To see the Danish trading platform CCEDK &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ccedk.com/&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.openledger.info/&quot;&gt;Open Ledger is a transparent decentralized crypto exchange&lt;/a&gt; using OBITS as means of investing in digital assets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The ICOO’s tokens crowdsale details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Start Date: May 20th at 18:00 UTC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Duration: 42 days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conversion Schedule:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For the first 12 days: 1000 ICOO tokens for 1 bitcoin (BTC)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For the 15 subsequent days: 925 ICOO tokens for 1 bitcoin (BTC)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For the 10 successive days: 850 ICOO tokens for 1 bitcoin (BTC)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For the last 5 days: constant 775 ICOO tokens for 1 bitcoin (BTC)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;rise&quot;&gt;Rise&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Crowdsale On in June 2016 (close 24 June)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CAREFUL!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rise.vision/ico&quot;&gt;Rise ICO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rise looks like an ambitions project. However, Alex of &lt;a href=&quot;http://icocountdown.com&quot;&gt;icocountdown.com&lt;/a&gt; did the legwork of googling and &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@icocountdown/why-has-rise-been-delisted-from-icocountdown-com-2907e956d5a4#.g81o85j0g&quot;&gt;delisted Rise from his ICO-watching website&lt;/a&gt;. The founders already have a history of &lt;a href=&quot;http://cointelegraph.com/news/cloakcoin-we-had-to-do-everything-from-scratch-only-the-name-has-stuck&quot;&gt;CloakCoin&lt;/a&gt; and the testnet seems cranky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are still interested &lt;a href=&quot;https://rise.vision/blog/post/ico-terms&quot;&gt;here are the full ICO terms&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;elastic-project&quot;&gt;Elastic Project&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Crowdsale On in Summer 2016 (close 12 August)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elastic project is listed as an ICO, which it basically is, but not a speculative one. The project needs to be funded which is supposed to be done by means of donations. Donors however shouldn’t expect any profit: The tokens have no value other than accessing the software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;That is, do not expect any future rewards for your donation. Elastic Coins (XEL) have no value and should neither be considered as a storage of value nor as any kind of investment. Instead, the Elastic Coins (XEL) you receive are just an early access to the open source software that is created in the context of Elastic. That is, Elastic Coins (XEL) can be seen as the “cryptographic fuel” that is needed to submit work to the Elastic Network and/or perform transactions on the Elastic blockchain and so Elastic Coins (XEL) are a software product under Swiss law. Donating, to emphasize once again, just means supporting the development of an open source project and nothing else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.elastic.pro/donations&quot;&gt;Elastic.pro Donations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;cometcoin&quot;&gt;CometCoin&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Crowdsale On in June 2nd to 12th 2016&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A small coin that opens ICO to fund a small dev team. The only place it is ever mentioned is &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=1501173.0&quot;&gt;bitcointalk, very briefly&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cometcoin.com/cometcoin-ico&quot;&gt;CometCoin Home&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/ico-2016/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/ico-2016/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s Waves Platform</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/waves.jpeg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/waves.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Waves will be integrated in the new updated version of Mycelium wallet.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New altcoin will be added to Poloniex next week. Initial coin offering (ICO) ended on the first of June but if you want to ride some waves as trading of new coin opens, do follow this one - Waves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;waves---quick-info&quot;&gt;Waves - Quick Info&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is Waves: &lt;em&gt;Waves is a blockchain-based colored coins platform, which will allow for future decentralized value transfers all over the world. It connects the fiat world and cryptocurrencies.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ICO price per coin: &lt;em&gt;0.2 USD&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Total token supply: &lt;em&gt;100 Million&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Codebase: &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/wavesplatform&quot;&gt;https://github.com/wavesplatform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://wavesplatform.com/whitepaper_v0.pdf&quot;&gt;Whitepaper (link to PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TRADING STARTS: 14 JUNE 2016&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The whitepaper says that WAVES is a decentralized blockchain platform focusing on custom blockchain tokens operations. National currencies transfer is maintained on the WAVES blockchain through compliant gateway operators. Decentralized token exchange facilitates fundraising, crowdfunding, and trading of
financial instruments on the blockchain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In plain English, Waves is meant literally as p2p cash, taking into account different nations have different currencies and putting these on blockchain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is interesting idea but it should be noted that it is unclear how and if it will actually work in real world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;getting-waves-as-a-supporter-bounty&quot;&gt;Getting Waves as a Supporter Bounty&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Early supporters receive bounties for the following activities:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;200000 tokens reserved for following official WAVES account on Twitter.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;200000 tokens reserved for joining official WAVES Facebook group.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;100000 tokens reserved for translations and maintaining national WAVES threads.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;200000 tokens  reserved for subscribing to WAVES newsletter at wavesplatform.com website.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;300000 tokens reserved for signature campaign participants at Bitcointalk.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;more-info&quot;&gt;More info:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://slack.wavesplatform.com/&quot;&gt;Free to join Slack channel&lt;/a&gt; - wavesplatform.slack.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=1387944.0&quot;&gt;BitcoinTalk Thread&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.wavesplatform.com/&quot;&gt;Wavesplatform Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;press&quot;&gt;Press:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://bravenewcoin.com/news/the-new-mycelium-wallet-is-integrating-fiat-currencies-debit-cards-personal-finance-and-more/&quot;&gt;BraveNewCoin: The new Mycelium wallet is integrating fiat currencies, debit cards, personal finance, and more.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://themerkle.com/mycelium-wallet-will-support-fiat-tokens-through-waves/&quot;&gt;The Merkle: Mycelium Wallet Will Support Fiat Tokens Through Waves.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/waves/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/waves/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Technical Analysis in Altcoin Trading</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/ethereum.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/ethereum.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Ethereum has enough volume, technical analysis is justified.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s the &lt;strong&gt;best technical indicator&lt;/strong&gt; for an altcoin?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who knows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should be asking if &lt;strong&gt;technical analysis&lt;/strong&gt; will apply for your altcoin at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;In any case, markets are small and available leverage easy to get. In some cases, like with LTC or ETH, the leverage available is 20x or more. LTC is traded on Okcoin, ETH has futures on BitMEX. It’s easy to be a whale and manipulate the markets.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Usually, if a trend is good, some changes in volume should occure before a spike or chop. But volume indicators should only be applied above certain daily volume. Otherwise the market is too susceptible to manipulation.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;daily-volume&quot;&gt;Daily volume&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see volume for last 24 hours on &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinmarketcap.com/&quot;&gt;coinmarketcap.com&lt;/a&gt;. You should be looking at 100k USD and up if you want to use TA meaningfully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s not to say you shouldn’t trade anything else. It’s just that your everyday usual normal technical analysis won’t work there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take for instance Lisk and The DAO. Both these things were launching on Poloniex (and elsewhere) at close dates. In both cases there was ICO (initial coin offering) where people could buy the token with a discount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very similar situation but different sentiment. There was a lot of talking about DAOs in general (that they are pretty much nonsense). There was no such talk about LISK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though the long term value is questionable in both cases, people launched the trading with the sentiment “new playground for traders, upupupupup free money” in the case of Lisk and with the sentiment “where can I short it?” in the case of The DAO tokens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-to-look-for&quot;&gt;What to look for?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1/ News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read forums, slack chats, gitter chats, idiotic click baits in well-respected printed media etc. Forget about truth or justice. Buy the rumor, sell the news.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2/ Price&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set up price alarm. For altcoins it’s easy to do on mobile with app called TabTrader. It’s free. On desktop you can try cryptowat.ch and bitcoinwisdom.com. During rally though cryptowat.ch tends to lag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once there is a spike or chop in price, it’s generally good idea to trade it as it usually doesn’t end after the first leg. Unless it is a &lt;em&gt;head fake&lt;/em&gt;, a fake movement that will turn into big trend in the other direction. Look for price patterns, more on that in the resources section further down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indicators that will tell you if the altcoin has enough juice to carry on the movement it started are momentum indicators. They are all lagging though - based on past price only. Look for patterns and use indicators only for confirmations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3/ Volume&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, when the volume of the altcoin is good enough, you will see increase in buying volume before the price moves up or increased selling volume before the price drops. There are volume based indicators that follow just that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Bitcoinwisdom has &lt;a href=&quot;http://stockcharts.com/school/doku.php?id=chart_school:technical_indicators:chaikin_money_flow_cmf&quot;&gt;CMF - Chaikin money flow&lt;/a&gt; which is probably your best option.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Cryptowatch has &lt;a href=&quot;http://stockcharts.com/school/doku.php?id=chart_school:technical_indicators:on_balance_volume_obv&quot;&gt;OBV - on balance volume&lt;/a&gt;. To spot emerging trend on Cryptowatch you can also use &lt;a href=&quot;http://stockcharts.com/school/doku.php?id=chart_school:technical_indicators:aroon&quot;&gt;Aroon&lt;/a&gt; even though it’s a momentum indicator.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;resources-to-learn-technical-analysis&quot;&gt;Resources to learn technical analysis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…the good way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You won’t find here any resources that give explicit trading or investment advice. That’s not meant to be (just) the standard no investment advice disclaimer but for real - you should try and see what fits you and what’s the best way you can form decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;John Bollinger&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The creator of Bollinger bands is on twitter and sometimes posting crypto-related ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;de&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Thanks to all the Bitcoin folk who acknowledged my work! BTCUSD is a great vehicle for Bollinger Band analysis. Look at other pairs too.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; John Bollinger (@bbands) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/bbands/status/736226984322203648&quot;&gt;27. Mai 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is also a website called &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bollingeronbollingerbands.com/methods/?m=3&quot;&gt;Bollinger on Bollinger bands&lt;/a&gt; that is full of methods for signal recognition, typical patterns etc. But as the author says himself - try it out yourself and see what fits you. It’s a long read and a 90’s style website but it’s worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bollingeronbollingerbands.com/methods/?m=0&quot; class=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Bollinger on BBANDS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chart Patterns&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simple website not loaded with tons of graphics and ad trash. Just text and a couple of images showcasing chart patterns. Take a look at triangles and pennants if you want to look smart in crypto-trading chats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chartpatterns.com/&quot; class=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Chart Patterns&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Swing Trading Stocks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here it’s not so much about the nitty gritty of technical analysis and more about strategies and methods how to day trade. If you are looking to swing trading altcoins, or even any altcoin trading in shorter timespans, not holding long term - this one will be good for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.swing-trade-stocks.com/&quot; class=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Swing Trading Stocks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/technical-analysis/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/technical-analysis/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ETH vs LISK</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-4.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: ETH vs LSK&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ethereum&quot;&gt;Ethereum&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/&quot;&gt;Homepage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ethereum&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ethereum.stackexchange.com/&quot;&gt;ETH StackExchange&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So you probably know the ETH. It’s tradable crypto-currency that isn’t scarce as bitcoin and is primarily supposed to be used as a token for blockchain apps. So even though if it technically isn’t meant to be a currency suitable for payments its fiat value can still be significant if it is used widely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Ethereum makes it easy for people to create their own decentralized apps and tokens for them - these tokens are also tradable.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Ethereum is also a platform for smart contracts. That is a contract that will hold a contributor’s money until any given date or goal is reached. Depending on the outcome, the funds will either be released to the project owners or safely returned back to the contributors. All of this is possible without requiring a centralized arbitrator, clearing house or having to trust anyone.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The last step of what is possible with Ethereum is creation of DAOs - decentralized autonomous applications.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ethereum is run by Ethereum foundation (Stiftung Ethereum), Zug, Switzerland. Unlike with bitcoin, ETH has enough of well paid developers to take care of the legwork. One of their main offices is in Berlin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The flagship decentralized autonomous organization &lt;em&gt;The DAO&lt;/em&gt; just pumped (and dumped) the ETH value, now the DAO tokens themselves will be traded at Poloniex. It is taking off at 28th of May.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Reminder: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/search?q=%24DAO&amp;amp;src=ctag&quot;&gt;$DAO&lt;/a&gt; will be available for trading on May 28th. We will announce when the market is live.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Poloniex Exchange (@Poloniex) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/736038608361132032&quot;&gt;May 27, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lisk&quot;&gt;Lisk&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;”Lisk is a next generation crypto-currency and decentralized application platform, written entirely in JavaScript.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://lisk.io&quot;&gt;Homepage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/LiskHQ/lisk&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Developers also call lisk the &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lisk.io/lisk-the-first-modular-crypto-currency-dd3e8df87613#.y5kr9jxnm&quot;&gt;”first modular crypto-currency”&lt;/a&gt;, leveraging the age old issue of bitcoin scalability that is still being discussed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lisk is supposed to be used for development of decentralized apps of which each one will have its own sidechain. Lisk only uses Javascript which is supposed to make it unique and easy to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s for the buzzwords. The reality is LISK is just a &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lisk.io/olivier-and-max-leave-crypti-to-establish-lisk-3fd60eb0808f#.4uuz8ur23&quot;&gt;fork of a failed altcoin, Crypti (XCR)&lt;/a&gt;. The lead developers left the Crypti project because of lack of efficient leadership and forked it to improve it. To finance that they had ICO (initial coin offering) that started in February.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/lisk.jpeg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/lisk.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In order to kick start our platform, i.e. pay for developers and marketing, we will hold an ICO starting 22nd February 2016, in which we will accept Bitcoin, Crypti and Ethereum. At this point we can only say that we will keep a constant conversion rate for your Crypti at 1300 satoshi per XCR. We feel this provides a fair value to your XCR and creates an escape route to a fresh project for the whole Crypti community. More details will be published soon.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ICO page is now offline (the ICO was up for 1 month) but the stats and data are available &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lisk.io/lisk-ico-statistics-ac36fbb94fe3#.88l7agnip&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
Total Amount  

BTC exchanged ~ 14,052 BTC
BTC bonus ~ 410 BTC
XCR exchanged ~ 78,242,600 XCR
Total equivalent ~ 15,480 BTC
Exchange rate ~ 0.0001821238671 BTC/LSK
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see that anyone who bought LSK in the ICO cashed in nicely. Poloniex started trading LSK at about 0.0004, during first three days the price saw 0.0012 and LSKBTC was the most traded pair. It was traded more than ETHBTC on Poloniex, until ETH started crashing hard that is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is the initial fad. All coins get pumped when they just start trading. But will the coin last?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can say that ETH is probably here to stay, at least for some forseeable future. It’s price is a different matter, and The DAO can fail hard. Meanwhile, LSK forum is jumping the shark.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/LiskHQ&quot;&gt;@LiskHQ&lt;/a&gt; forum has the usual tribalism. I am sure &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin&quot;&gt;@VitalikButerin&lt;/a&gt; is worried lol &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/gglZ0s6RzZ&quot;&gt;https://t.co/gglZ0s6RzZ&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/VYSRenFpwW&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/VYSRenFpwW&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Chris Ellis (@MrChrisEllis) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MrChrisEllis/status/735612073527382016&quot;&gt;May 25, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wouldn’t trust a German engineer more than a Russian geek. I know that many Germans would though, and truth or reason is not what governs the markets. It’s questionable though if these people are the people around cryptocurrencies or if they are too old or otherwise irrelevant to this space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;German geeks know about ETH. And not only geeks. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.welt.de/wirtschaft/webwelt/article153228987/Das-ist-der-neue-grosse-Rivale-des-Bitcoin.html&quot;&gt;Welt&lt;/a&gt; even called it the new great rival of BTC - which is something that would be called clickbait if it wasn’t a reputable German newspaper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another thing is that ETH also uses Javascript, &lt;a href=&quot;https://solidity.readthedocs.io/en/latest/&quot;&gt;sort of&lt;/a&gt;. It’s called Solidity and it’s a language very similar to JS. As far as blockchain apps are concern, Solidity should be better than JS. So if the usability is the fundament, LSK shouldn’t really be any better. Quite so the opposite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-problem&quot;&gt;The problem&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The issue with all this is that as of yet, all of it is &lt;em&gt;just words&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;ETH’s The DAO and slockit is a geek’s pipedream that wouldn’t survive without funding&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Lisk is just this new thing to play with on Poloniex.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In both cases, it’s just speculations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make some speculatory conclusions…ETH has quite a good tribe. Not to say I support them in particular but they’ve been through a lot. Lisk is neither first nor better, both from the tech and community point.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-vs-lisk/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-vs-lisk/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ethereum sentiment - Where to get reliable information?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/megathread.jpeg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/megathread.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: OMG Ether Ethereum ETH FOMO BTFD&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;where-to-get-quick-sentiment&quot;&gt;Where to get quick sentiment&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reddit has been the place for short term sentiment for quite some time now. It will be good place for you &lt;em&gt;if you are a trader&lt;/em&gt; looking to get BTC or fiat profit out of altcoin markets but &lt;em&gt;are not emotionally invested into an altcoin&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The trick is to see beyond PR/delusion. Quite a good way to do that is to avoid subreddits that focus on one altcoin in particular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It works because the times are gone that ETH and other coins were strictly banned from being mentioned in bitcoin threads. On the other hand, bitcoiners don’t buy into the &lt;em&gt;new paradigm bullshit&lt;/em&gt; all that much, so circlejerking and downright pump shill will still not survive. Comments on TA, price, fundamentals and similar will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets&quot;&gt;/r/bitcoinmarkets now has a weekly Altcoin megathread&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-05-24T21:46:03.246Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4kmayw/alt_cryptocurrencies_megathread/d3i5h1h&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4kmayw/alt_cryptocurrencies_megathread/&quot;&gt;[Alt Cryptocurrencies Megathread]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said, &lt;strong&gt;trollboxes&lt;/strong&gt; are probably the worst place to come for insight. If you want to read them, TradingView chat is about the &lt;em&gt;least bad&lt;/em&gt; place to do so. Please forget about Poloniex. Mods are doing their best but the flow in the trollbox is too fast and you won’t get away without seeing posts like “omg why vcash so cheap now” and the like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TradingView Charts: (You will see the trollbox when logged in - reg is free)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/chart/?symbol=POLONIEX%3AETHBTC&quot;&gt;Poloniex ETHBTC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/chart/?symbol=POLONIEX%3AXMRBTC&quot;&gt;Poloniex XMRBTC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will still get tons of shit technical analysis on TV, but the spam is not as massive as on Poloniex. Time and again someone will show up who also trades markets that you maybe weren’t thinking about at all and you might actually learn something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;read-blogs-but&quot;&gt;Read blogs but…&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…Keep in mind that blogging is a form of PR these days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t have enough information to make your own decisions, go and read different opinions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://sebfor.com/&quot;&gt;Ethereum News Website - Sebfor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/the-coinbase-blog/ethereum-is-the-forefront-of-digital-currency-5300298f6c75#.jbwf3mjft&quot;&gt;Coinbase blog is now very pro-ETH&lt;/a&gt; saying that basically, BTC is a legacy technology now and its fundamentals are out of the loop.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://telegram.me/joinchat/AyAwggbO-w_gl8xqPkiLuw&quot;&gt;Ethereum Trading Telegram Chat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Reddit’s reactions?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;“…also this screams like coinbase screaming for help.” &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4ks0u8/daily_discussion_tuesday_may_24_2016/d3i7mdj&quot;&gt;**&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;“Indeed Coinbase is screaming for help, after watching Bitcoin calcify into a Legacy technology. It’s a good thing that Ethereum is here to provide what Bitcoin cannot, and a good thing that Ehrsam is wise enough to see it’s time to move on.” &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4ks0u8/daily_discussion_tuesday_may_24_2016/d3i8327&quot;&gt;**&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been pretty much the sentiment lately that bitcoin won’t be &lt;em&gt;the next USD&lt;/em&gt;, it will be a good store of value though and great for gambling or other online activities. For decentralized apps though, there will be utility for altcoins. At the same time that doesn’t mean to jump all in into some of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It means there will be activity, and whatever might cause it, there will be profit to be taken. Naivity, morals and similar BS aside, you can still &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/pump-dump-know-signs-trading-altcoins/&quot;&gt;earn on pump and dump if you are careful&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://buytrezor.com?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wallets/trezor.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; title=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;non-trading-services-that-announced-eth-support&quot;&gt;Non-Trading Services that announced ETH support&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://buytrezor.com/?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;TREZOR the bitcoin wallet &lt;/a&gt; already supports altcoins, unlike Ledger wallet. They &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethereum/comments/4jsz9j/ethereum_support_coming_soon_to_trezor/&quot;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; they will now support ETH too.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://plutus.it/&quot;&gt;Plutus&lt;/a&gt; is now planning to feature &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/plutus/comments/4jw8j4/crowdsale_updates_pludao_eth_payment_option/&quot;&gt;Ethereum as a payment option&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
Dictionary
FOMO = fear of missing out
BTFD = buy the fucking dip
&lt;/pre&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/ethereum-may-2016/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/ethereum-may-2016/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Buy the rumor, sell the news</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As of 20th May 2016 it is no longer rumor! &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/4k47rq/coinbase_exchange_to_rebrand_following_launch_of/&quot;&gt;Coinbase is rebranding to GDAX and is launching Ethereum trading&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/coinbase/coinbase-eth.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/coinbase/coinbase-eth.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Coinbase API already responds to ETH queries.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is how the rumor started - bitcoin traders looking for a reason for the recent series of dips. There has been a speculation that traders get tired of the ever sideways non-eventness of BTCUSD, are dropping their positions and move funds into ETHBTC and ETHUSD to cash in on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://daohub.org&quot;&gt;DAO&lt;/a&gt; bubble. And there was loads of long positions in BTCUSD with the expectation of the halving which is believed to drive the price up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;de&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;So &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/coinbase&quot;&gt;@coinbase&lt;/a&gt; is adding &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;amp;src=ctag&quot;&gt;$ETH&lt;/a&gt;. Go to the exchange, click &amp;quot;My fees&amp;quot; and there it&amp;#39;s listed. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/CmvdvigcRE&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/CmvdvigcRE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; WhalePanda (@WhalePanda) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/WhalePanda/status/733194899265327104&quot;&gt;19. Mai 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either way, after a tweet with (real or fake?) screenshot from Coinbase featuring ETH appeared, people were looking to verify or deny this, and found out it is most likely real news since Coinbase API already responds to ETH queries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can try it yourself: &lt;a href=&quot;https://api.coinbase.com/v2/prices/buy?currency=ETH&quot;&gt;https://api.coinbase.com/v2/prices/buy?currency=ETH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/okcoin/okcoin-eth.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/okcoin/okcoin-eth.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There has been a similar rumor regarding OkCoin (The Place To Get Rekt&lt;sup&gt;TM&lt;/sup&gt;) last week. The story went also from people randomly querying the API for ETH. And while once it redirected all wrong requests to BTCUSD, ETH queries for some reson stopped doing that. At some point, a column featuring ETH balance started to show up and someone captured it &lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.is/Kd2VN&quot;&gt;on archive.is right here (scroll below the chart)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, so far it is all a rumor but indeed, if you went long on ETH as the DAO pump started, you might be a rich man by now. If you didn’t, don’t catch the knife now - the volatility will be wild now. Plenty of time to ride the waves. I can imagine &lt;a href=&quot;https://bestbitcoinexchange.co/leveraged-trading.html#some-numbers&quot;&gt;with OKCoin’s 20x leverage it will be a bloodbath&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;services-that-also-announced-eth-support&quot;&gt;Services that also announced ETH support&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://buytrezor.com/?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;TREZOR the bitcoin wallet &lt;/a&gt; already supports altcoins, unlike Ledger. They &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethereum/comments/4jsz9j/ethereum_support_coming_soon_to_trezor/&quot;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; they will now support ETH too.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://plutus.it/&quot;&gt;Plutus&lt;/a&gt; is now planning to feature &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/plutus/comments/4jw8j4/crowdsale_updates_pludao_eth_payment_option/&quot;&gt;Ethereum as a payment option&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://buytrezor.com?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wallets/trezor.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; title=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-okcoin-coinbase/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-okcoin-coinbase/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Buy and sell altcoins in one day</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/charts/xmr1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/charts/xmr1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: XMRBTC Chart - Cryptowat.ch&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So you are looking into daytrading with altcoins, basically. You want to buy an altcoin and sell it the same day for profit in bitcoin or fiat. Is that possible?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The answer is yes, indeed, but not if market moves rapidly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;go-for-less-profits&quot;&gt;Go for less profits&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to close your position as soon as possible and with profit, don’t look for huge profit from every single trade. You might find them by coincidence but don’t think twice before jumping into them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If you see a breakout on bitcoin markets, you check TA indicators and might decide to buy. Your order probably will fill and you will make it safely to your sell at the top.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If you see parabolic growth on altcoin markets chances are it was a single order pump or so. If you buy there might not be enough sellers if nobody trades long term with that particular altcoin (which depends). If you leave that order there it might first execute on the way back down.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the altcoin markets are simply not deep enough yet. If you are okay with holding that coin for a few months you might try things but remember that altcoin prices are very volatile. You will either go with your money in an altcoin stuck for a few months or you sell that altcoin and lose big.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daytrading is the legwork and it also means you don’t want to hold that altcoin.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;daytrading-example&quot;&gt;Daytrading example&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s see the title picture for illustration. It shows the recent altcoin crash that indeed also affected Monero. Monero started dropping with what looked like a single sell-off.
Opportunity for a daytrader?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monero has relatively mid to big trade volume and quite some stable audience. A daytrader should buy as low as possible right after the dip (that was at about 0.00275 BTC) and wait for correction. Correction topped at some 0.00321 BTC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Buy: 1 BTC, at 0.00275 ~ 362 XMR after fee 0.25%
Sell: 362 XMR, at 0.00321  ~ 1.16144 BTC after fee 0.25%
Profit ~ 16%
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;where-to-do-this&quot;&gt;Where to do this?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smaller alctoins&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You need a good altcoin exchange with real liquidity. That’s only &lt;a href=&quot;https://poloniex.com&quot;&gt;Poloniex&lt;/a&gt; these days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Poloniex is a full altcoin exchange, you won’t be able to withdraw cash directly though they do have tether. Tether is altcoin that is pegged to USD and linked to a bank account. To obtain a tether address one has to go through full identity verification. &lt;a href=&quot;https://tether.to&quot;&gt;More here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;A major drawback to Poloniex is that their website is not stable enough for the fact that everyone trades there. During major sales or volatility it &lt;em&gt;will be&lt;/em&gt; down or at least cranky.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For these cases it might be better to also have account on &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://bleutrade.com/sign_up/25600&quot;&gt;Bleutrade&lt;/a&gt;, a much smaller exchange that also trades many relatively unknown altcoins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from these two indeed, do have accounts on &lt;a href=&quot;https://btc-e.com&quot;&gt;BTC-e&lt;/a&gt; which also has some smaller coins like NMC or PPC. You can withdraw fiat on BTC-e - they support services like &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://perfectmoney.is/?ref=7622697&quot;&gt;PerfectMoney&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://perfectmoney.is/?ref=7622697&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Perfect Money&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/pm2.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Big names only&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are only interested in Ether trading, go for the classics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.bitfinex.com/?refcode=5egV78YtlC&quot;&gt;Bitfinex&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://kraken.com&quot;&gt;Kraken&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their volumes are best, for charts head over to &lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptowat.ch/&quot;&gt;Cryptowatch&lt;/a&gt;. These two will also let you withdraw fiat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/daytrading/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/daytrading/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Value of Altcoins: Money and Tokens</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/charts/ethdash.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/charts/ethdash.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: ETH-Dash chart (data from ShapeShift instant exchange, chart altcoinwisdom.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is it all about altcoins in 2016? It looks like a big thing starting out. Sure, markets are volatile and risky but in spite of that interesting things are on the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, to the altcoin value, apart from the fact that every altcoin is &lt;em&gt;new paradigm, totally&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;absolutely something new&lt;/em&gt;, there are two, well - actually three categories of altcoins out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;types-of-altcoins&quot;&gt;Types of altcoins&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;altcoins-as-money&quot;&gt;Altcoins as money&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some altcoins were developed as means of payment. You can usually tell from the coin’s name - like &lt;em&gt;Monero&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Digital Cash (DASH)&lt;/em&gt;. Litecoin was also developed primarily for payments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These altcoins usually solve one of the drawbacks of Bitcoin: the fact that Bitcoin is not anonymous, that scalability is not built in by default (see the current block size debate) or that there is still some sort of centralized governance needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trading money-altcoins is much like trading forex. It’s money, it’s a storage of value, a hedge - it is (if all is right) held and used by some people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interesting altcoins:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Monero&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scalable and mined in a decentralized fashion Monero also takes privacy into account: Payments are unlinkable, untraceable and anonymous. At the moment there is a Monero-based market on Poloniex along with the BTC-based one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;DASH&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dash is short for digital cash. The pivotal property of DASH is anonymous blockchain. No more block explorers. Another advantage is no governance and no way to link transactions together. DASH is currently traded heavily on Poloniex and Bittrex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Litecoin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Up until recently LTC was the second most popular altcoin. It was created to handle massive transaction volumes but, uh, whatever happened to it, nobody seems interested anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similar properties regarding volumes also has Nextcoin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;altcoins-as-tokens&quot;&gt;Altcoins as tokens&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some altcoins were developed with blockchain technology in mind. Anyone who wants to participate in whatever lives on whichever blockchain needs to have the appropriate token. That can be &lt;em&gt;Ether&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;MaidSafeCoin&lt;/em&gt;, for instance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is why Vitalik Buterin doesn’t endorse Ether as a value storage. It is not supposed to be money, it is supposed to be used to fuel certain type of apps. That is supposed to be it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why are these tokens speculated so much then? The answer is &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blue_Ocean_Strategy#Concept&quot;&gt;Blue ocean Strategy&lt;/a&gt;. Traders argue that Ether and other tokens are downplaying the monetary value of the coin on purpose: To show that it is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; just another “better money”. Tokens are a new category - something for which the demand is yet to be created. The value is expected to surge with the new demand. The demand will be by nature of the process focused on the token with no competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interesting altcoins:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MaidSafeCoin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MaidSafeCoin is a token for SAFE network. SAFE means Secure access for everyone, it is a distributed data management. All data is encrypted and cryptosigned by client. Computers storing data of SAFE network are mining credits ( ~ safecoins ) which are exchanged for goods and services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn more about the SAFE network &lt;a href=&quot;http://maidsafe.net/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ether &amp;amp; Co&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ether was heavily pumped, before which fanboys kept spamming bitcoin traders on Reddit claiming ETH is the new bitcoin. Now the interest is cooling down, there are no real massively popular Ethereum apps (Đapps) that would make the interest in Ether more than a pump/dump scheme for now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There in infinite amount of Ether to be mined but the inflation is only 1% a year. If the value of the coin gets stable it makes ETH a better value storage than traditional money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ethereum is the platform on which Ether is the token. It is a platform on which Đapps (decentralized apps) are supposed to live. These can be used to store data or smart contracts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other important tokens related to ETH:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/eth-vs-lisk/&quot;&gt;The DAO&lt;/a&gt; - Decentralized Autonomous Organization - and slock.it&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://dgx.io/#/&quot;&gt;Digix&lt;/a&gt; - Gold certificates&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ripple&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ripple is focused on smart contracts too. As a currency, its value is that of a bridge currency: All transaction across currencies can be instantaneous if every currency is liquid to Ripple and if exchange transactions are done through Ripple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;BitShares&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BitShares are one of the most interesting ideas in the altcoin space (click &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php?topic=7628.0&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for ELI5). The concept of BTS are shares in Decentralized Autonomous Companies (DACs). Anyone can become a “shareholder” of the first DAC by buying BitShares. The company’s work is then focused on revenue generation in form of bitUSD or whatever the company decides to call their profit unit. That is: the profit is generated in form of a “currency” pegged to USD. BTS (BitShares) can be thought of as a regular stock on a stock market&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;shitcoins&quot;&gt;Shitcoins&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last category are shitcoins. Coins that were created as an ego-blast of someone who could afford to pay the programmer and have no value proposition. If you check their websites you will see generic terms and buzzwords regarding issues that were already solved by many altcoins before, like&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Vcash was engineered to be innovative and forward-thinking. It prevents eavesdropping and censorship, promotes decentralized, energy efficient and instant network transactions.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.vanillacoin.net/&quot;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their value is purely speculative. They might pump and you might be coming early enough to cash in but that’s it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/value/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/value/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
