<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Altcoin Trading</title>
    <description>Altcoin Trading is the forex of cryptocurrencies, with bitcoin as the base currency.</description>
    <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.altcointrading.net/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 09:53:37 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 09:53:37 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s Waves Platform</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/waves.jpeg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/waves.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Waves will be integrated in the new updated version of Mycelium wallet.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New altcoin will be added to Poloniex next week. Initial coin offering (ICO) ended on the first of June but if you want to ride some waves as trading of new coin opens, do follow this one - Waves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;waves---quick-info&quot;&gt;Waves - Quick Info&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is Waves: &lt;em&gt;Waves is a blockchain-based colored coins platform, which will allow for future decentralized value transfers all over the world. It connects the fiat world and cryptocurrencies.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ICO price per coin: &lt;em&gt;0.2 USD&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Total token supply: &lt;em&gt;100 Million&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Codebase: &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/wavesplatform&quot;&gt;https://github.com/wavesplatform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://wavesplatform.com/whitepaper_v0.pdf&quot;&gt;Whitepaper (link to PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TRADING STARTS: 14 JUNE 2016&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The whitepaper says that WAVES is a decentralized blockchain platform focusing on custom blockchain tokens operations. National currencies transfer is maintained on the WAVES blockchain through compliant gateway operators. Decentralized token exchange facilitates fundraising, crowdfunding, and trading of
financial instruments on the blockchain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In plain English, Waves is meant literally as p2p cash, taking into account different nations have different currencies and putting these on blockchain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is interesting idea but it should be noted that it is unclear how and if it will actually work in real world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;getting-waves-as-a-supporter-bounty&quot;&gt;Getting Waves as a Supporter Bounty&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Early supporters receive bounties for the following activities:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;200000 tokens reserved for following official WAVES account on Twitter.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;200000 tokens reserved for joining official WAVES Facebook group.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;100000 tokens reserved for translations and maintaining national WAVES threads.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;200000 tokens  reserved for subscribing to WAVES newsletter at wavesplatform.com website.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;300000 tokens reserved for signature campaign participants at Bitcointalk.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;more-info&quot;&gt;More info:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://slack.wavesplatform.com/&quot;&gt;Free to join Slack channel&lt;/a&gt; - wavesplatform.slack.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=1387944.0&quot;&gt;BitcoinTalk Thread&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.wavesplatform.com/&quot;&gt;Wavesplatform Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;press&quot;&gt;Press:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://bravenewcoin.com/news/the-new-mycelium-wallet-is-integrating-fiat-currencies-debit-cards-personal-finance-and-more/&quot;&gt;BraveNewCoin: The new Mycelium wallet is integrating fiat currencies, debit cards, personal finance, and more.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://themerkle.com/mycelium-wallet-will-support-fiat-tokens-through-waves/&quot;&gt;The Merkle: Mycelium Wallet Will Support Fiat Tokens Through Waves.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/waves/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/waves/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Technical Analysis in Altcoin Trading</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/ethereum.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/ethereum.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Ethereum has enough volume, technical analysis is justified.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s the &lt;strong&gt;best technical indicator&lt;/strong&gt; for an altcoin?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who knows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should be asking if &lt;strong&gt;technical analysis&lt;/strong&gt; will apply for your altcoin at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;In any case, markets are small and available leverage easy to get. In some cases, like with LTC or ETH, the leverage available is 20x or more. LTC is traded on Okcoin, ETH has futures on BitMEX. It’s easy to be a whale and manipulate the markets.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Usually, if a trend is good, some changes in volume should occure before a spike or chop. But volume indicators should only be applied above certain daily volume. Otherwise the market is too susceptible to manipulation.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;daily-volume&quot;&gt;Daily volume&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see volume for last 24 hours on &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinmarketcap.com/&quot;&gt;coinmarketcap.com&lt;/a&gt;. You should be looking at 100k USD and up if you want to use TA meaningfully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s not to say you shouldn’t trade anything else. It’s just that your everyday usual normal technical analysis won’t work there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take for instance Lisk and The DAO. Both these things were launching on Poloniex (and elsewhere) at close dates. In both cases there was ICO (initial coin offering) where people could buy the token with a discount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very similar situation but different sentiment. There was a lot of talking about DAOs in general (that they are pretty much nonsense). There was no such talk about LISK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though the long term value is questionable in both cases, people launched the trading with the sentiment “new playground for traders, upupupupup free money” in the case of Lisk and with the sentiment “where can I short it?” in the case of The DAO tokens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-to-look-for&quot;&gt;What to look for?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1/ News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read forums, slack chats, gitter chats, idiotic click baits in well-respected printed media etc. Forget about truth or justice. Buy the rumor, sell the news.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2/ Price&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set up price alarm. For altcoins it’s easy to do on mobile with app called TabTrader. It’s free. On desktop you can try cryptowat.ch and bitcoinwisdom.com. During rally though cryptowat.ch tends to lag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once there is a spike or chop in price, it’s generally good idea to trade it as it usually doesn’t end after the first leg. Unless it is a &lt;em&gt;head fake&lt;/em&gt;, a fake movement that will turn into big trend in the other direction. Look for price patterns, more on that in the resources section further down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indicators that will tell you if the altcoin has enough juice to carry on the movement it started are momentum indicators. They are all lagging though - based on past price only. Look for patterns and use indicators only for confirmations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3/ Volume&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, when the volume of the altcoin is good enough, you will see increase in buying volume before the price moves up or increased selling volume before the price drops. There are volume based indicators that follow just that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Bitcoinwisdom has &lt;a href=&quot;http://stockcharts.com/school/doku.php?id=chart_school:technical_indicators:chaikin_money_flow_cmf&quot;&gt;CMF - Chaikin money flow&lt;/a&gt; which is probably your best option.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Cryptowatch has &lt;a href=&quot;http://stockcharts.com/school/doku.php?id=chart_school:technical_indicators:on_balance_volume_obv&quot;&gt;OBV - on balance volume&lt;/a&gt;. To spot emerging trend on Cryptowatch you can also use &lt;a href=&quot;http://stockcharts.com/school/doku.php?id=chart_school:technical_indicators:aroon&quot;&gt;Aroon&lt;/a&gt; even though it’s a momentum indicator.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;resources-to-learn-technical-analysis&quot;&gt;Resources to learn technical analysis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…the good way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You won’t find here any resources that give explicit trading or investment advice. That’s not meant to be (just) the standard no investment advice disclaimer but for real - you should try and see what fits you and what’s the best way you can form decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;John Bollinger&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The creator of Bollinger bands is on twitter and sometimes posting crypto-related ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;de&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Thanks to all the Bitcoin folk who acknowledged my work! BTCUSD is a great vehicle for Bollinger Band analysis. Look at other pairs too.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; John Bollinger (@bbands) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/bbands/status/736226984322203648&quot;&gt;27. Mai 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is also a website called &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bollingeronbollingerbands.com/methods/?m=3&quot;&gt;Bollinger on Bollinger bands&lt;/a&gt; that is full of methods for signal recognition, typical patterns etc. But as the author says himself - try it out yourself and see what fits you. It’s a long read and a 90’s style website but it’s worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bollingeronbollingerbands.com/methods/?m=0&quot; class=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Bollinger on BBANDS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chart Patterns&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simple website not loaded with tons of graphics and ad trash. Just text and a couple of images showcasing chart patterns. Take a look at triangles and pennants if you want to look smart in crypto-trading chats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chartpatterns.com/&quot; class=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Chart Patterns&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Swing Trading Stocks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here it’s not so much about the nitty gritty of technical analysis and more about strategies and methods how to day trade. If you are looking to swing trading altcoins, or even any altcoin trading in shorter timespans, not holding long term - this one will be good for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.swing-trade-stocks.com/&quot; class=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Swing Trading Stocks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/technical-analysis/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/technical-analysis/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ETH vs LISK</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-4.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: ETH vs LSK&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ethereum&quot;&gt;Ethereum&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/&quot;&gt;Homepage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ethereum&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ethereum.stackexchange.com/&quot;&gt;ETH StackExchange&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So you probably know the ETH. It’s tradable crypto-currency that isn’t scarce as bitcoin and is primarily supposed to be used as a token for blockchain apps. So even though if it technically isn’t meant to be a currency suitable for payments its fiat value can still be significant if it is used widely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Ethereum makes it easy for people to create their own decentralized apps and tokens for them - these tokens are also tradable.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Ethereum is also a platform for smart contracts. That is a contract that will hold a contributor’s money until any given date or goal is reached. Depending on the outcome, the funds will either be released to the project owners or safely returned back to the contributors. All of this is possible without requiring a centralized arbitrator, clearing house or having to trust anyone.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The last step of what is possible with Ethereum is creation of DAOs - decentralized autonomous applications.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ethereum is run by Ethereum foundation (Stiftung Ethereum), Zug, Switzerland. Unlike with bitcoin, ETH has enough of well paid developers to take care of the legwork. One of their main offices is in Berlin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The flagship decentralized autonomous organization &lt;em&gt;The DAO&lt;/em&gt; just pumped (and dumped) the ETH value, now the DAO tokens themselves will be traded at Poloniex. It is taking off at 28th of May.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Reminder: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/search?q=%24DAO&amp;amp;src=ctag&quot;&gt;$DAO&lt;/a&gt; will be available for trading on May 28th. We will announce when the market is live.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Poloniex Exchange (@Poloniex) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Poloniex/status/736038608361132032&quot;&gt;May 27, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lisk&quot;&gt;Lisk&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;”Lisk is a next generation crypto-currency and decentralized application platform, written entirely in JavaScript.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://lisk.io&quot;&gt;Homepage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/LiskHQ/lisk&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Developers also call lisk the &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lisk.io/lisk-the-first-modular-crypto-currency-dd3e8df87613#.y5kr9jxnm&quot;&gt;”first modular crypto-currency”&lt;/a&gt;, leveraging the age old issue of bitcoin scalability that is still being discussed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lisk is supposed to be used for development of decentralized apps of which each one will have its own sidechain. Lisk only uses Javascript which is supposed to make it unique and easy to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s for the buzzwords. The reality is LISK is just a &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lisk.io/olivier-and-max-leave-crypti-to-establish-lisk-3fd60eb0808f#.4uuz8ur23&quot;&gt;fork of a failed altcoin, Crypti (XCR)&lt;/a&gt;. The lead developers left the Crypti project because of lack of efficient leadership and forked it to improve it. To finance that they had ICO (initial coin offering) that started in February.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/lisk.jpeg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/lisk.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In order to kick start our platform, i.e. pay for developers and marketing, we will hold an ICO starting 22nd February 2016, in which we will accept Bitcoin, Crypti and Ethereum. At this point we can only say that we will keep a constant conversion rate for your Crypti at 1300 satoshi per XCR. We feel this provides a fair value to your XCR and creates an escape route to a fresh project for the whole Crypti community. More details will be published soon.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ICO page is now offline (the ICO was up for 1 month) but the stats and data are available &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lisk.io/lisk-ico-statistics-ac36fbb94fe3#.88l7agnip&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
Total Amount  

BTC exchanged ~ 14,052 BTC
BTC bonus ~ 410 BTC
XCR exchanged ~ 78,242,600 XCR
Total equivalent ~ 15,480 BTC
Exchange rate ~ 0.0001821238671 BTC/LSK
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see that anyone who bought LSK in the ICO cashed in nicely. Poloniex started trading LSK at about 0.0004, during first three days the price saw 0.0012 and LSKBTC was the most traded pair. It was traded more than ETHBTC on Poloniex, until ETH started crashing hard that is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is the initial fad. All coins get pumped when they just start trading. But will the coin last?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can say that ETH is probably here to stay, at least for some forseeable future. It’s price is a different matter, and The DAO can fail hard. Meanwhile, LSK forum is jumping the shark.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/LiskHQ&quot;&gt;@LiskHQ&lt;/a&gt; forum has the usual tribalism. I am sure &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin&quot;&gt;@VitalikButerin&lt;/a&gt; is worried lol &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/gglZ0s6RzZ&quot;&gt;https://t.co/gglZ0s6RzZ&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/VYSRenFpwW&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/VYSRenFpwW&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Chris Ellis (@MrChrisEllis) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MrChrisEllis/status/735612073527382016&quot;&gt;May 25, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wouldn’t trust a German engineer more than a Russian geek. I know that many Germans would though, and truth or reason is not what governs the markets. It’s questionable though if these people are the people around cryptocurrencies or if they are too old or otherwise irrelevant to this space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;German geeks know about ETH. And not only geeks. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.welt.de/wirtschaft/webwelt/article153228987/Das-ist-der-neue-grosse-Rivale-des-Bitcoin.html&quot;&gt;Welt&lt;/a&gt; even called it the new great rival of BTC - which is something that would be called clickbait if it wasn’t a reputable German newspaper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another thing is that ETH also uses Javascript, &lt;a href=&quot;https://solidity.readthedocs.io/en/latest/&quot;&gt;sort of&lt;/a&gt;. It’s called Solidity and it’s a language very similar to JS. As far as blockchain apps are concern, Solidity should be better than JS. So if the usability is the fundament, LSK shouldn’t really be any better. Quite so the opposite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-problem&quot;&gt;The problem&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The issue with all this is that as of yet, all of it is &lt;em&gt;just words&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;ETH’s The DAO and slockit is a geek’s pipedream that wouldn’t survive without funding&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Lisk is just this new thing to play with on Poloniex.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In both cases, it’s just speculations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make some speculatory conclusions…ETH has quite a good tribe. Not to say I support them in particular but they’ve been through a lot. Lisk is neither first nor better, both from the tech and community point.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-vs-lisk/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-vs-lisk/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ethereum sentiment - Where to get reliable information?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/megathread.jpeg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/megathread.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: OMG Ether Ethereum ETH FOMO BTFD&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;where-to-get-quick-sentiment&quot;&gt;Where to get quick sentiment&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reddit has been the place for short term sentiment for quite some time now. It will be good place for you &lt;em&gt;if you are a trader&lt;/em&gt; looking to get BTC or fiat profit out of altcoin markets but &lt;em&gt;are not emotionally invested into an altcoin&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The trick is to see beyond PR/delusion. Quite a good way to do that is to avoid subreddits that focus on one altcoin in particular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It works because the times are gone that ETH and other coins were strictly banned from being mentioned in bitcoin threads. On the other hand, bitcoiners don’t buy into the &lt;em&gt;new paradigm bullshit&lt;/em&gt; all that much, so circlejerking and downright pump shill will still not survive. Comments on TA, price, fundamentals and similar will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets&quot;&gt;/r/bitcoinmarkets now has a weekly Altcoin megathread&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-05-24T21:46:03.246Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4kmayw/alt_cryptocurrencies_megathread/d3i5h1h&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4kmayw/alt_cryptocurrencies_megathread/&quot;&gt;[Alt Cryptocurrencies Megathread]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said, &lt;strong&gt;trollboxes&lt;/strong&gt; are probably the worst place to come for insight. If you want to read them, TradingView chat is about the &lt;em&gt;least bad&lt;/em&gt; place to do so. Please forget about Poloniex. Mods are doing their best but the flow in the trollbox is too fast and you won’t get away without seeing posts like “omg why vcash so cheap now” and the like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TradingView Charts: (You will see the trollbox when logged in - reg is free)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/chart/?symbol=POLONIEX%3AETHBTC&quot;&gt;Poloniex ETHBTC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/chart/?symbol=POLONIEX%3AXMRBTC&quot;&gt;Poloniex XMRBTC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will still get tons of shit technical analysis on TV, but the spam is not as massive as on Poloniex. Time and again someone will show up who also trades markets that you maybe weren’t thinking about at all and you might actually learn something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;read-blogs-but&quot;&gt;Read blogs but…&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…Keep in mind that blogging is a form of PR these days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t have enough information to make your own decisions, go and read different opinions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://sebfor.com/&quot;&gt;Ethereum News Website - Sebfor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/the-coinbase-blog/ethereum-is-the-forefront-of-digital-currency-5300298f6c75#.jbwf3mjft&quot;&gt;Coinbase blog is now very pro-ETH&lt;/a&gt; saying that basically, BTC is a legacy technology now and its fundamentals are out of the loop.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://telegram.me/joinchat/AyAwggbO-w_gl8xqPkiLuw&quot;&gt;Ethereum Trading Telegram Chat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Reddit’s reactions?&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;“…also this screams like coinbase screaming for help.” &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4ks0u8/daily_discussion_tuesday_may_24_2016/d3i7mdj&quot;&gt;**&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;“Indeed Coinbase is screaming for help, after watching Bitcoin calcify into a Legacy technology. It’s a good thing that Ethereum is here to provide what Bitcoin cannot, and a good thing that Ehrsam is wise enough to see it’s time to move on.” &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4ks0u8/daily_discussion_tuesday_may_24_2016/d3i8327&quot;&gt;**&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been pretty much the sentiment lately that bitcoin won’t be &lt;em&gt;the next USD&lt;/em&gt;, it will be a good store of value though and great for gambling or other online activities. For decentralized apps though, there will be utility for altcoins. At the same time that doesn’t mean to jump all in into some of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It means there will be activity, and whatever might cause it, there will be profit to be taken. Naivity, morals and similar BS aside, you can still &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/pump-dump-know-signs-trading-altcoins/&quot;&gt;earn on pump and dump if you are careful&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://buytrezor.com?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wallets/trezor.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; title=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;non-trading-services-that-announced-eth-support&quot;&gt;Non-Trading Services that announced ETH support&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://buytrezor.com/?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;TREZOR the bitcoin wallet &lt;/a&gt; already supports altcoins, unlike Ledger wallet. They &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethereum/comments/4jsz9j/ethereum_support_coming_soon_to_trezor/&quot;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; they will now support ETH too.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://plutus.it/&quot;&gt;Plutus&lt;/a&gt; is now planning to feature &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/plutus/comments/4jw8j4/crowdsale_updates_pludao_eth_payment_option/&quot;&gt;Ethereum as a payment option&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
Dictionary
FOMO = fear of missing out
BTFD = buy the fucking dip
&lt;/pre&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/ethereum-may-2016/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/ethereum-may-2016/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Buy the rumor, sell the news</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As of 20th May 2016 it is no longer rumor! &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/4k47rq/coinbase_exchange_to_rebrand_following_launch_of/&quot;&gt;Coinbase is rebranding to GDAX and is launching Ethereum trading&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/coinbase/coinbase-eth.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/coinbase/coinbase-eth.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Coinbase API already responds to ETH queries.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is how the rumor started - bitcoin traders looking for a reason for the recent series of dips. There has been a speculation that traders get tired of the ever sideways non-eventness of BTCUSD, are dropping their positions and move funds into ETHBTC and ETHUSD to cash in on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://daohub.org&quot;&gt;DAO&lt;/a&gt; bubble. And there was loads of long positions in BTCUSD with the expectation of the halving which is believed to drive the price up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;de&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;So &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/coinbase&quot;&gt;@coinbase&lt;/a&gt; is adding &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;amp;src=ctag&quot;&gt;$ETH&lt;/a&gt;. Go to the exchange, click &amp;quot;My fees&amp;quot; and there it&amp;#39;s listed. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/CmvdvigcRE&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/CmvdvigcRE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; WhalePanda (@WhalePanda) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/WhalePanda/status/733194899265327104&quot;&gt;19. Mai 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either way, after a tweet with (real or fake?) screenshot from Coinbase featuring ETH appeared, people were looking to verify or deny this, and found out it is most likely real news since Coinbase API already responds to ETH queries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can try it yourself: &lt;a href=&quot;https://api.coinbase.com/v2/prices/buy?currency=ETH&quot;&gt;https://api.coinbase.com/v2/prices/buy?currency=ETH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/okcoin/okcoin-eth.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/okcoin/okcoin-eth.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There has been a similar rumor regarding OkCoin (The Place To Get Rekt&lt;sup&gt;TM&lt;/sup&gt;) last week. The story went also from people randomly querying the API for ETH. And while once it redirected all wrong requests to BTCUSD, ETH queries for some reson stopped doing that. At some point, a column featuring ETH balance started to show up and someone captured it &lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.is/Kd2VN&quot;&gt;on archive.is right here (scroll below the chart)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, so far it is all a rumor but indeed, if you went long on ETH as the DAO pump started, you might be a rich man by now. If you didn’t, don’t catch the knife now - the volatility will be wild now. Plenty of time to ride the waves. I can imagine &lt;a href=&quot;https://bestbitcoinexchange.co/leveraged-trading.html#some-numbers&quot;&gt;with OKCoin’s 20x leverage it will be a bloodbath&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;services-that-also-announced-eth-support&quot;&gt;Services that also announced ETH support&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://buytrezor.com/?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;TREZOR the bitcoin wallet &lt;/a&gt; already supports altcoins, unlike Ledger. They &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethereum/comments/4jsz9j/ethereum_support_coming_soon_to_trezor/&quot;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; they will now support ETH too.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://plutus.it/&quot;&gt;Plutus&lt;/a&gt; is now planning to feature &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/plutus/comments/4jw8j4/crowdsale_updates_pludao_eth_payment_option/&quot;&gt;Ethereum as a payment option&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://buytrezor.com?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wallets/trezor.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; title=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-okcoin-coinbase/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-okcoin-coinbase/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Buy and sell altcoins in one day</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/charts/xmr1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/charts/xmr1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: XMRBTC Chart - Cryptowat.ch&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So you are looking into daytrading with altcoins, basically. You want to buy an altcoin and sell it the same day for profit in bitcoin or fiat. Is that possible?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The answer is yes, indeed, but not if market moves rapidly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;go-for-less-profits&quot;&gt;Go for less profits&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to close your position as soon as possible and with profit, don’t look for huge profit from every single trade. You might find them by coincidence but don’t think twice before jumping into them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If you see a breakout on bitcoin markets, you check TA indicators and might decide to buy. Your order probably will fill and you will make it safely to your sell at the top.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If you see parabolic growth on altcoin markets chances are it was a single order pump or so. If you buy there might not be enough sellers if nobody trades long term with that particular altcoin (which depends). If you leave that order there it might first execute on the way back down.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the altcoin markets are simply not deep enough yet. If you are okay with holding that coin for a few months you might try things but remember that altcoin prices are very volatile. You will either go with your money in an altcoin stuck for a few months or you sell that altcoin and lose big.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daytrading is the legwork and it also means you don’t want to hold that altcoin.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;daytrading-example&quot;&gt;Daytrading example&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s see the title picture for illustration. It shows the recent altcoin crash that indeed also affected Monero. Monero started dropping with what looked like a single sell-off.
Opportunity for a daytrader?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monero has relatively mid to big trade volume and quite some stable audience. A daytrader should buy as low as possible right after the dip (that was at about 0.00275 BTC) and wait for correction. Correction topped at some 0.00321 BTC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Buy: 1 BTC, at 0.00275 ~ 362 XMR after fee 0.25%
Sell: 362 XMR, at 0.00321  ~ 1.16144 BTC after fee 0.25%
Profit ~ 16%
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;where-to-do-this&quot;&gt;Where to do this?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smaller alctoins&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You need a good altcoin exchange with real liquidity. That’s only &lt;a href=&quot;https://poloniex.com&quot;&gt;Poloniex&lt;/a&gt; these days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Poloniex is a full altcoin exchange, you won’t be able to withdraw cash directly though they do have tether. Tether is altcoin that is pegged to USD and linked to a bank account. To obtain a tether address one has to go through full identity verification. &lt;a href=&quot;https://tether.to&quot;&gt;More here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;A major drawback to Poloniex is that their website is not stable enough for the fact that everyone trades there. During major sales or volatility it &lt;em&gt;will be&lt;/em&gt; down or at least cranky.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For these cases it might be better to also have account on &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://bleutrade.com/sign_up/25600&quot;&gt;Bleutrade&lt;/a&gt;, a much smaller exchange that also trades many relatively unknown altcoins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from these two indeed, do have accounts on &lt;a href=&quot;https://btc-e.com&quot;&gt;BTC-e&lt;/a&gt; which also has some smaller coins like NMC or PPC. You can withdraw fiat on BTC-e - they support services like &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://perfectmoney.is/?ref=7622697&quot;&gt;PerfectMoney&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://perfectmoney.is/?ref=7622697&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Perfect Money&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/pm2.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Big names only&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are only interested in Ether trading, go for the classics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.bitfinex.com/?refcode=5egV78YtlC&quot;&gt;Bitfinex&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://kraken.com&quot;&gt;Kraken&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their volumes are best, for charts head over to &lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptowat.ch/&quot;&gt;Cryptowatch&lt;/a&gt;. These two will also let you withdraw fiat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/daytrading/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/daytrading/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Value of Altcoins: Money and Tokens</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/charts/ethdash.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/charts/ethdash.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: ETH-Dash chart (data from ShapeShift instant exchange, chart altcoinwisdom.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is it all about altcoins in 2016? It looks like a big thing starting out. Sure, markets are volatile and risky but in spite of that interesting things are on the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, to the altcoin value, apart from the fact that every altcoin is &lt;em&gt;new paradigm, totally&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;absolutely something new&lt;/em&gt;, there are two, well - actually three categories of altcoins out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;types-of-altcoins&quot;&gt;Types of altcoins&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;altcoins-as-money&quot;&gt;Altcoins as money&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some altcoins were developed as means of payment. You can usually tell from the coin’s name - like &lt;em&gt;Monero&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Digital Cash (DASH)&lt;/em&gt;. Litecoin was also developed primarily for payments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These altcoins usually solve one of the drawbacks of Bitcoin: the fact that Bitcoin is not anonymous, that scalability is not built in by default (see the current block size debate) or that there is still some sort of centralized governance needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trading money-altcoins is much like trading forex. It’s money, it’s a storage of value, a hedge - it is (if all is right) held and used by some people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interesting altcoins:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Monero&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scalable and mined in a decentralized fashion Monero also takes privacy into account: Payments are unlinkable, untraceable and anonymous. At the moment there is a Monero-based market on Poloniex along with the BTC-based one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;DASH&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dash is short for digital cash. The pivotal property of DASH is anonymous blockchain. No more block explorers. Another advantage is no governance and no way to link transactions together. DASH is currently traded heavily on Poloniex and Bittrex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Litecoin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Up until recently LTC was the second most popular altcoin. It was created to handle massive transaction volumes but, uh, whatever happened to it, nobody seems interested anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similar properties regarding volumes also has Nextcoin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;altcoins-as-tokens&quot;&gt;Altcoins as tokens&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some altcoins were developed with blockchain technology in mind. Anyone who wants to participate in whatever lives on whichever blockchain needs to have the appropriate token. That can be &lt;em&gt;Ether&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;MaidSafeCoin&lt;/em&gt;, for instance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is why Vitalik Buterin doesn’t endorse Ether as a value storage. It is not supposed to be money, it is supposed to be used to fuel certain type of apps. That is supposed to be it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why are these tokens speculated so much then? The answer is &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blue_Ocean_Strategy#Concept&quot;&gt;Blue ocean Strategy&lt;/a&gt;. Traders argue that Ether and other tokens are downplaying the monetary value of the coin on purpose: To show that it is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; just another “better money”. Tokens are a new category - something for which the demand is yet to be created. The value is expected to surge with the new demand. The demand will be by nature of the process focused on the token with no competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interesting altcoins:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MaidSafeCoin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MaidSafeCoin is a token for SAFE network. SAFE means Secure access for everyone, it is a distributed data management. All data is encrypted and cryptosigned by client. Computers storing data of SAFE network are mining credits ( ~ safecoins ) which are exchanged for goods and services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn more about the SAFE network &lt;a href=&quot;http://maidsafe.net/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ether &amp;amp; Co&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ether was heavily pumped, before which fanboys kept spamming bitcoin traders on Reddit claiming ETH is the new bitcoin. Now the interest is cooling down, there are no real massively popular Ethereum apps (Đapps) that would make the interest in Ether more than a pump/dump scheme for now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There in infinite amount of Ether to be mined but the inflation is only 1% a year. If the value of the coin gets stable it makes ETH a better value storage than traditional money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ethereum is the platform on which Ether is the token. It is a platform on which Đapps (decentralized apps) are supposed to live. These can be used to store data or smart contracts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other important tokens related to ETH:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/eth-vs-lisk/&quot;&gt;The DAO&lt;/a&gt; - Decentralized Autonomous Organization - and slock.it&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://dgx.io/#/&quot;&gt;Digix&lt;/a&gt; - Gold certificates&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ripple&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ripple is focused on smart contracts too. As a currency, its value is that of a bridge currency: All transaction across currencies can be instantaneous if every currency is liquid to Ripple and if exchange transactions are done through Ripple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;BitShares&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BitShares are one of the most interesting ideas in the altcoin space (click &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php?topic=7628.0&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for ELI5). The concept of BTS are shares in Decentralized Autonomous Companies (DACs). Anyone can become a “shareholder” of the first DAC by buying BitShares. The company’s work is then focused on revenue generation in form of bitUSD or whatever the company decides to call their profit unit. That is: the profit is generated in form of a “currency” pegged to USD. BTS (BitShares) can be thought of as a regular stock on a stock market&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;shitcoins&quot;&gt;Shitcoins&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last category are shitcoins. Coins that were created as an ego-blast of someone who could afford to pay the programmer and have no value proposition. If you check their websites you will see generic terms and buzzwords regarding issues that were already solved by many altcoins before, like&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Vcash was engineered to be innovative and forward-thinking. It prevents eavesdropping and censorship, promotes decentralized, energy efficient and instant network transactions.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.vanillacoin.net/&quot;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their value is purely speculative. They might pump and you might be coming early enough to cash in but that’s it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/value/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/value/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Earning More of a Coin: Interests and Lending</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/lending/poloniex-bot.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/lending/poloniex-bot.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Automatic bitcoin lending with Poloniex bot.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feeling &lt;em&gt;tilted&lt;/em&gt;? Seriously, because trading altcoins can sometimes feel more like gamble.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Putting all eggs in one basket can have very bad consequences but so can panic selling at every movement. Altcoins are volatile right now, if you are in an non-leveraged position you sometimes need to keep calm, hold on and wait for the price to get where you need it. For a day trader who is after fast profits this can be hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t feel like playing the coin game right now but you still want your money to earn something, keep reading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;poloniex-lending&quot;&gt;Poloniex lending&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s right, a nice way to earn daily interest rate on coins that you are not planning to risk at the moment. The lowest possible loan period is 2 days so don’t worry that your coins will sit somewhere for 2 months. They might but it’s not necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, the title says Poloniex. Bitfinex has the same system of margin funding as Poloniex - your money is provided by other users who placed a loan offer for a daily interest rate that was lower than the maximum IR you specified.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The difference for you as a lender is that Poloniex is altcoin exchange and people borrow tons of bitcoin. Bitfinex is a bitcoin exchange where people mostly want to borrow dollars. That’s why interest rate on Bitfinex can be as much as 50x lower than on Poloniex. You read that right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure thing more people are earning on Poloniex now which means you will need some unfair advantage, like a lending bot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;lending-bot-for-poloniex&quot;&gt;Lending bot for Poloniex&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well the very first thing is you want to set up an account on &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://poloniex.com&quot;&gt;Poloniex.com&lt;/a&gt;. Even if you have one already, it might be better to set up a new one for lending only. After all, with the lending bot you are having your API key and secret in a text file in plain text on your normal day-to-day computer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a second thing you need to transfer some bitcoin to Poloniex and as it comes, transfer it from exchange wallet to lending wallet. The lending bot will get your available lending balance and split it into smaller chunks that will be offered at a few different rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Installing the bot is really easy if you are on Linux. Just clone &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://github.com/Mikadily/poloniexlendingbot&quot;&gt;this Github repo&lt;/a&gt; and run the pythin script. If you are on Windows, &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://github.com/Mikadily/poloniexlendingbot/blob/master/README.md&quot;&gt;RTFM&lt;/a&gt;. It is a command line script and it doesn’t need a lot of resources, you can run it even from a pretty weak laptop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the first run the lending bot will ask you to edit a config file. Copypaste your API key and secret from &lt;em&gt;Settings &amp;gt; API keys&lt;/em&gt; on Poloniex. Further down in the file change the minimum acceptable daily interest rate, the default value is too low.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/lending/poloniex-bot.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/lending/poloniex-bot.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you start the bot it keeps waiting and calling the exchange every 60 seconds. If there is some money returned to your lending wallet it will attempt to lend them. It makes a lot of offers that are too high to be immediately filled you have to wait a few minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have much better chance to hit the spikes with the bot than by manually reloading the order book in web backend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/lending/taken.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/lending/taken.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can kill the bot once your money is borrowed. It only places the orders, you don’t have to keep it running at all times. Although it is better to keep the bot running because it will attempt to lend any money that returns into your lending wallet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-much-you-earn-on-bitcoin-lending&quot;&gt;How much you earn on bitcoin lending?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is quite a passive income but don’t expect too much unless you have a lot of coin to lend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nowadays quite a normal interest rate is around 0.3% daily. You will pick up some spikes but you cannot count on them. Also, you will probably switch off the bot some times and your money will not be provided at all times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daily interest on bitcoin loans of 0.3% will in ideal case give you about 9% monthly, which minus 15% Poloniex fee is some 7.65%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you (realistically) earn 5% netto per month, you still only earn 0.5 BTC on each 10 BTC you lend.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can lend out LTC and other coins too on Poloniex but expect much lower interest rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/lending/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/lending/</guid>
        
        <category>popular</category>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Altcoin Exchanges, Tried and True</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So you want to join the madness and start trading altoins?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s first look at what is important - what you should be looking for - and what you can leave behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You need:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Find a liquid exchange. Chinese exchanges are perfect for that, simply because of the number of Chinese.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Keep checking is &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/volume/24-hour/&quot;&gt;Coinmarketcap 24h volume&lt;/a&gt;. Different cryptocurrencies have different liquidity, go with the flow.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Keep in mind that smaller market means wilder changes, less predictability and high risk of bad losses.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Less important:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;AML/KYC for altcoin trading is still (luckily) an overkill in many places. Go with that.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Screw inhouse charts. Use &lt;a href=&quot;http://bitcoinwisdom.com&quot;&gt;Bitcoinwisdom.com&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://cryptowat.ch&quot;&gt;Cryptowat.ch&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cryptocoincharts.info&quot;&gt;Cryptocoincharts.info&lt;/a&gt;. Cryptowatch is best for altcoin trading and also actively maintained. It leaves quite some footprint in browsers though.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;altcoin-traders-from-the-us&quot;&gt;Altcoin traders from the US&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You probably know about the witch hunt. US traders have it always more difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use VPN at all times as a general security measure and it is fine with any of the following exchanges. Since ID verification is not usually a requirement when only cryptocurrencies are in play (and not fiat), you should be OK. For performance I can recommend &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://airvpn.org/?referred_by=209931&quot;&gt;AirVPN&lt;/a&gt; though I have also tried PureVPN and Hide My Ass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only thing worth mentioning is probably to distribute your bankroll on several exchanges. Don’t trade a lot of money on a single account if you don’t want to go through verification.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;best-altcoin-trading-liquidity&quot;&gt;Best Altcoin Trading Liquidity&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;chinese-exchanges-ltc&quot;&gt;Chinese Exchanges (LTC)&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/exchanges/okcoin-na.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/exchanges/okcoin-na.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chinese exchanges are good place to trade. Keep in mind that Chinese have more interest in coins due to their capital control. That means prices will usually be a bit above the western markets. If you find a way to arbitrage this, good on you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Typically though you will only be able to trade LTC pairs in China.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Policies: No AML/KYC paperwork necessary. Chinese traders say that international traders are never hassled, but sometimes traders with high balance are picked and asked to state their ID number or so. The trick is that you get asked for ID number (without verification) on sign up but as they lock your account and ask you, you cannot go and check. This is theor way to filter out frauds (and seize their coins).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also: When signing up you need to certify you are not from US, Indonesia or other restricted countries (they are specified in Terms).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.okcoin.com/&quot;&gt;OKCoin (China)&lt;/a&gt; needs 2-factor authentification.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinwisdom.com/markets/okcoin/ltccny&quot;&gt;LTCCNY Charts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://exchange.btcc.com/&quot;&gt;BTCC&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;BTCC has a &lt;a href=&quot;https://exchange.btcc.com/&quot;&gt;spot exchange&lt;/a&gt; and pro-exchange &lt;a href=&quot;https://pro.btcc.com/&quot;&gt;which is leveraged (up to 20x)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.btcc.com/fees&quot;&gt;Fees&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinwisdom.com/markets/btcchina/ltccny&quot;&gt;LTC / CNY Charts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.huobi.com/&quot;&gt;Huobi (China)&lt;/a&gt; needs a verified phone number.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Fee: 0.5% on withdrawal.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinwisdom.com/markets/huobi/ltccny&quot;&gt;LTC / CNY Charts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://perfectmoney.is/?ref=7622697&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Perfect Money&quot; src=&quot;/img/ads/pm2.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;poloniex-most-altcoins&quot;&gt;Poloniex (most altcoins)&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/exchanges/poloniex.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/exchanges/poloniex.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Definitely the best choice is you are looking to trade small altcoins, not only Litecoin. &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://poloniex.com/&quot;&gt;Poloniex&lt;/a&gt; has a lot of traders on ETH, DASH, DOGE, Monero and other markets. Exchange trading and margin (leveraged) trading available. Funds for margin are provided by other users - you can lend out your bitcoins to earn interest too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Policies:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://poloniex.com/terms/&quot;&gt;Poloniex is based in US but has restriction for US altcoin traders&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Verification is not really necessary. You need to state your name and country to get $2000 daily limit. Filling in your address and phone number gives you $7000 daily. The dollar limits are for illustration only - &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://poloniex.com/&quot;&gt;Poloniex&lt;/a&gt; only operates in cryptocurrencies.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Charts: &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://poloniex.com/&quot;&gt;Poloniex&lt;/a&gt; has awful charts. Use &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cryptocoincharts.info/pair/dash/btc/poloniex&quot;&gt;Cryptocoincharts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fees
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Trade: 0.15%/0.25% maker-taker.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Deposit: All crypto &lt;strong&gt;free&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Withdrawal: All crypto &lt;strong&gt;free&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobile trading: TabTrader. &lt;strong&gt;There is a “Poloniex app” for Android but it is fraudulent!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;other-big-names&quot;&gt;Other Big Names&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;bitfinex&quot;&gt;Bitfinex&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/exchanges/bitfinex.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/exchanges/bitfinex.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.bitfinex.com/?refcode=5egV78YtlC&quot;&gt;Bitfinex&lt;/a&gt; is based in HongKong, owned by JL van der Velde - CEO of iFinex Inc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.bitfinex.com/?refcode=5egV78YtlC&quot;&gt;Bitfinex&lt;/a&gt; bitcoin deposits and withdrawals go without verification. You need 6 confirmations to use the deposit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Liquidity: &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.bitfinex.com/?refcode=5egV78YtlC&quot;&gt;Bitfinex&lt;/a&gt; launched Ethereum market even though they are not ETH supporters. The market has been lively since, it is not a bad choice to go there if you are of all altcoins only interested in ETH.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.bitfinex.com/?refcode=5egV78YtlC&quot;&gt;Bitfinex&lt;/a&gt; also has a LTCBTC market but it is markedly smaller than the BTCUSD one: &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinmarketcap.com/exchanges/bitfinex/&quot;&gt;see on coinmarketcap&lt;/a&gt;.
  * Try &lt;a href=&quot;#btc-e&quot;&gt;BTC-e&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;#bit-x&quot;&gt;Bit-x&lt;/a&gt; for bigger LTCBTC markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Policies: Might require AML/KYC if you are from certain locations or trade a lot of money. So be careful and don’t put too much in one basket. Also, when they get hacked, they are not liable for losses.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Charts: Use Bitcoinwisdom &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinwisdom.com/markets/bitfinex/ltcbtc&quot;&gt;LTC / BTC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.bitfinex.com/pages/fees/?refcode=5egV78YtlC&quot;&gt;Fees&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Trade: Maker-Taker, 0.1%/0.2% below $500k monthly&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Deposit: Bitcoin, Litecoin &lt;strong&gt;free&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Withdrawal: Bitcoin, Litecoin &lt;strong&gt;free&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobile trading: Native app, TabTrader, zTrader&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Special offer - Sign up with &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.bitfinex.com/?refcode=5egV78YtlC&quot;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt; to get 10% discount on Bitfinex fees!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;btc-e-many-altcoins&quot;&gt;BTC-e (many altcoins)&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/exchanges/btce.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/exchanges/btce.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://btc-e.com&quot;&gt;BTC-e&lt;/a&gt; is most likely based in Russia but no official info is given. They are now the oldest exchange, operating since 2011 without scams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Policies: ID verification only for fiat deposits or withdrawal. To deposit an altcoin, trade it in any way, and withdraw more altcoin goes without verification.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The BTC-e exchange has no liability for losses. Have a 2FA, please.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The presently supported payment methods are:&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;US Bank Wire, EU Bank Wire (SEPA)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visa, Mastercard&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://perfectmoney.is/?ref=7622697&quot;&gt;PerfectMoney&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Liqpay.com, unikarta.com, WebCreds.com, Ukash.com, Webmoney.ru&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Good selection of lively altcoin markets involving coins like LTC, NVC, PPC and NMC. Markets are quite big.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Charts: Use Bitcoinwisdom.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://btc-e.com/page/2&quot;&gt;Fees&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Trade: Flat 0.2%&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Deposit: Any crypto for &lt;strong&gt;free&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Withdrawal: Any crypto has fee of &lt;strong&gt;0.001 coin&lt;/strong&gt; (quite high). Fees on fiat withdrawals change with method but generally are quite high compared to the industry levels.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobile trading: TabTrader&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;new-ish-places-but-tested-without-issues&quot;&gt;New-ish places but tested without issues&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;bittrex&quot;&gt;Bittrex&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/exchanges/bittrex.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/exchanges/bittrex.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://bittrex.com/&quot;&gt;Bittrex&lt;/a&gt; is exclusively altcoin exchange. Newish, but people trade &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cryptocoincharts.info/markets/show/bittrex&quot;&gt;dash and ether there&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Policies: Again - &lt;a href=&quot;https://bittrex.com/Home/Terms&quot;&gt;Based in US and has US restrictions&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;DO NOT keep untraded coins in&lt;/strong&gt;: Funds left on the account not moved for an unspecified period of time will be treated as unclaimed property.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Charts: Use &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cryptocoincharts.info/markets/show/bittrex&quot;&gt;cryptocoincharts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://bittrex.com/Fees#trading&quot;&gt;Fees&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Trade: 0.25% Flat&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobile trading: TabTrader&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;bit-x&quot;&gt;Bit-X&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/exchanges/bitx.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/exchanges/bitx.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://bit-x.com&quot;&gt;Bit-x&lt;/a&gt; only needs an unverified phone number. The only quite lively altcoin market is LTCBTC but don’t expect too much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They also offer a &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://bit-x.com&quot;&gt;virtual credit card (or a plastic one.)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Policies: They charge fee per open transaction (0,02%). You don’t get it back if you cancel the trade. In addition to this, there also are trade fees as normally.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Charts: Use &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinity.org/markets/bit-x/USD&quot;&gt;Bitcoinity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fees
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Trade: Flat 0.2%&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Deposit: Any crypto for &lt;strong&gt;free&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Withdrawal: Any crypto &lt;strong&gt;free&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobile trading: So far no app has them?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;to-keep-checking-low-volumes-for-now&quot;&gt;To keep checking (Low volumes for now)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;anxpro&quot;&gt;AnxPro&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/exchanges/anxpro.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/exchanges/anxpro.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://anxpro.com/&quot;&gt;Anxpro&lt;/a&gt; looks like a Forex platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks fine but doesn’t have enough liquidity yet - only some DOGE trades up until now (check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cryptocoincharts.info/markets/show/anxpro&quot;&gt;trade volume table at the bottom&lt;/a&gt;). Probably only worth checking out for now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Policies: No verification needed for altcoin trading without fiat movements. Users in US or prohibited countries will be banned if they use a VPN. There is no clear specification which countries these are.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Charts: Use &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cryptocoincharts.info/markets/show/anxpro&quot;&gt;Cryptocoincharts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fees
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Trade: Makers 0.3%, takers0.6%&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Deposit: All crypto &lt;strong&gt;free&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Withdrawal: All crypto &lt;strong&gt;free&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobile trading: TabTrader&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;who-has-problems&quot;&gt;Who has problems&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;YoBit.net - &lt;a href=&quot;http://siliconangle.com/blog/2016/02/28/problems-with-withdrawals-support-reported-at-bitcoin-altcoin-exchange-yobit/&quot;&gt;Probably short on coin, users have issues withdrawing.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;HitBTC - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/461rhm/a_warning_to_avoid_hitbtc/&quot;&gt;As for altcoins withdrawals seem fine, not in fiat though.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/altcoin-exchanges/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/altcoin-exchanges/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Altcoin Wallets</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/wallets/electrum.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/wallets/electrum.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Electrum wallet supports altcoins too.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You must be reading this all the time, but still: Never keep untrader coins on an exchange and never send coins from one exchange to another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;hardware-altcoin-wallets&quot;&gt;Hardware Altcoin Wallets&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to hold an altcoin that you think should grow in the future, you should get either wallet as a software or a hardware wallet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ledgerwallet.com/r/e274&quot;&gt;Ledger Wallet&lt;/a&gt; said they will not support any altcoins.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://buytrezor.com?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;Trezor&lt;/a&gt; on the other hand supports Electrum wallet which also has Dash and Litecoin integration. There is a full &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://buytrezor.com?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;Trezor&lt;/a&gt; integration now so you can hold bitcoins, litecoins and dash on a single &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://buytrezor.com?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;Trezor&lt;/a&gt; device.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://buytrezor.com?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wallets/trezor.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; title=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;electrum-for-litecoin&quot;&gt;Electrum for Litecoin&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get it &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://electrum-ltc.org/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; (official website). It is a regular Electrum wallet, still with the privacy flaw of being able to tell which pool of addresses belong to a single wallet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;electrum-for-dash&quot;&gt;Electrum for Dash&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another Electrum flavor is Dash wallet. You can get it from &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.dash.org/downloads&quot;&gt;Dash homepage&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;web-based-altcoin-wallets&quot;&gt;Web Based Altcoin Wallets&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For altcoin trading you will be best off with a multi-currency wallet. Go for &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.cryptonator.com/about&quot;&gt;Cryptonator&lt;/a&gt;. It can hold litecoins, dash, bitcoin and other coins. You will also be able to generate addresses as you go.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/altcoin-wallets/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/altcoin-wallets/</guid>
        
        <category>popular</category>
        
        
        <category>wallets</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
