<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Altcoin Trading</title>
    <description>Altcoin Trading is the forex of cryptocurrencies, with bitcoin as the base currency.</description>
    <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.altcointrading.net/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 02:40:27 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 02:40:27 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICONOMI</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://ico.iconomi.net/img/press/company/ICONOMI-logo-white.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://ico.iconomi.net/img/press/company/ICONOMI-logo-white.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Iconomi&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-is-iconomi&quot;&gt;What is ICONOMI&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ICO for ICONOMI is long gone yet the project is still well alive - in the altcoin space, this is a very good sign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;ICONOMI is creating the missing link between the old and the new economy. Speaking the language of the old economy and acting by the principles of the new one, ICONOMI’s transparent management will be provided by an EU legislation compliant and regulated service operator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ICONOMI is a digital assets management platform. If you want to invest into decentralised economy, the easiest way to create portfolio of preselected coins can be ICONOMI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-does-iconomi-work-with&quot;&gt;What does ICONOMI work with?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ICONOMI is written on Ethereum - it is a smart contract platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The platform was launched to alpha-testers by the end of 2016. Public launch was set to some time in 2017 to gain some time for fixes and improvements. &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/iconominet/iconomi-optimising-its-digital-assets-management-platform-before-the-public-launch-in-early-2017-5cf78c51776b#.avadakup0&quot;&gt;Read their blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;trading&quot;&gt;Trading&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Iconomi token trades as ICN. The token is tradable on several high profile exchanges - see &lt;a href=&quot;https://coinmarketcap.com/assets/iconomi/#markets&quot;&gt;coinmarketcap&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kraken	ICN/BTC&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kraken	ICN/ETH&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Liqui	ICN/BTC&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Gatecoin	ICN/BTC&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;EtherDelta	ICN/ETH&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;resources&quot;&gt;Resources&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=1587736.0&quot;&gt;Bitcointalk&lt;/a&gt; - This is the first ever post with all basic info. A lot of the info is related to the ICO that is now closed but it is still informative if you don’t know anything about ICONOMI.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/iconominet&quot;&gt;Medium&lt;/a&gt; - This is the official ICONOMI blog. Some of the posts will be quite technical. If you just want to follow the news, go for twitter.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/iconominet&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ICONOMI/&quot;&gt;Reddit&lt;/a&gt; - The ICONOMI subreddit is lively and active.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;scam-corner&quot;&gt;Scam corner&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/5pb4gv/real_iconomi_has_been_added_to_mercatox_fake_icn/&quot;&gt;22 Jan 2017 - Fake Iconomi tokens added to YoBit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ledgerwallet.com/r/e274&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Ledger Wallet protects your bitcoins&quot; src=&quot;https://www.ledgerwallet.com/images/promo/ledger-468x90-01.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/iconomi/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/iconomi/</guid>
        
        
        <category>coins</category>
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Monero - Where the heck are you supposed to cold-store it?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/monero-logo.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/monero-logo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: XMR wallet&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monero is undoubtedly one of the altcoins that cannot be called shitcoin: private and untracable, developers are responsive and not assholes just collecting money, setup is trustless, market cap grew insanely in 2016. Yet if you want to trade the coin the only hassle free way seems to be the dodgy setup of money on the exchange. Since the Bitfinex hack in August 2016 it has been a popular topic to joke whether thenext in line is Kraken or Poloniex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either way, if you trade Monero short term on spot or with leverage you can always cashout Bitcoin and store it in your Electrum or Mycelium wallet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What if you want to invest in Monero long term? You should not leave the coin on an exchange and forget about it for a couple of months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;lightweight-client-like-electrum-for-moneroeh&quot;&gt;Lightweight client like Electrum for Monero…Eh?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;reddit-card&quot; data-card-created=&quot;1483411736&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Monero/comments/4ghl0z/will_there_ever_be_a_lightweight_wallet_like/?ref=share&amp;amp;ref_source=embed&quot;&gt;Will there ever be a lightweight wallet (like Electrum) for Monero?&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reddit.com/r/Monero&quot;&gt;Monero&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//embed.redditmedia.com/widgets/platform.js&quot; charset=&quot;UTF-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every cryptotrader knows Electrum. It’s the lightweight wallet that is easy to use and doesn’t need you to download the full blockchain. There are integrations - Electrum for Litecoin and Dash (&lt;a href=&quot;/altcoin-wallets/&quot;&gt;see here&lt;/a&gt;). Unfortunately, nothing like this for Monero.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only alternative for Monero is software called LightWallet. It is not the same system as Electrum - it needs full node, the &lt;em&gt;light&lt;/em&gt; part is that the node runs somewhere else and the wallet connects to it from outside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words someone runs the node for you and will let your wallet to use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;true&quot; data-embed-uuid=&quot;61d47572-8d5f-448b-92bd-3ae43bd693f4&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2017-01-03T02:49:16.915Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Monero/comments/4ghl0z/will_there_ever_be_a_lightweight_wallet_like/d2hnur8/&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Monero/comments/4ghl0z/will_there_ever_be_a_lightweight_wallet_like/&quot;&gt;Will there ever be a lightweight wallet (like Electrum) for Monero?&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=903579.0&quot;&gt;Lightweight wallet&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jwinterm/LightWallet2/releases&quot;&gt;Releases on Github - exe for Windows and jar for Linux/Android/anything with java&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You need to have simplewallet and necessary dlls in the same folder as LightWallet to run the program - you will get these on the official download page at &lt;a href=&quot;https://getmonero.org/downloads/&quot;&gt;getmonero.com&lt;/a&gt;. Or, you know, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jwinterm/LightWallet2&quot;&gt;read the docs yourself&lt;/a&gt; actually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/wallets/xmr-lightwallet.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/wallets/xmr-lightwallet.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This client is your best bet if you want GUI and don’t want to store your coins with some third party web service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;full-node&quot;&gt;Full Node&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://getmonero.org/downloads/&quot;&gt;getmonero.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, if you don’t mind running the full node, on the main “Downloads” page there is a command-line wallet that comes with it. No GUI though - you need to use the command line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a beta release of Monero GUI as of 22 Dec 2016 - &lt;a href=&quot;https://getmonero.org/2016/12/22/monero-core-gui-beta-released.html&quot;&gt;see here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Monero/comments/5jr7r4/monero_core_gui_beta_1_released/&quot;&gt;Redditors are sofar excited&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;web-client&quot;&gt;Web Client&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mymonero.com/#/&quot;&gt;mymonero.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is something that is actually endorsed on the getmonero.com website unlike the LightWallet. MyMonero is website that will get you a Monero address, sign up pretty much takes one click. You click the one and only button on the landing page and in thenext step it is already showing you your private login key:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Below this you will find your thirteen word “Private Login Key”. Keeping this secure and private is very important, as it is the only way that you will be able to login to your MyMonero account. As we don’t store your private login key on the server there is no way to recover it if it is lost!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next step is already your web wallet, it doesn’t even want your email address:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/wallets/mymonero.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/wallets/mymonero.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pretty impressive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t want to use MyMonero for some reason, there are also multi-altcoin web wallets like &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.cryptonator.com/about&quot;&gt;Cryptonator&lt;/a&gt; but in this case I’d follow the XMR devs endorsement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jaxx-support&quot;&gt;Jaxx support&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The multi-altcoin wallet Jaxx announced they got &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinmagazine.com/articles/monero-coming-jaxx-wallets-including-ios-with-apple-s-blessing-1476224917/&quot;&gt;Apple’s blessing&lt;/a&gt; to include Monero in their iOS app available from Apple store. So far the Jaxx wallet only supports BTC, LTC, ETH, RSK and Dash while Dash is not available in the iOS version. Apple actually has a list of approved coins for the App store and Dash is not on the list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;hardware-wallets&quot;&gt;Hardware Wallets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a serious believer it would of course be ideal to have proper cold storage. However the present situation is still bleak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;trezor-hardware-wallet-and-monero&quot;&gt;Trezor hardware wallet and Monero&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Developer &lt;a href=&quot;https://forum.getmonero.org/4/academic-and-technical/2495/experimental-trezor-firmware-testing&quot;&gt;NoodleDoodle started thread on the official Monero forum&lt;/a&gt; documenting that he’s working on Trezor firmware that would support XMR. He kept the thread updated with new (experimental) releases up until December 2016 when the links to his Github repo went defunct. Alarmed Monero users started inquiring and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/TREZOR/comments/5ezhly/monero_with_trezor/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; is the response that was posted on Reddit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;NoodleDoodle’s experimental binaries are available &lt;a href=&quot;https://forum.getmonero.org/4/academic-and-technical/2495/experimental-trezor-firmware-testing&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, while his source code is no longer posted at github, but source code forks are referenced &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Monero/comments/5dnhgv/does_anyone_have_a_linkcopy_to_noodledoodles/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;strong&gt;The experimental V0313 simplewallet client supports the –hardware-wallet flag, i.e. ./simplewallet –hardware-wallet 0. This simplewallet command will cease to function about this time next year when implementation of CT functionality becomes mandatory.&lt;/strong&gt; This point about CT forced me to examine how well the experimental code supports wallet recovery from 25 Electrum mnemonic seed words synthesized from the 24 BIP 39 mnemonic seed words - used to typically restore a Trezor hardware wallet. No use in using a Trezor with an experimental Monero capability unless there is a “reliable” means to perform a software wallet restore when Monero CT becomes mandatory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I was unsuccessful carrying out the 25 Electrum seed word recovery unless the Trezor V0313 firmware was used with with no Trezor password (a plausible deniability rubber-hose password) that can complement the a Trezor’s connection PIN. For example, within the V0313 binary distributions there is a C++ ./trezorctl command, which is different from https://github.com/trezor/python-trezor/blob/master/trezorctl. Try a V0313
% ./trezorctl recover_mnemonic 0 “” English explain olympic caught soccer ethics retire outdoor giant deposit legal quarter cupboard radar silent palm ecology scrap adapt install bone warm clog fantasy language
Private key: f7a5feeec0bf87c4124c158d298388f3adf0009ad35cdbfcde4888a95ba8d200 Wallet address: 49y97TqN1yyHMPmHPWFt7aHkF9zpLdGV51Lsx8j7tEDuHw7kALtQVoWTyitz5qhcwADnPsg7fFKZs5XynjzDuTm134tRyyv Mnemonic: exult toenail snug dotted germs begun dual lettuce alpine enlist patio nutshell upon cuddled shocking gumball upgrade unfit glide camp sovereign neither smash snake lettuce&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;For the 24 word BIP 39 seed test vector above, I could only get a blank password (the empty quotes after the integer 0) to be used to reconstitute a Monero wallet that didn’t involve the Trezor hardware device using either simplewallet or monero-wallet-cli using the bolded mnemonic with the –restore-deterministic-wallet argument.
IMO, the Monero Trezor wallet capability is at a standstill unless some serious software development talent steps up to the plate an takes over were NoodleDoodle left off, or NoodleDoodle is incentivized to get the ball rolling again so hardware wallet vendors can perform tighter integrations with their existing frameworks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If memory serves me from postings, &lt;strong&gt;NoodleDoodle is more interested with trying to integrate Monero with Ledger or Keepkey hardware implementations 1st&lt;/strong&gt; before pressing forward with any other Trezor integrations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Another point worth noting is the &lt;strong&gt;current Monero Trezor implementation is not consistent with recommended BIP 32/39/44 test vector results&lt;/strong&gt; posted here that properly mimics Trezor password behaviors. Additionally, bitcoin-explorer (bx) commands also faithfully mimic Jaxx private/public keys and address synthesis abilities for a number of other altcoins. (Worth noting Jaxx doesn’t currently support BIP 39 passwords.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;As another example, using the same BIP 39 seed words above, and a rubber-hose password of 1234, here the results relevant to m/44/128/0 which IMO should correspond to ./simplewallet –hardware-wallet 0 to simplify integration with existing hardware wallets in general:
% echo “explain olympic caught soccer ethics retire outdoor giant deposit legal quarter cupboard radar silent palm ecology scrap adapt install bone warm clog fantasy language” | bx mnemonic-to-seed -p “1234” | bx hd-new | bx hd-private -d -i 44 | bx hd-private -d -i 128 | bx hd-private -d -i 0 | bx hd-to-ec | ./xmr
Seed : 0c0660372103343dc2c68cfd9cec0c4105b8c16d79b3fee2f9108162876e4a1f Private Spend Key : 1f326ada06a021e5eb29955abef22d2c05b8c16d79b3fee2f9108162876e4a0f Private View Key : beb076f8fa3e0c4508a111c683e85bde8776886d5654f15fede38b4f34c21b04 Public Spend Key : 932ab0238a1091443b1374f7d078ee4fc5a7797f9f1b1aaad54cda388a1e397a Public View Key : 8f6efc5e1187ea49ec2969fbdd4416d06d739ea0b2ef0aa2c394eeb04820c609 Monero Address : 47Ca9Q9pMEQCQvazCgp1oTELtaAHGB2CyVaJAzHZQbvQMVzKgU2FEdFDN9B3TeNChbbs1Ur8bnCdFUE1r7zpKc7X26Quv91 Electrum Seed Words : aspire argue upwards bias berries zero eldest anybody illness voyage fizzle laboratory sewage emit powder foyer sanity oyster vitals afloat igloo gleeful heels ivory oyster&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;FYSA - Monero kicked my butt for a while to determine how to write the ./xmr command above in C++.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words, the experimental Trezor firmware became obsolete before it stopped being experimental.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There already was a &lt;a href=&quot;https://forum.getmonero.org/9/work-in-progress/265/adding-monero-support-for-trezor?page=&amp;amp;noscroll=1#post-1520&quot;&gt;project to add Trezor support for Monero&lt;/a&gt; (even successfully funded!) in 2015 but it is marked as &lt;strong&gt;“Completed  -  Failed promises and broken dreams”&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://buytrezor.com?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wallets/trezor.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; title=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;ledger-the-hardware-wallet-and-monero&quot;&gt;Ledger the hardware wallet and Monero&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The Ledger Wallet already supports altcoins as long as they support BIP39 and BIP 32. However, a client application (the software wallet) is needed to communicate with the chip. Fork the Ledger Chrome app (https://github.com/LedgerHQ/ledger-wallet-chrome) and build support for the altcoin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://support.ledgerwallet.com/knowledge_base/topics/are-altcoin-supported-by-ledger-hardware-wallets&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ledgerwallet.com/r/e274&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Ledger Wallet protects your bitcoins&quot; src=&quot;https://www.ledgerwallet.com/images/promo/ledger-468x90-01.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, the problem is that as Monero keeps evolving the codebase is not stable enough to think about hardware implementations. The code gets obsolete before there is chance to properly test it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/monero-wallet/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/monero-wallet/</guid>
        
        
        <category>coins</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kraken opens Monero trading</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/TZi9xx6aiuY&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.kraken.com/post/155126375697/kraken-launches-monero-trading&quot;&gt;Link to Kraken’s blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Monero trading on Kraken opened on 2nd of January 2017&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;There is a hard fork on 9th or 10th of January 2017, deposits will be defunct shortly&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Available pairs: XMR/XBT, XMR/EUR, XMR/USD (all spot)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Margin trading coming soon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/monero-kraken/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/monero-kraken/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Finexening - Bitfinex hack</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/bitfinex/gox.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/bitfinex/gox.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Comparisons to MtGox is quite obvious.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are reading this bit chances are you didn’t miss all the drama. The best source of information is probably their status page at &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitfinex.statuspage.io&quot;&gt;bitfinex.statuspage.io&lt;/a&gt;, though the information is scarce. Sane Tackett /u/zanetackett is trying to keep the facade of the company and panic hasn’t kicked in but as for useful info he doesn’t provide much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://buytrezor.com?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wallets/trezor.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; title=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bad news for all ETH, ETC or LTC traders is that even though their assets were not affected by the hack, it seems they are lost too - just as USD assets, which were uneffected as well. The most likely outcome is some form socialized loss - a haircut - if it can be made in a legal way. The official statement however is still “we have not decided yet”. Most traders conclude it was actually quite expected after the spectacular 24h downtime couple of weeks earlier during wild price movements. Though Kraken fails like this too, repeatedly, and no hack occured as of yet - so take out of it what you like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the most important info you might have missed if you haven’t been lurking on Reddit since that not-so-much-black-swan event happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;update---recording-of-zane-tacketts-press-conference-on-teamspeak&quot;&gt;Update - Recording of Zane Tackett’s press conference on teamspeak&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;object width=&quot;148&quot; height=&quot;44&quot;&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;movie&quot; value=&quot;http://vocaroo.com/player.swf?playMediaID=s1TgZO1BXVZw&amp;amp;autoplay=0&quot; /&gt;&amp;lt;/param&amp;gt;&lt;param name=&quot;wmode&quot; value=&quot;transparent&quot; /&gt;&amp;lt;/param&amp;gt;&lt;embed src=&quot;http://vocaroo.com/player.swf?playMediaID=s1TgZO1BXVZw&amp;amp;autoplay=0&quot; width=&quot;148&quot; height=&quot;44&quot; wmode=&quot;transparent&quot; type=&quot;application/x-shockwave-flash&quot; /&gt;&amp;lt;/embed&amp;gt;&lt;/object&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://vocaroo.com&quot; style=&quot;font-size:xx-small;&quot; title=&quot;Vocaroo Voice Recorder&quot;&gt;Online recording software &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Yes, Bitfinex takes part in paying the missing money. All customers will get a haircut of 36%. The hack wasn’t done via logging into customers accounts. There will be a shitcoin released to pay for the 36% that will not be paid back right now. No details about the hack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;will-it-affect-the-general-trust-in-cryptocurrencies&quot;&gt;Will it affect the general trust in cryptocurrencies?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a lot of people who don’t really think so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en-gb&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Collectively, high-profile exchange hacks like MtGox and Bitfinex have set &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&quot;&gt;#Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt; back...&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; #BubbleMoku (@CarpeNoctom) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/CarpeNoctom/status/761502184571822080&quot;&gt;5 August 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After all Bitfinex was hacked, there is no flaw in any coin - but, if you are not actually able to safely trade anywhere, what is it for? This is a setback for all cryptos, and probably will be “solved” by bullshit regulations that will make crypto trading even more of a hassle with risks not really lowered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-uuid=&quot;f4695195-89c8-4417-8f22-089008d82f51&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-08-06T15:08:25.903Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4vtv1m/bitfinex_down_due_to_bitcoin_security_breach/d667ehe&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4vtv1m/bitfinex_down_due_to_bitcoin_security_breach/&quot;&gt;Bitfinex down due to bitcoin security breach&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ledgerwallet.com/r/e274&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Ledger Wallet protects your bitcoins&quot; src=&quot;https://www.ledgerwallet.com/images/promo/ledger-468x90-01.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;was-the-bitfinex-hack-an-inside-job&quot;&gt;Was the Bitfinex hack an inside job?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en-gb&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&quot;&gt;#Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/HackLeak?src=hash&quot;&gt;#HackLeak&lt;/a&gt; exposed.&lt;br /&gt;hypot. P2SH stats vs Futures &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/OKCoinBTC&quot;&gt;@OKCoinBTC&lt;/a&gt;, hack info = value.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HD: &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/CH4kErhTfs&quot;&gt;https://t.co/CH4kErhTfs&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/GI4nzBXQf7&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/GI4nzBXQf7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Beetcoin (@Beetcoin) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Beetcoin/status/761299853985058817&quot;&gt;4 August 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;can-we-learn-from-our-mistakes-for-the-next-time&quot;&gt;Can we learn from our mistakes for the next time?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some say it was plain as a yoghurt that Finex will be hacked: It had strange downtimes during busy times - but so do many exchanges. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4vtv1m/bitfinex_down_due_to_bitcoin_security_breach/d666nk6&quot;&gt;It was hosted on an AWS&lt;/a&gt; - every expert will cringe but Gemini also run on AWS and OKCoin International too. Ask the bot coders - they know where to put their codes to be in the same datacenter as the exchange. There is no exchange that would keep their own bare metal in a server room. Cost cutting wins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only thing we can do is to NEVER baghold or anything like that: Send money to exchange, do the trade, send them to Trezor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://buytrezor.com?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wallets/trezor.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; title=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;who-runs-bitfinex-anyway&quot;&gt;Who runs Bitfinex anyway?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-uuid=&quot;324f63fa-8a2d-4886-a9b7-fa6dbef79390&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-08-06T14:49:21.941Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4webkx/daily_discussion_saturday_august_06_2016/d66oeue&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4webkx/daily_discussion_saturday_august_06_2016/&quot;&gt;[Daily Discussion] Saturday, August 06, 2016&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bitfinex’s CEO is a Dutch man &lt;a href=&quot;https://bestbitcoinexchange.co/locations.html#asia&quot;&gt;Jean-Louis van der Velde&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/j-l-van-der-velde-26a24b6&quot;&gt;Here is his LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;. Their risk manager is also public on LinkedIn - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/giancarlo-devasini-2a564682?trk=pub-pbmap&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Their PR representative Zane Tackett is well known to anyone on Reddit - /u/zanetackett, loyal till his death and beyond. His boss is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/philip-potter-087495a6&quot;&gt;Phill Potter&lt;/a&gt;. However &lt;strong&gt;none of these people actually founded Bitfinex&lt;/strong&gt;. The platform was fonded by &lt;a href=&quot;https://fr.linkedin.com/in/raphaelnicolle/en&quot;&gt;a freelance sysadmin Raphael Nicolle&lt;/a&gt; with codebase from Bitcoinica, an exchange that was hacked back in the 2012.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;is-someone-liable-for-something-they-had-bitgo-which-is-insured&quot;&gt;Is someone liable for something? They had BitGo which is insured..?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The insurance doesn’t cover this hack. BitGo supplied Bitfinex with an implementation of segregated user-specific wallets to fill the regulatory requirements that were raised by futures regulatory commissions - margin swaps offered on finex were basically a futures product without the user specific wallets. However Bitfinex &lt;strong&gt;probably&lt;/strong&gt; had complete control over the BitGo implementation and turned off its security functions (like, limits on withdrawals).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-uuid=&quot;6d857b4d-0587-4229-8a58-2fb7b34eea5c&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-08-06T15:04:07.053Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4w2osg/daily_discussion_thursday_august_04_2016/d63n4rp&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4w2osg/daily_discussion_thursday_august_04_2016/&quot;&gt;[Daily Discussion] Thursday, August 04, 2016&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;USD funds for verified USA customers that came from US bank accounts should be insured via SynapsePay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;are-now-kraken-and-poloniex-coming-next&quot;&gt;Are now Kraken and Poloniex coming next?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kraken uses BitGo but with a different setup:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-uuid=&quot;2bc0682a-fae0-4c6b-9e30-b92fb66f5174&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-08-06T15:07:32.945Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4vw7ti/kraken_you_are_up_to_bat/d62kdih&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4vw7ti/kraken_you_are_up_to_bat/&quot;&gt;Kraken, you are up to bat.&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poloniex … Well, who knows anything about Poloniex, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;is-there-still-hope&quot;&gt;Is there still hope?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bitfinex will not pay for the losses of its customers. Bitstamp did, but the loss was smaller and they had VC funding. The only way a VC might want to flow into Bitfinex would probably be via an acquisition. If some other exchange with better security bought Finex they could essentially only buy the user base and their position. To simplify it, Finex accounts could carry on their existence on another platform with their pre-hack balance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bitfinex’s daily volume was known and it seems that a hack of this size wasn’t such a big hit really. It is unclear why Bitfinex people refuse to state their net BTC worth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-uuid=&quot;fdea13c4-49b9-4650-8d42-28a36418d318&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-08-06T15:11:12.669Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4vtv1m/bitfinex_down_due_to_bitcoin_security_breach/d666970&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4vtv1m/bitfinex_down_due_to_bitcoin_security_breach/&quot;&gt;Bitfinex down due to bitcoin security breach&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;places-to-watch&quot;&gt;Places to watch&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;stakepool teamspeak&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;reddit’s bitcoin markets&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;trading view cryptocurrency trollbox&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;/u/zanetackett with a big grain of salt&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;bitfinex.statuspage.io&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NOTE&lt;/strong&gt; There have been phishing emails from “ibitfinex.com”, these are fraudulent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-price-action-coming-from-this&quot;&gt;The price action coming from this?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because altcoins often mirror Bitcoin’s price action, do expect a wild ride until the dust settles…Which might take months. In an event like this all TA is probably worthless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There will be more shit to come once people realize Zane is a nice guy but all in all, not your family, and that blockchain companies are full of ex JP Morgan motherfuckers who are only going where the $$$ is and don’t give a shit about the people who actually make the existence of the business possible - the customers. And since folks with pedigrees are so networked each with another they will never lose a penny or reputation, effectively. We traders will, unless we protect our assets by a proper risk management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-uuid=&quot;d2b63219-1fca-4470-89f6-4ae4d2375cb6&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-08-06T15:21:08.578Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4webkx/daily_discussion_saturday_august_06_2016/d66p3hw&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4webkx/daily_discussion_saturday_august_06_2016/&quot;&gt;[Daily Discussion] Saturday, August 06, 2016&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/finexening/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/finexening/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to get free ETC out of thin air</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Small part of Ethereum community formed Ethereum Classic.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;https://gist.github.com/taoeffect/c910ebb16d9f6d248e9f1f3c6e10b1b8&quot;&gt;gist&lt;/a&gt; explains it all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;[…]At the moment it’s more like there are “1.25 Ethereum chains” because of the replay attacks, which are causing almost every transaction to get mirrored on the other chain. Replay attacks are possible because Ethereum’s hard fork did not take steps to make Ethereum transactions invalid on the original chain. Instead, all transactions are valid on both chains unless special smart contracts are used to distinguish between them (and most users probably aren’t doing this).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Send BTC to Coinbase
Transfer instantly that BTC to GDAX (Coinbase's fancy trading platform)
Trade BTC for ETH on GDAX
Transfer that ETH back to Coinbase
Transfer that ETH then to Poloniex (unclear whether skipping Step 4 and doing a direct transfer is possible)
Poloniex should &quot;credit&quot; you ETC for that ETH
Sell ETH and ETC for BTC
Send BTC back to Coinbase (repeat)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-uuid=&quot;702e8fcc-1caa-477e-9725-9b2f7645c5d3&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-07-29T04:24:40.540Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4uysor/daily_discussion_thursday_july_28_2016/d5v9dc5&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/4uysor/daily_discussion_thursday_july_28_2016/&quot;&gt;[Daily Discussion] Thursday, July 28, 2016&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/free-etc/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/free-etc/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ethereum Classic on Poloniex today, on Bitfinex soon</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-4.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Small part of Ethereum community formed Ethereum Classic.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;/eth-hard-fork/&quot;&gt;Ethereum hard fork&lt;/a&gt; on 20th of July went smoothly without any issues. All was received well by the community, both ETHBTC and ETHUSD price kept rising, DAO funds were recovered, attacker was left with nothing. So what happened?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/ethbtc-postfork.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/ethbtc-postfork.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://themerkle.com/the-ethereum-hard-fork-ethereum-classic/&quot;&gt;The Merkle&lt;/a&gt; puts it in a brief enough way:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;A small group within the Ethereum community has stayed on the old side of the fork with their own duplicate blockchain. This project is called Ethereum Classic and it promises to keep the ecosystem decentralized and free from censorship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This is a contradictory view to some, in the sense that Ethereum Classic has kept their own set of rules despite the consensus of the community, which is the exact opposite of what decentralized and censorship-free means. The project gained traction, none the less, with two mining pools dedicated to classic miners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, only four days after the hard fork, the first exchange is adding ETH Classic:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://themerkle.com/ethereum-classic-is-now-trading-on-poloniex/&quot;&gt;Ethereum Classic is now trading on Poloniex&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ETH Classic is the old blockchain, to be continued by people who don’t agree with recovering of the DAO stolen funds&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Trading of the Classic coin started on Poloniex on 24 July under the symbol ETC.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ETCBTC keeps low price after some wild initial pumping but volume is picking up (see below). At the time of writing ETCBTC costs 0.0014 while ETHBTC keeps at 0.0195 but sinking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/etcbtc.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/etcbtc.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zane Tackett, Bitfinex product manager, confirmed on /r/ethereum that ETHC will indeed be added soon:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-uuid=&quot;08749486-76d2-462e-aced-88ca08bdea5e&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-07-24T16:41:31.232Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethereum/comments/4uczsp/bitfinex_to_list_ethc_soon/d5opzjn&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethereum/comments/4uczsp/bitfinex_to_list_ethc_soon/&quot;&gt;Bitfinex to list $ETHC soon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-is-expected-from-a-traders-point-of-view&quot;&gt;What is expected from a trader’s point of view&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In spite of ETC being “the original” Ethereum it is not expected ETC will moon to the ETH levels any time soon.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Volume is great though, people might be buying in case it sticks.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;51% attack against ETC has been outed &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethereum/comments/4ucgia/i_am_chandler_guo_a_51_attack_on_ethereum_classic/?st=ir0ugc2w&amp;amp;sh=d12a2146&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ETC might be underpriced because traders are finding “free ETC” on their Poloniex accounts and selling them en masse. &lt;strong&gt;That’s the most important thing:&lt;/strong&gt; If you were holding ETH before the hard fork, you should be sitting on some ETC on Poloniex today. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/4ud74f/free_money_on_polo/?ref=share&amp;amp;ref_source=link&quot;&gt;Read here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;On the other hand, the ETC blockchain is not fit to be used for dApps anymore which makes it’s value only speculative at the moment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-classic/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-classic/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Value of Altcoins: Money and Tokens Reloaded</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/charts/ethdash.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/charts/ethdash.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: ETH-Dash chart (data from ShapeShift instant exchange, chart altcoinwisdom.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is it all about altcoins in 2016? It looks like a big thing starting out. Sure, markets are volatile and risky but in spite of that interesting things are on the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, to the altcoin value, apart from the fact that every altcoin is &lt;em&gt;new paradigm, totally&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;absolutely something new&lt;/em&gt;, there are two, well - actually three categories of altcoins out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;types-of-altcoins&quot;&gt;Types of altcoins&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;altcoins-as-means-of-payment&quot;&gt;Altcoins as means of payment&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some altcoins were developed as means of payment. You can usually tell from the coin’s name - like &lt;em&gt;Monero&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Digital Cash (DASH)&lt;/em&gt;. Litecoin was also developed primarily for payments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These altcoins usually solve one of the drawbacks of Bitcoin: the fact that Bitcoin is not anonymous, that scalability is not built in by default (see the current block size debate) or that there is still some sort of centralized governance needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trading money-altcoins is much like trading forex. It’s money, it’s a storage of value, a hedge - it is (if all is right) held and used by some people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interesting altcoins:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Monero&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scalable and mined in a decentralized fashion Monero also takes privacy into account: Payments are unlinkable, untraceable and anonymous. At the moment there is a Monero-based market on Poloniex along with the BTC-based one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;DASH&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dash is short for digital cash. The pivotal property of DASH is anonymous blockchain. No more block explorers. Another advantage is no governance and no way to link transactions together. DASH is currently traded heavily on Poloniex and Bittrex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Litecoin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Up until recently LTC was the second most popular altcoin. It was created to handle massive transaction volumes but, uh, whatever happened to it, nobody seems interested anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similar properties regarding volumes also has Nextcoin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;altcoins-as-tokens&quot;&gt;Altcoins as tokens&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some altcoins were developed with blockchain technology in mind. Anyone who wants to participate in whatever lives on whichever blockchain needs to have the appropriate token. That can be &lt;em&gt;Ether&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;MaidSafeCoin&lt;/em&gt;, for instance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is why Vitalik Buterin doesn’t endorse Ether as a value storage. It is not supposed to be money, it is supposed to be used to fuel certain type of apps. That is supposed to be it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why are these tokens speculated so much then? The answer is &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blue_Ocean_Strategy#Concept&quot;&gt;Blue ocean Strategy&lt;/a&gt;. Traders argue that Ether and other tokens are downplaying the monetary value of the coin on purpose: To show that it is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; just another “better money”. Tokens are a new category - something for which the demand is yet to be created. The value is expected to surge with the new demand. The demand will be by nature of the process focused on the token with no competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interesting altcoins:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MaidSafeCoin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MaidSafeCoin is a token for SAFE network. SAFE means Secure access for everyone, it is a distributed data management. All data is encrypted and cryptosigned by client. Computers storing data of SAFE network are mining credits ( ~ safecoins ) which are exchanged for goods and services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn more about the SAFE network &lt;a href=&quot;http://maidsafe.net/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ether &amp;amp; Co&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ether was heavily pumped, before which fanboys kept spamming bitcoin traders on Reddit claiming ETH is the new bitcoin. Now the interest is cooling down, there are no real massively popular Ethereum apps (Đapps) that would make the interest in Ether more than a pump/dump scheme for now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There in infinite amount of Ether to be mined but the inflation is only 1% a year. If the value of the coin gets stable it makes ETH a better value storage than traditional money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ethereum is the platform on which Ether is the token. It is a platform on which Đapps (decentralized apps) are supposed to live. These can be used to store data or smart contracts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other important tokens related to ETH:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/eth-vs-lisk/&quot;&gt;The DAO&lt;/a&gt; - Decentralized Autonomous Organization - and slock.it&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://dgx.io/#/&quot;&gt;Digix&lt;/a&gt; - Gold certificates&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ripple&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ripple is focused on smart contracts too. As a currency, its value is that of a bridge currency: All transaction across currencies can be instantaneous if every currency is liquid to Ripple and if exchange transactions are done through Ripple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;BitShares&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BitShares are one of the most interesting ideas in the altcoin space (click &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitsharestalk.org/index.php?topic=7628.0&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for ELI5). The concept of BTS are shares in Decentralized Autonomous Companies (DACs). Anyone can become a “shareholder” of the first DAC by buying BitShares. The company’s work is then focused on revenue generation in form of bitUSD or whatever the company decides to call their profit unit. That is: the profit is generated in form of a “currency” pegged to USD. BTS (BitShares) can be thought of as a regular stock on a stock market&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;List of “Smart Contract” Coins&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ETH&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;DAO&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;LISK&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MAID&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;del&gt;XRP / Codius&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;BURST&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;XCH&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;STEEM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some reading:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://changelly.com/blog/how-smart-contracts-work/&quot;&gt;How smart contracts work @changelly.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://steemit.com/lisk/@dan/why-lisk-is-inferior-to-ethereum&quot;&gt;Steem as a Smart Contract Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;shitcoins&quot;&gt;Shitcoins&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last category are shitcoins. Coins that were created as an ego-blast of someone who could afford to pay the programmer and have no value proposition. If you check their websites you will see generic terms and buzzwords regarding issues that were already solved by many altcoins before, like&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Vcash was engineered to be innovative and forward-thinking. It prevents eavesdropping and censorship, promotes decentralized, energy efficient and instant network transactions.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.vanillacoin.net/&quot;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their value is purely speculative. They might pump and you might be coming early enough to cash in but that’s it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/value/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/value/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Technical Analysis: Divergences</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/ta/bitfinex-divergences.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/ta/bitfinex-divergences.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Divergeces between lows or highs on the price action and the MACD can provide valuable signals.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;so-technical-analysis&quot;&gt;So, technical analysis?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technical analysis is something that newbie crypto-traders search for a lot while the sheer amount of resources is astounding. Often, the little Youtube channels are the best since they are managed by people who make living of trading and don’t have as much time to promote the Youtube channel - which is why most often you will not hear about them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TA Indicator: Divergences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is one channel maintained (occasionally) by a redditor /u/drwd. He does a series called “Better know an indicator” which already provided a very fine intro to the Ichimoku cloud for many traders. He made a good video on divergences (“divs”) that is worth looking at unless you are a seasoned trader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;700&quot; height=&quot;365&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/nGbqFV0koaQ&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Divergences in short&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Divergence happens when market price disagrees with indicators action. Divergence can be regular, hidden and exaggerated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Regular Div&lt;/em&gt; is a sign of trend reversal. Price keeps the trend but indicator already shows the reversal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Signal to short = the price makes higher high but MACD makes lower high. Underlying weakness, possible exhaustion of a bull trend.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Signal to long = the price makes lower low but MACD makes higher low. Underlying strength, possible exhaustion of bears.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hidden Div&lt;/em&gt; is a divergence that follows the trend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Signal to short = price makes lower highs but MACD makes higher highs. Tends to be found during a retracement up during a downtrend.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Signal to long = price makes higher low but MACD makes lower low. Tends to be found during a retracement in an uptrend.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Exaggerated Div&lt;/em&gt; is similar to regular div but price action makes double tops and double bottoms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/ta/divergences1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/ta/divergences1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The logic behind divergences is that sometimes the indicators shows hidden tendencies of the market (strength or weakness) that might not be visible from the price action yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not 100%, as always with technical analysis - the divergence can only inform you about a bias.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve read the list above it should be clear to you that you should first look at the bigger picture - are we in an uptrend or a downtrend? - and then start looking for divergences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you master them you can use them as a signal to enter or exit the market - they mark good spots for dip-buying and rally-selling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;good-to-read&quot;&gt;Good to read:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;”dukascopy.com / Do you know everything about divergences?” - The image above is taken from dukascopy.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dukascopy.com/fxcomm/fx-article-contest/?Do-You-Know-Everything-About=&amp;amp;action=read&amp;amp;id=890&quot; class=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Divs on dukascopy.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;”babypips.com / Divergence cheat sheet” - As images below. PRINT THEM!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.babypips.com/school/high-school/trading-divergences/divergence-cheat-sheet.html&quot; class=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Cheatsheet on babypips.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/ta/bp-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/ta/bp-2.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/ta-divergences/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/ta-divergences/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ethereum hard fork and your positions on exchanges</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-5.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;https://www.ethereum.org/images/assets/1900/Ethereum-homestead-background-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: ETH, the centralized mutable digital token.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The event that is by some pegged as the end of mETH as cryptocurrency is actually hapenning. The response to the DAO hack will, after all, be the hard fork. This is a solution that some say could have happened after the MtGox collaps during the first years of bitcoin, it didn’t happen though since it effectively undermines the most valuable asset of a blockchain based token - it’s immutability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-immutability-of-blockchain---its-not-a-dogma-folks&quot;&gt;The immutability of blockchain - It’s not a dogma, folks&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a misconception that blockchain is immutable by some kind of magic that has no way around it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The very simplistic explanation of blockchain immutability is the hash that is generated for each blockchain block mined. The hash contains among other data also a reference to the previous block’s hash - which contains a reference to the previous block’s hash, and so on. Because of this the blockchain is &lt;em&gt;internally consistent&lt;/em&gt;, there can be some checks run on this. If a block shows up that contains the wrong reference it will be disregarded as invalid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To create a tampered blockchain therefore needs to effectively rebuild the blockchain from the modified block on. This is something that is difficult and won’t occur with no one noticing it, nevertheless &lt;strong&gt;it is possible&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is presumably more difficult with bitcoin since the governance is (in spite of all tryings) still more decentralized. There was a hardfork on bitcoin blockchain once, during the very early stages of it when Satoshi Nakamoto was still the lead and also one of the very few people who actually knew bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ETH is far more widespread than BTC during the time it was forked, but it still revolves all about Vitalik Buterin and Ethereum Foundation. There are many other people on /r/ethereum or /r/ethtrader but if you’ve read them for a while you see they look up to their leaders a lot. It is even now relatively easy for them to just “give a green light” to a decision like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be fair, it should also be mentioned the ETH hard fork will not have the effect of erasing all transaction history to the point of the fork. (More on this in next paragraph.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitsonblocks.net/2016/02/29/a-gentle-introduction-to-immutability-of-blockchains/&quot;&gt;Read more - Immutability of blockchain on bitsonblocks.net.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-it-means-for-an-altcoin-trader&quot;&gt;What it means for an altcoin trader?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many speculations as to the USD and BTC value of Ether and TheDAO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.colony.io/why-a-post-hard-fork-ethereum-will-be-more-valuable-abc35bbf6e98#.2q2vd0xwo&quot;&gt;Here a TheDAO token holder argues post-hard fork ETH will be more valuable.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Unlike Bitcoin, an Ethereum hard fork will not involve a wholesale rollback of the blockchain state. It will involve only a surgical strike to convert theDAO to a withdrawal only contract, allowing theDAO tokens to be redeemed for Ether. That’s it. It will not effect any other transaction history or balances.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;~ This is a very good news since &lt;strong&gt;your positions on exchanges will not be affected&lt;/strong&gt;. There will be a brief period of instability during the actual fork. Because of this, exchanges will freeze withdrawals and deposits for a few hours but trading will carry on as usual. The hard fork will occur and a winnign blockchain will be chosen but all past transactions wil be transferred onto it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It is recommended to record your ETH positions - profits, losses, funding costs and maintenance margin - in case of a glitch on behalf of the exchange.&lt;/em&gt; Make a screenshot or write them on paper and check after the fork if all is OK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another smart argument that speculators will like to see is that ETH hard fork might be very well received by the general public. Forking a coin to mitigate a downside, a bailout effectively, is something most people like to see since it gives them a sense of security. Much like insurance and pension funds. It’s a fact that there are very few people who prefer to really take care of themselves, think through possible risks and manage them - while all this doesn’t make for a good reputation because it is something not quite common among people, making one unpredictable and un-see-through-able for others, which is frowned upon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the hard fork, it’s quite likely ETH will be seen as the legit digital token used for benevolent app development while bitcoin will be seen as the drug money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is quite ironic that a token that has security holes and nothing new about its governance (which is centralized) will come better off out of this but as for trading, there is no truth - the price action depends on if most traders share the same opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://buytrezor.com?a=fany@tutanota.com&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wallets/trezor.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; title=&quot;Trezor Wallet for bitcoins and altcoins&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;official-statements-of-exchanges&quot;&gt;Official statements of exchanges&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.ethereum.org/2016/07/15/to-fork-or-not-to-fork/&quot;&gt;Here is the official blog of Ethereum foundation.&lt;/a&gt; It’s more about the technical details if that’s what you are interested in.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://poloniex.com/press-releases/2016.07.15-Ethereum-Hard-Fork/&quot;&gt;Poloniex press release assures customers they don’t need to do anything.&lt;/a&gt; Deposits and withdrawals will be paused around the hard fork but all ETH balances will be automatically transferred to the winning blockchain.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bitfinex.com/posts/118&quot;&gt;Bitfinex also released an announcement, similar to Poloniex.&lt;/a&gt; If you have more questions you can try support or Reddit, where Bitfinex’s product manager resides at /u/zanetackett. He has already been talking about this - browse through his posts before asking. There will be status updates on &lt;a href=&quot;http://bitfinex.statuspage.io/&quot;&gt;http://bitfinex.statuspage.io/&lt;/a&gt; which you can subscribe via email.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;reddit-embed&quot; data-embed-media=&quot;www.redditmedia.com&quot; data-embed-parent=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-live=&quot;false&quot; data-embed-uuid=&quot;4122a9e5-b2f3-4e80-a502-cb17d6d176a6&quot; data-embed-created=&quot;2016-07-17T08:19:29.133Z&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/4sxxjf/daily_discussion_15jul2016/d5dp8nj&quot;&gt;Comment&lt;/a&gt; from discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/4sxxjf/daily_discussion_15jul2016/&quot;&gt;[Daily Discussion] - 15/Jul/2016&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-hard-fork/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/eth-hard-fork/</guid>
        
        
        <category>coins</category>
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bitcoin and Altcoin Trading with the Ichimoku Cloud</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/bitfinex_ichimoku.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/bitfinex_ichimoku.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Ethereum has enough volume, technical analysis is justified.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ichimoku cloud is the mysterious indicator available on &lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptowat.ch/&quot;&gt;cryptowat.ch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://stockcharts.com/school/doku.php?id=chart_school:technical_indicators:ichimoku_cloud&quot;&gt;Stockcharts on Ichimoku cloud&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Ichimoku Kinko Hyo translates into “one look equilibrium chart”. With one look, chartists can identify the trend and look for potential signals within that trend. The indicator was developed by Goichi Hosoda, a journalist, and published in his 1969 book. Even though the Ichimoku Cloud may seem complicated when viewed on the price chart, it is really a straight forward indicator that is very usable. It was, after all, created by a journalist, not a rocket scientist!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;lines-on-ichimoku-cloud-explained-like-youre-five&quot;&gt;Lines on Ichimoku cloud explained like you’re five&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/bitfinex_ichimoku_leg.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/bitfinex_ichimoku_leg.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ichimoku cloud uses past action of the market to predict future most likely direction along with support and resistance lines.
It is calculated from past EMAs and highs vs lows, among other things, &lt;a href=&quot;http://stockcharts.com/school/doku.php?id=chart_school:technical_indicators:ichimoku_cloud&quot;&gt;here’s more if you need to know&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The number of lines is confusing but here’s the basic info you need to know:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Senkou span are the borders of the (here) green cloud. It is green in this case as the market is bullish. It will be red in bearish markets. The space between the lines is called kumo. Senkou spans are major support/resistance lines - people set their stop orders on them because once the trend breaks through both of them, a reversal should come.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kinjun and Tenken lines are “balance” lines - &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.babypips.com/school/elementary/moving-averages/moving-average-crossover-trading.html&quot;&gt;fast and slow EMAs&lt;/a&gt;. If the price keeps around them, it is not overhyped nor underpriced. If it gets distant it is changing direction way faster than it “should” and a pullback is likely. In such a case, people set stop-loss orders around the lines if they are in a position and don’t want to take profits until necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Chinkou line is a lagging indicator. You can use it to confirm a trend.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video Intro into Ichimoku Cloud from Youtube by @CarpeNoctom&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;700&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/J3t2Tsn_Imk&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BASICS: Ichimoku cloud Bullish signals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a strong bullish signal, everything must occur above the Kumo cloud: The price action must remain &lt;strong&gt;above&lt;/strong&gt; the Kumo cloud. The Chinkou line must stay &lt;strong&gt;above&lt;/strong&gt; the kumo and Tenken should be crossing Kinjun also &lt;strong&gt;above&lt;/strong&gt; the Kumo. Tenken should be crossing upside - if this cross occurs inside of the Kumo that’s still bullish but not so strongly bullish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BASICS: Ichimoku cloud Bearish signals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for strong bearish signal, with Ichimoku cloud you can pretty much reverse all that has been said to bullish signals - price action occurs &lt;strong&gt;below&lt;/strong&gt; Kumo, as well as Tenken and Kinjun crossing and the lagging line Chinkou. Basically the more happens below the stronger the bears are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BASICS: None of this?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If none of this is happening then it most likely means that at your timeframe the market is &lt;em&gt;undecided, sideways, waiting for direction&lt;/em&gt;. Don’t worry, if a breakout happens the traders of twitter and reddit will call it - keep reading to learn whom to follow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-to-read-and-whom-to-follow&quot;&gt;What to read and whom to follow&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[TOOL]&lt;/strong&gt; Ichimoku Trading signals&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A whole website about it. None of anything is investment advice though - trade your thoughts. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ichimokutrader.com/signals.html&quot;&gt;See the signal page.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traders who tweet about Ichimoku cloud&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CarpeNoctom&lt;/strong&gt; (Josh Olszewicz)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/CarpeNoctom&quot;&gt;#BubbleMoku&lt;/a&gt; is the author of the above mentioned Youtube channel, and also DrWD on Reddit, as mentioned below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en-gb&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Busy chart that says we&amp;#39;re going up, so long as we don&amp;#39;t break 600. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;trgt = 840-940 BFX &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/j5pzJjXORI&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/j5pzJjXORI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; #BubbleMoku (@CarpeNoctom) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/CarpeNoctom/status/748010819775041542&quot;&gt;29 June 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Triforcetrader&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/triforcetrader&quot;&gt;Triforcetrader&lt;/a&gt; tweets general trading stuff since he is a full-time trader. Sometimes he’ll feaure some TA but there is plenty of it on his website - &lt;a href=&quot;http://triforcetrader.com/trading/ichimoku/&quot;&gt;Here is his post on Ichimoku cloud.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He made a video on how he trades Ichimoku cloud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;700&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/p_Z6ogQIE6E&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Redditors who post about Ichimoku cloud&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DrWD&lt;/strong&gt; (Josh Olszewicz) is probably the only consistent Ichimoku advocate in the cryptocurrency space on Reddit these days. He posts in the stickied threads on /r/BitcoinMarkets. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/drwd&quot;&gt;Bookmark his profile page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SFFWMorin&lt;/strong&gt; posted an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/StockMarket/comments/434jrn/ichimoku_cloud_how_to_trade_guide/&quot;&gt;Ichimoku cloud tutorial on the subreddit /r/StockMarkets&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;shifted-left&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe data-aa=&quot;147076&quot; src=&quot;https://ad.a-ads.com/147076?size=728x90&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; style=&quot;width:728px; height:90px; border:0px; padding:0;overflow:hidden&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/ichimoku-cloud/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/ichimoku-cloud/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
