<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <channel>
    <title>AltcoinTrading.NET Airdrops</title>
    <description>
      Upcoming Airdrops AltcoinTrading.NET
    </description>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.altcointrading.net/img/logo.jpg</url>
      <title>AltcoinTrading.NET</title>
      <link>https://www.altcointrading.net</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/airdrops/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.altcointrading.net/rss-airdrop-content.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 08:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 08:27:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <item>
        <title>All LIVE or soon launching Airdrops and Bounties</title>
        <description>
          <![CDATA[
            
<table class="airdrops">
  <tr>
    <th>Name</th>
    <th>Date</th>
    <th>How to access</th>
    <th>Official URL</th>
    <th>Additional Info</th>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>Ethermon.io rare monsters</td>
    <td>March 2020</td>
    <td>Play the 2019 relaunched, community-based version of Ethermon and catch rare monster that can be sold on Opensea or other markets. Value up to 2.5 ETH, average price for regular collectibles from Ethermon is at 0.15 ETH.</td>

    <td><a target="_blank" href="https://twitter.com/HBWallet_Ether/status/1237316654373068801">details</a></td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/38UmVEh">play</a></td>

  </tr>
<tr>
  <td>OKEx Welcome Bonus</td>
  <td>Feb 2020</td>
  <td>
    OKEx, formerly called OKCoin and known as OKCasino, was the BitMEX of 2015 but has fallen out of favour since. They are now running a similar campaign as Coinbase did to get their signup rates up: If you sign up and buy 100 USD worth of BTC, you get 10 USD bonus.
  </td>
  <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/okex-affilatnet-2020">details</a></td>
  <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/okex-affilatnet-2020">make acct</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
  <td>Blockstack 🔥 Free crypto airdrop</td>
  <td>Jan - Feb 2020</td>
  <td>
    The webwallet blockchain.com is giving away free Stack $STX crypto to their Gold users. The Gold level requires an ID scan and selfie.
  </td>
  <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2FmvStN">details</a></td>
  <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2FmvStN">make acct</a></td>
</tr>

<tr>
  <td>PRIMEDICE Free crypto promotion</td>
  <td>Until 28 Dec 2019</td>
  <td>
    Deposit more than $5 in BTC, ETH, XRP, BCH or DOGE - get free $3 in LTC (credited after 24 hours). No rollover condition or restriction!
  </td>
  <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2WT2CD3">details</a></td>
  <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2WT2CD3">make acct</a></td>
</tr>

  <tr>
    <td>Cloudbet Turbo Thursday Reload Bonus</td>
    <td>Every Thursday between 05:00-23:59 UTC</td>
    <td>
      Make a deposit of 0.1 mBTC or more today, Cloudbet gives you a 100% Reload Bonus of up to 50 mBTC/1 BCH. Remember you must activate the bonus in your player dashboard before making a deposit for the bonus to be credited! The bonus is only available for the Casino, not the Sportsbook.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2BhLXyK">details</a></td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2BhLXyK">make acct</a></td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>New non-custodial anonymous peer-to-peer Bitcoin trading</td>
    <td>Opened 19 Nov 2019</td>
    <td>
      If you miss the heyday of LocalBitcoins where anyone could buy BTC locally for cash (which has been banned since this summer) and anonymously (now site-wide KYC is required, plus allegedly LocalBitcoins have been working with three-letter agencies), since 19th November you have the chance to go back in time and buy your corn without ID again - at least for some time. You know that good things like this don't last ...
       The former ETH marketplace LocalEthereum rebranded to LocalCryptos and offers local and anonymous BTC trading with fully automated escrow that is built natively on BTC blockchain - because bitcoin's smart contract scripting capabilities are good enough for simple stuff like escrows. You can even import your vendor reputation from LocalBitcoins.
       The reputation import is done via adding a unique code to your LBC profile page, not by linking anything directly, but still in case you like your privacy it's probably only a good idea id you never ID'd on LocalBitcoins.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/localcryptos">details</a></td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/localcryptos">make acct</a></td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>Crypto Flowers dApp Game event</td>
    <td>12 - 22 Dec 2019</td>
    <td>
      Play the Crypto Flowers TRON version of the dApp game any time between 12 and 22 December to enter the Prize Pool of 100`000 TRX. Just collect and breed flowers and have a chance to win prize pool, no special action needed.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/36HfT55">details</a></td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/36HfT55">make acct</a></td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>POOL-X exchange listing promo</td>
    <td>Daily until listing</td>
    <td>
      POL has a random twitter draw of users who post a POOL-X graphic design every day until their token listing on the KuCoin exchange. You need to sign up via Google form and have a KuCoin account.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2OeL9AL">form</a></td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/32HQ6HP">make acct</a></td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>Verasity New Triviata Competition</td>
    <td>November 5 at 00:00 UTC - November 20th 00:00 UTC</td>
    <td>
      Verasity is a token-based platform for the attention economy. They always engaged a lot with the community and organized several airdrop and competition campaigns so far.
      The current two-week campaign relates to the Triviata app (iOS/Android). Sign up and enable your game participation in the app profile, and you get the chance of winning prizes with 4000 USD in total. Even if you don't win though, participating will earn you tokens that can be staked in the official wallet for over 30% yearly earnings.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="https://triviata.onelink.me/M2h9/b8ec2cf4">join</a></td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="https://www.thebusinessofcrypto.com/articles/verasity-token-listings-airdropped/">about</a></td>
  </tr>

<tr>
  <td>Bethereum Price Pool on VK</td>
  <td>November 2019</td>
  <td>
    There are regular competitions with the total pool of prizes worth 40K Bether if you join the gaming platform's VK channel.
  </td>
  <td><a target="_blank" href="https://medium.com/bethereum/join-our-vk-channel-october-competition-5b480c305b62">details</a></td>
  <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/35cLg7K">make acct</a></td>
</tr>

  <tr>
    <td>Brave New Coin Challenge</td>
    <td>Until the end of the year</td>
    <td>
      The crypto market data provider is giving away small amount of their tokens if you add people to their telegram group.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="https://challenge.bravenewcoin.com/">register</a></td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="https://t.me/joinchat/IedL3Bdfw5lv2YW8IXAmgg">telegram</a></td>
  </tr>

  <tr>
    <td>FanEspo Big Competition (ERC20)</td>
    <td>All the time</td>
    <td>
      Fanespo is launching a new promotion contest worth $500 in FAN tokens. Details will pop up on you when you sign up on site. Overall, the eSports platform FanEspo is giving away the total of $1.6 million of tokens in contests. You need to have a FanEspo account.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2Gv2ZvJ">details</a></td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2Gv2ZvJ">make acct</a></td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>Atomars Opportunity</td>
    <td>Launch promo</td>
    <td>
      There is a new altcoin axchange launched that now offers zero-fee trading, and possibly thinner markets for the market makers around.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2mo9Gco">details</a></td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2mo9Gco">make acct</a></td>
  </tr>

  <tr>
    <td>Keybase Stellar Lumens Drop</td>
    <td>11 September 2019 & Onwards</td>
    <td>
      The Keybase team announced a surprise airdrop worth 21 USD in XLM to all account holders who ever installed the Keybase app. To get the Lumens, you need to sign in again and claim them - you should have received a bot message with instructions. Keybase has been funded by the Stellar Developer Foundation for years and so this collab is not a one-off. You can choose to keep participating in the Lumens airdrop by using Keybase, the total dollar worth each user can get is 500 USD. New accounts can still participate as long as they have a Github or HackerNews account created before 9 September 2019.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="https://keybase.io/airdrop">more</a></td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="https://keybase.io/airdrop">join</a></td>
  </tr>


    <tr>
      <td>BlockWage Airdrops + Bounties</td>
      <td>Recurring</td>
      <td>
        Platform for freelancers marketplace. Airdrops randomly announced via Discord, there's also the possibility of Masternodes.
      </td>
      <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2U7IaLB">join</a></td>
      <td><a target="_blank" href="https://blockwage.net">web</a></td>
    </tr>

    <tr>
      <td>Vaultoro Token Launch Promo</td>
      <td>September 2019</td>
      <td>
        The crypto-gold exchange Vaultoro has been around for years, getting attention in the 2015 bear market and tagging along through the subsequent bull run. They are now launching their own exchange token which you can get for free if you don't have an account yet. Every new sign up with basic ID verification gets 200 VAULT tokens.
      </td>
      <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2Msxbgs">homepage</a></td>
      <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2Msxbgs">make acct</a></td>
    </tr>

</table>

          ]]>
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 08:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>airdrops@altcointrading.net</author>
        <webmaster>airdrops@altcointrading.net</webmaster>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/airdrops/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/airdrops/</guid>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
