<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <channel>
    <title>AltcoinTrading.NET Airdrops</title>
    <description>
      Upcoming Airdrops AltcoinTrading.NET
    </description>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.altcointrading.net/img/logo.jpg</url>
      <title>AltcoinTrading.NET</title>
      <link>https://www.altcointrading.net</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/airdrops/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.altcointrading.net/rss-airdrop-content.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 03:44:53 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 03:44:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <item>
        <title>All LIVE or soon launching Airdrops and Bounties</title>
        <description>
          <![CDATA[
            
<table class="airdrops">
  <tr>
    <th>Token and platform</th>
    <th>Date</th>
    <th>How to get the airdrop</th>
    <th>Link</th>
  </tr>

  <tr>
    <td>The Crown of Elrond Competition on Bitfinex</td>
    <td>Between 10 Sep (10:00:00 AM UTC) and 13 Sep (11:59:59 PM UTC)</td>
    <td>
      Bitfinex is promoting the launch of EGLD trading with a daily prize pool 900 EGLD for users who deposit at least 20 EGLD and complete at last one trade on the Elrond's USD or USDt market. Daily prize goes to the first 30 users who meet the condition each day. Competitors must get verified to at least intermediate level.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="https://bit.ly/bfx2020-bl">more here</a></td>

  </tr>

  <tr>
    <td>Opportunity: Ledger Wallet 20% Discount Coupon</td>
    <td>Until 21 September 2020</td>
    <td>
      Ledger wallet released a September 2020 discount code. The promo code is good for either the Nano X or Nano S, if you want to get both check their bundle offers.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/at-backtoschool">get code</a></td>
  </tr>

  <tr>
    <td>Cloudbet Turbo Thursday Reload Bonus</td>
    <td>Every Thursday between 05:00-23:59 UTC</td>
    <td>
      Make a deposit of 0.1 mBTC or more today, Cloudbet gives you a 100% Reload Bonus of up to 50 mBTC/1 BCH. Remember you must activate the bonus in your player dashboard before making a deposit for the bonus to be credited! The bonus is only available for the Casino, not the Sportsbook.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2BhLXyK">details</a></td>
  </tr>

   <tr>
    <td>Markaccy Bounty Launch promo</td>
    <td>Until 30 September 2020</td>
    <td>
      MKCY is a token that is starting to trade on HOTBIT in September 2020. There are weekly social media bounties that must be reported into the linked bitcointalk thread.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="https://bit.ly/3lFMAse">report here</a></td>
  </tr>

  <tr>
    <td>Opportunity: Negative Fees on Vaultoro Gold markets</td>
    <td>Since 22nd of July 2020</td>
    <td>
      The gold trading platform Vaultoro is now offering negative fees for market makers. The rebate is 0.05% at any traded volume, however it only applies to crypto markets there - not to gold markets. At least the gold fees got cut back to pre-COVID levels on Vaultoro.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="https://bit.ly/31KqL1m">more here</a></td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>OKEx Crypto Signup Bonus</td>
    <td>Bonus for Signup</td>
    <td>
      OKEx, formerly called OKCoin and known as OKCasino, was the BitMEX of 2015 but has fallen out of favour since. They are now running a similar campaign as Coinbase did to get their signup rates up: If you sign up and buy 100 USD worth of BTC, you get 10 USD bonus.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/okex-affilatnet-2020">details</a></td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>New non-custodial anonymous peer-to-peer Bitcoin trading</td>
    <td>Opened 19 Nov 2019</td>
    <td>
      If you miss the heyday of LocalBitcoins where anyone could buy BTC locally for cash (which has been banned since this summer) and anonymously (now site-wide KYC is required, plus allegedly LocalBitcoins have been working with three-letter agencies), since 19th November you have the chance to go back in time and buy your corn without ID again - at least for some time. You know that good things like this don't last ...
       The former ETH marketplace LocalEthereum rebranded to LocalCryptos and offers local and anonymous BTC trading with fully automated escrow that is built natively on BTC blockchain - because bitcoin's smart contract scripting capabilities are good enough for simple stuff like escrows. You can even import your vendor reputation from LocalBitcoins.
       The reputation import is done via adding a unique code to your LBC profile page, not by linking anything directly, but still in case you like your privacy it's probably only a good idea id you never ID'd on LocalBitcoins.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/localcryptos">details</a></td>
  </tr>


</table>

          ]]>
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 03:44:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>airdrops@altcointrading.net</author>
        <webmaster>airdrops@altcointrading.net</webmaster>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/airdrops/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/airdrops/</guid>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
