<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
version="2.0"
xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
xmlns:yandex="http://news.yandex.ru"
xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
xmlns:turbo="http://turbo.yandex.ru">
  <channel>
    <title>AltcoinTrading.NET Airdrops</title>
    <description>
      Crypto Black Friday 2020 - Live Deals
    </description>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.altcointrading.net/img/doge-share.png</url>
      <title>AltcoinTrading.NET</title>
      <link>https://www.altcointrading.net</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/blackfriday/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.altcointrading.net/rss-blackfriday.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 06:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 06:11:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
    
      <item>
        <title><![CDATA[ BillFodl + Hardware Wallet Bundles ]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[  ]]></description>
        <content:encoded><![CDATA[ 



BillFodl (or PrivacyPros) is coming up with bundle deals with all currently existing wallets.

The steel plate wallet is compatible with the seed format of Trezor, Ledger and KeepKey wallet.

This is a brand new 2020 deal.

Current bundle prices depend on the version of the hardware wallet as their tech gets out of date more quickly.

BillFodl &amp;amp; HW Wallet Bundle Prices, ordered from the most expensive to the cheapest option:


  Trezor T + BillFodl Bundle - 240 USD
  Ledger Nano X + BillFodl Bundle - 199 USD
  Ledger Nano S + BillFodl Bundle - 139 USD
  Trezor One + BillFodl - 145 USD
  KeepKey + BillFodl - 109 USD


Get Your BillFodl Bundle on PrivacyPros

About Billfodl

Billfodl is next to Cryptosteel one of the leaders in true cold storage for crypto - producer of the super resistant metal private key storage for the paranoid.

Billfodl is made 100% of the highest quality 316 stainless steel that has super high melting point (to withstand house fires), is very resistant to corrosion (even in salt water) and also completely shock-proof (to withstand explosions). Very good for your cold storage coins that never move.

They also have bundle packs of multiple steel plates, in case you are ultra paranoid and want to split your main money seed in two to store it in two different locations.

Other than that, you can newly get a bundle of Billfodl and a hardware crypto wallet. There are bundles with Ledger, Trezor and KeepKey wallets available.
The e-shop at PrivacyPros accepts payments in all major debit or credit cards as well as the usual set of cryptocurrencies (BTC, LTC, ETH, XMR, DOGE). You can split your payment into interest-free installments.
NOTE: Billfodl wallets ship from the US and only show prices before tax on their e-shop. If you're outside the US you will need to pay extra duties on your order.


 ]]></content:encoded>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 07:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>shill.shillerton@altcointrading.net</author>
        <webmaster>shill.shillerton@altcointrading.net</webmaster>
        <media:content url="https://www.altcointrading.nethttps://res.cloudinary.com/atnetcloud/image/upload/c_lpad,h_360,w_700/v1604371162/atnet/altcoin-wallets/Screenshot_2020-11-03_at_9.38.31_AM_hgtusf.jpg" medium="image" />
        <link>" | prepend: site.baseurl | prepend: site.url }}</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">" | prepend: site.baseurl | prepend: site.url }}</guid>
        <category><![CDATA[ billfodl ]]></category><category><![CDATA[ ledger ]]></category><category><![CDATA[ keepkey ]]></category><category><![CDATA[ trezor ]]></category><category><![CDATA[ hardware-wallet ]]></category><category><![CDATA[ bundle ]]></category><category><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency-wallet ]]></category>
        <category><![CDATA[ live ]]></category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title><![CDATA[ Ledger Wallet Bundle Deals ]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[  ]]></description>
        <content:encoded><![CDATA[ 



Ledger Wallet Family Pack: Up to 21% off per device

Ledger Wallet Bundle Offer - September 2020: 6-21% Discount per device

★★★★★

Ledger wallet keeps with their usual strategy of discounting wallet bundles through the year, and in 2020 we get 3 different Ledger wallet bundles.

You can get a Ledger Family Pack (triplet of Nano S wallets or triplet of Nano X wallets) and a Ledger Backup Pack which has one of each Ledger Nano devices.

Your discount gets higher for packs with Nano S wallets, as the Ledger Nano S is the older product.

2020 Ledger Wallet Bundle Discounts - Price Breakdown


  Ledger Nano S family Pack: 3x Ledger Nano S ~ 21% off
    
      GO TO OFFER
    
  
  Ledger Backup Pack: 1x Ledger Nano S + 1x Ledger Nano X ~ 18% off
    
      GO TO OFFER
    
  
  Ledger Nano X family Pack: 3x Ledger Nano X ~ 16% off
    
      GO TO OFFER
    
  


Why it’s good to have more than one hardware wallet

The best way to make use of the Ledger discount code deal is to have as big a total bill as possible:


  You can buy Ledger Nano X to use as your cold-ish storage. The Ledger Nano X is a Bluetooth® enabled secure device that stores the private keys of your cryptocurrencies. It has extended memory capacity, which means it can house keys of more cryptocurrencies than Ledger Nano S.
  Ledger Nano S is cheaper but can pretty much operate with a single crypto on it only, due to the small memory. That makes it ideal for a single-purpose wallet.
  So, if you trade mostly with, say, Bitcoin as your base currency, Ledger Nano S is the most time-, cost- and security-efficient wallet to serve as your trading wallet.


It’s also useful to have a separate wallet for the darknetmarkets. Speaking purely hypothetically of course.
 ]]></content:encoded>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 08:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>shill.shillerton@altcointrading.net</author>
        <webmaster>shill.shillerton@altcointrading.net</webmaster>
        <media:content url="https://www.altcointrading.nethttps://res.cloudinary.com/atnetcloud/image/upload/c_lpad,h_360,w_700/v1588053412/atnet/altcoin-wallets/Screen_Shot_2020-04-28_at_12.55.57_zikwqu.jpg" medium="image" />
        <link>" | prepend: site.baseurl | prepend: site.url }}</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">" | prepend: site.baseurl | prepend: site.url }}</guid>
        <category><![CDATA[ ledger ]]></category><category><![CDATA[ hardware-wallet ]]></category><category><![CDATA[ bundle ]]></category>
        <category><![CDATA[ live ]]></category>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
