<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <channel>
    <title>AltcoinTrading.NET Airdrops</title>
    <description>
      Upcoming Airdrops AltcoinTrading.NET
    </description>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.altcointrading.net/img/logo.jpg</url>
      <title>AltcoinTrading.NET</title>
      <link>https://www.altcointrading.net</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/airdrops/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.altcointrading.net/rss-airdrop-content.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 04:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 04:57:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <item>
        <title>All LIVE or soon launching Airdrops and Bounties</title>
        <description>
          <![CDATA[
            
<table class="airdrops">
  <tr>
    <th>Name</th>
    <th>Date</th>
    <th>How to access</th>
    <th>Official URL</th>
    <th>Additional Info</th>
  </tr>



<tr>
  <td>New Opportunity: Negative Fees on Vaultoro</td>
  <td>Since 22nd of July 2020</td>
  <td>
    The gold trading platform Vaultoro is now offering negative fees for market makers. The rebate is 0.05% at any traded volume, however it only applies to crypto markets there - not to gold markets. At least the gold fees got cut back to pre-COVID levels on Vaultoro.
  </td>
  <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2kwSK38">more here</a></td>
</tr>

  <tr>
    <td>Cloudbet Turbo Thursday Reload Bonus</td>
    <td>Every Thursday between 05:00-23:59 UTC</td>
    <td>
      Make a deposit of 0.1 mBTC or more today, Cloudbet gives you a 100% Reload Bonus of up to 50 mBTC/1 BCH. Remember you must activate the bonus in your player dashboard before making a deposit for the bonus to be credited! The bonus is only available for the Casino, not the Sportsbook.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2BhLXyK">details</a></td>

  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>OKEx Crypto Signup Bonus</td>
    <td>Bonus for Signup</td>
    <td>
      OKEx, formerly called OKCoin and known as OKCasino, was the BitMEX of 2015 but has fallen out of favour since. They are now running a similar campaign as Coinbase did to get their signup rates up: If you sign up and buy 100 USD worth of BTC, you get 10 USD bonus.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/okex-affilatnet-2020">details</a></td>
  </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>CPD project airdrop to BTC holders</td>
      <td>At BTC halving block</td>
      <td>
        CPD project airdrops tokens at BTC halving to anyone who signups with an ETH address and submits a BTC address that is verified via a signed message. The project aims at creating less monopolized internet environment for innovatiove development.
      </td>
      <td><a target="_blank" href="https://bit.ly/3b2FJSW">details</a></td>
    </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>Ethermon.io ChainGuardians Discord Airdrop and Signup Bonus</td>
    <td>April 2020</td>
    <td>
      Ethermon announced on Apr 13 that some of their Mons will be part of a new blockchain RPG game developed by ChainGuardians. There is a discord promo for this launch: On the launch date of the ChainGuardians Official NFT Sale, 150 EMONT will be airdropped to the first 10 people who post a screenshot on Discord fighting a Zedakazm within the ChainGuardians RPG along with proof of purchase (TXID)of any ChainGuardians bundle.
      The signup bonus is to play ChainGuardians game logged in via an anonymous identity from SafeName.io. You get 100 FREE CGC valued at 0.05 ETH, the link to claim is at the page where you land after confirming your email.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/3a0CNqi">Signup at Ethermon</a></td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>Blockstack Free crypto airdrop</td>
    <td>Jan - Feb 2020</td>
    <td>
      The webwallet blockchain.com is giving away free Stack $STX crypto to their Gold users. The Gold level requires an ID scan and selfie.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2FmvStN">details</a></td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>New non-custodial anonymous peer-to-peer Bitcoin trading</td>
    <td>Opened 19 Nov 2019</td>
    <td>
      If you miss the heyday of LocalBitcoins where anyone could buy BTC locally for cash (which has been banned since this summer) and anonymously (now site-wide KYC is required, plus allegedly LocalBitcoins have been working with three-letter agencies), since 19th November you have the chance to go back in time and buy your corn without ID again - at least for some time. You know that good things like this don't last ...
       The former ETH marketplace LocalEthereum rebranded to LocalCryptos and offers local and anonymous BTC trading with fully automated escrow that is built natively on BTC blockchain - because bitcoin's smart contract scripting capabilities are good enough for simple stuff like escrows. You can even import your vendor reputation from LocalBitcoins.
       The reputation import is done via adding a unique code to your LBC profile page, not by linking anything directly, but still in case you like your privacy it's probably only a good idea id you never ID'd on LocalBitcoins.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/localcryptos">details</a></td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>Crypto Flowers dApp Game event</td>
    <td>12 - 22 Dec 2019</td>
    <td>
      Play the Crypto Flowers TRON version of the dApp game any time between 12 and 22 December to enter the Prize Pool of 100`000 TRX. Just collect and breed flowers and have a chance to win prize pool, no special action needed.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/36HfT55">details</a></td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>FanEspo Big Competition (ERC20)</td>
    <td>All the time</td>
    <td>
      Fanespo is launching a new promotion contest worth $500 in FAN tokens. Details will pop up on you when you sign up on site. Overall, the eSports platform FanEspo is giving away the total of $1.6 million of tokens in contests. You need to have a FanEspo account.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2Gv2ZvJ">details</a></td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>Atomars Opportunity</td>
    <td>Launch promo</td>
    <td>
      There is a new altcoin axchange launched that now offers zero-fee trading, and possibly thinner markets for the market makers around.
    </td>
    <td><a target="_blank" href="http://bit.ly/2mo9Gco">details</a></td>
  </tr>


</table>

          ]]>
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 04:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>airdrops@altcointrading.net</author>
        <webmaster>airdrops@altcointrading.net</webmaster>
        <link>https://www.altcointrading.net/airdrops/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.altcointrading.net/airdrops/</guid>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
